<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<danh_sach_truyen>
	<truyen ten="star wars: the last jedi adaptation" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Movies - tv, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>star wars: the last jedi adaptation</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>star-wars-the-last-jedi-adaptation</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Gary Whitta, Michael Walsh</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/s/star-wars-the-last-jedi-adaptation/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The Resistance has found Luke Skywalker! But the First Order is hot on their tail... and they are out for blood. Join writer Gary Whitta (ROGUE ONE: A STAR WARS STORY) and artist Michael Walsh (STAR WARS ANNUAL, HAWKEYE and THE VISION) as they take on the adventures of Force prodigy Rey, ace pilot Poe Dameron, and ex-First Order recruit Finn from the hit blockbuster STAR WARS: THE LAST JEDI - featuring never-before-seen scenes of your favorite characters!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/star-wars-the-last-jedi-adaptation-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="the wicked righteous" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Post-apocalyptic" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>the wicked righteous</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>the-wicked-righteous</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Terry Mayo, Chris Hall, Lucas Romero, Brandon DeStefano</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/the-wicked-righteous/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Biological warfare has decimated the earth's population, leaving two distinct groups of survivors in its wake. In San Diego, four teenage brothers rescue a young girl from a brutal gang of psychopaths and spark a chain of events that attracts an onslaught of unspeakable evil. This is the world of the Wicked and the Righteous... and the children will lead them all.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/the-wicked-righteous-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="the spider king" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Fantasy, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>the spider king</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>the-spider-king</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Josh Vann, Simone D'Armini</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/the-spider-king/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>When a fleet of spaceships crashes into northern Europe in 956 AD, a group of unlikely Viking heroes are the last line of defense against a brutal intergalactic warlord. Equal parts science fiction and fantasy, The Spider King follows the adventures of Viking warriors as they defend their world against alien invaders armed with futuristic technology and impossible weapons.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/the-spider-king-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="peter parker: the spectacular spider-man" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>peter parker: the spectacular spider-man</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>peter-parker-the-spectacular-spider-man</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Chip Zdarsky, Adam Kubert</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/p/peter-parker-the-spectacular-spider-man/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>SPIDER-MAN RETURNS TO THE FRIENDLY NEIGHBORHOOD! The webslinging, wallcrawling wonder returns to New York City in the all-new PETER PARKER: THE SPECTACULAR SPIDER-MAN. A companion series to the best-selling Amazing Spider-Man series, Peter Parker is going back-to-basics for big heroics in the Big Apple. Featuring adversaries old and new, be there as Spider-Man returns to his friendly neighborhood for his never ending battle against crime and the dreaded 'Parker Luck'.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/peter-parker-the-spectacular-spider-man-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="the immortal men" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>the immortal men</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>the-immortal-men</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>James Tynion IV, Ryan Benjamin, Jim Lee</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/the-immortal-men/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>There is a secret history to the DC Universe of heroes who have protected humanity from the shadows since the dawn of time... and who can live forever. Enter the Immortal Men! The team, headed by the Immortal Man, has waged a secret war against the House of Conquest for countless years-but Conquest has dealt a devastating blow. When their base of operations, known as the Campus, is savagely attacked, the Immortal Men must seek out their last hope-an emerging metahuman known as Caden Park! Caden's emerging powers may be able to ensure the Immortal Men's survival-but will Conquest get to him first?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/the-immortal-men-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="you are deadpool" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>you are deadpool</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>you-are-deadpool</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Al Ewing, Salvador Espin, Rahzzah</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/y/you-are-deadpool/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>DID YOU EVER WANT TO BE DEADPOOL??? Now's your chance! This series is not JUST the most amazing comic book you've ever read... it's also a role-playing adventure! YOU decide what choices Deadpool makes!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/you-are-deadpool-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="batman and the signal" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>batman and the signal</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>batman-and-the-signal</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Tony Patrick, Scott Snyder, Cully Hamner, Laura Martin</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Comic_Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/b/batman-and-the-signal/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Batman may own the night, but with new villains emerging during the day he needs an ally to defend the city when he can't. Only one teen is up to the challenge, Duke Thomas. After months of training, he's ready to step out of the shadow of the bat to become his own kind of hero. Meet Gotham City's newest protector: The Signal! Spinning out of adventures in ALL-STAR BATMAN and WE ARE ROBIN, comics superstar Scott Snyder and newcomer Tony Patrick take our young hero to new heights in this exciting miniseries with artwork by Cully Hamner.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Completed/batman-and-the-signal-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="sheena: queen of the jungle (2017)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fanservice, Leading ladies" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>sheena: queen of the jungle (2017)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>sheena-queen-of-the-jungle-2017</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Marguerite Bennett, Christina Trujillo, Moritat</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/s/sheena-queen-of-the-jungle-(2017)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>In this riveting relaunch, the guardian of the jungle, SHEENA, pursues a mysterious invader that has come to spy on the Amazon's most ancient secrets... Following the path of the trespasser, she encounters a forbidden ruin in which even more deadly dangers lie in wait and begins an adventure that will take her beyond her wildest imaginings!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/sheena-queen-of-the-jungle-2017-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="mera: queen of atlantis" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>mera: queen of atlantis</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>mera-queen-of-atlantis</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Dan Abnett, Lan Medina, Richard Friend, Veronica Gandini</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/m/mera-queen-of-atlantis/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>From the pages of AQUAMAN comes a brand-new adventure starring Mera, in her own title for the first time ever! As the brutal Atlantean Civil War rages, Mera must keep the peace between the surface world and Atlantis as its newly anointed queen in exile. But when Aquaman's brother Orm, a.k.a. Ocean Master, learns of his homeland's fate, he'll stop at nothing to return to Atlantis as its king and savior!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/mera-queen-of-atlantis-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="captain america (2017)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>captain america (2017)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>captain-america-2017</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Mark Waid, Chris Samnee</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/c/captain-america-(2017)/695_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>HOME OF THE BRAVE begins - and Steve Rogers is back in action in the red-white-and-blue! Steve begins a journey across America to restore his tarnished reputation - and the dangers he encounters along the way are unlike any he`s faced before!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/captain-america-2017-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="venomized" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>venomized</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>venomized</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Cullen Bunn, Iban Coello</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/v/venomized/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The story that began in VENOMVERSE reaches its epic conclusion with VENOMIZED! The POISONS, a species that hungers for super-powered symbiotes and their hosts, have picked their next target... THE MARVEL UNIVERSE ITSELF! Their first objective? Put every superhuman in a Klyntar symbiote - and CONSUME THEM! But with VENOM and the X-MEN still missing after the events of 'Poison-X,' the planet and its heroes are defenseless!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/venomized-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="ninja-k" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>ninja-k</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>ninja-k</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Christos N. Gage, Tomas Giorello</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/n/ninja-k-(2017)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>A NEW CAN'T-MISS ONGOING SERIES! From acclaimed writer Christos Gage (Netflix's Daredevil) and superstar artist Tomas Giorello (X-O MANOWAR), the United Kingdom's most dreaded intelligence operative delves into the cold, calculating world of espionage and international intrigue!nFor nearly a century, MI-6, the most elite branch of Britain's clandestine intelligence service, has honed a ruthlessly effective, top-secret division - THE NINJA PROGRAMME - into one of its nation's most finely wielded weapons. Tasked as the first and last line of defense for queen and country, this small shadow army of agents and assassins has produced a succession of notable assets, including NINJA-A, the Queen's silent weapon of World War I; NINJA-E, the globe-trotting secret agent that pulled the Cold War back from the brink of Armageddon; and, most recently, NINJA-K, aka Colin King, a brash but fearless instrument of lethality that has saved the world from madmen and terror at every turn. But now... an unknown enemy is hunting and killing members of THE NINJA PROGRAMME one by one and NINJAK is next on the list.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/ninja-k-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="rise of the black panther" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>rise of the black panther</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>rise-of-the-black-panther</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Ta-Nehisi Coates, Evan Narcisse, Paul Renaud, Brian Stelfreeze</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/r/rise-of-the-black-panther-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Just in time for the highly anticipated film, witness the early years of the man who will come to rule one of the most scientifically advanced countries in the world! Wakanda has always kept itself isolated from Western society, but that's all about to change. Young T'Challa knows he is destined to become king, but when his father is brutally murdered by outsiders, he'll find himself taking up a mantle he may not be ready for. Experience never-before-seen drama from the reign of T'Chaka, the king whose death changes a nation's history forever. Learn about the mother T'Challa never knew. See how the world learns about this wondrous nation for the first time. Will the power of the Black Panther be enough to keep his country safe? Journalist Evan Narcisse makes his comics debut alongside acclaimed writer Ta-Nehisi Coates as they chronicle T'Challa's rise to the throne - and to the Panther legacy that made him an Avenger.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/rise-of-the-black-panther-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="agent 47: birth of the hitman" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Spy, Video games" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>agent 47: birth of the hitman</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>agent-47-birth-of-the-hitman</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Christopher Sebela, Ariel Medel, Jonathan Lau</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/a/agent-47-birth-of-the-hitman/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>47 and his handler, Diana Burnwood, are a team responsible for some of the most ruthless, efficient and untraceable assassinations across the globe. But before they were operatives of the shadowy International Contracts Association, 47 and Burnwood were on their own separate paths in life streets lined with blood, bullets and revenge. As 14-year-old Diana begins a mission to track down the people who killed her parents, the one responsible, 47, is struggling to free himself and his brother, 6, from the mysterious Institute which has bred them as killers since they were kids. With a story that stretches from the heartland of America to the Berlin Wall, Lone Wolves will trace the birth of the legendary Hitman and the secret past of the woman behind him who pulls the string and knows just how hard taking a life truly is.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/agent-47-birth-of-the-hitman-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="marvel's ant-man and the wasp prelude" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>marvel's ant-man and the wasp prelude</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>marvel-s-ant-man-and-the-wasp</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Will Corona Pilgrim, Chris Allen</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/m/marvels-ant-man-and-the-wasp-prelude/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>SCOTT LANG's life is a bit of a mess. But when he got out of jail (yeah, jail), he swore he'd to turn it all around. Go straight. Show his daughter and ex-wife he's worthy of being a role model. But when a 'last score' lands him in HANK PYM's size-changing suit, Scott finds himself in a brand-new role: as the ANT-MAN! Hank needs someone with Scott's skills to stop DARREN CROSS from weaponizing his size-changing technology, and it's going to take the team of Scott, Hank and HOPE (daughter of the original WASP) to save the day! The adventure doesn't get any bigger (smaller?!) than this! See Scott's first mission as the ANT-MAN, and how HOPE VAN DYNE became the WASP in this adaptation of the original hit film before this summer's feature MARVEL'S ANT-MAN AND THE WASP!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Completed/marvel-s-ant-man-and-the-wasp-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="suicide squad: hell to pay" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>suicide squad: hell to pay</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>suicide-squad-hell-to-pay</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jeff Parker, Matthew Dow Smith</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/s/suicide-squad-hell-to-pay/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Amanda Waller has her 'Get Out of Hell Free' card, but why did she go to such lengths to acquire it?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/suicide-squad-hell-to-pay-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="old man hawkeye" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>old man hawkeye</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>old-man-hawkeye</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Ethan Sacks, Marco Checchetto</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/o/old-man-hawkeye/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The super heroes have fallen. The country has been divided into territories controlled by super villains. Among the wastelands lives CLINT BARTON - one of the few Avengers to survive. But it's been 45 years, and he's no Avenger. Trying to eke out a living anyway he can, the former HAWKEYE is confronted with a startling discovery: the sharpshooter is going blind. With time running short, Clint realizes there's one last thing he wants to see: revenge for his fallen comrades-in-arms. Rising-star writer ETHAN SACKS and superstar artist MARCO CHECCHETTO take you back to the Wastelands in a story set five years before the original classic OLD MAN LOGAN.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/old-man-hawkeye-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="raven  " tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy, Magic, Superhero, Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>raven  </ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>raven</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Alisson Borges, Marv Wolfman</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/r/raven/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>In a tale set between TEEN TITANS #24 and TEEN TITANS: REBIRTH #1, Raven takes a break from the team and moves to San Francisco to stay with her estranged aunt and face her most perilous challenge yet: high school! As Raven discovers more about her human side, one of her classmates goes missing under mysterious circumstances, and she must face an evil like none she's known before!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Completed/raven-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="new mutants: dead souls" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>new mutants: dead souls</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>new-mutants-dead-souls</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Matt Rosenberg, Adam Gorham, Ryan Stegman</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/n/new-mutants-dead-souls/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>THEY AREN'T JUST THE X-MEN IN TRAINING ANYMORE! The New Mutants are launching themselves headfirst into some of the creepiest corners of the Marvel Universe, going on the missions no one else will. But does the team know what they are really hunting for? And what are they willing to do to get it? The enigmatic MAGIK will lead her team of WOLFSBANE, RICTOR, BOOM-BOOM and STRONG GUY and bring them face-to-face with paranormal threats that they may not be prepared for, and that might just tear them apart! Rising-star writer Matthew Rosenberg (PHOENIX RESURRECTION) teams up with future superstars Adam Gorham and Michael Garland (ROCKET) to bring you the next chapter in the lives of Marvel's underdog team. Welcome to the new class of New Mutants - hope you make it out alive.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/new-mutants-dead-souls-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="sideways" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Movies - tv, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>sideways</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>sideways</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Dan Didio, Justin Jordan, Kenneth Rocafort, Dan Brown</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/s/sideways/2_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>During the events of DARK NIGHTS: METAL, high school junior Derek James accidentally fell through a rift into the dark matter dimension! Now, as Sideways, he can create rifts in midair to leap through dimensions at will! But with that much power comes great liability and cracks are starting to form in the fabric of the space-time continuum...</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/sideways-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="accell" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Movies - tv, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>accell</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>accell</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Joe Casey, Robert Campanella, Damion Scott</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/c/catalyst-prime-accell/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Daniel DosSantos is a young man living at the speed of life. After gaining powers from exposure to an extraterrestrial object, DosSantos became the rapid action superhero called Accell, the first of a new public kind of self-appointed crime fighter. Unfortunately, there are consequences to moving faster than sound. Accell is about to learn that danger exists on the flipside of having superpowers and will have to grow up quickly to survive.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/accell-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="star wars: thrawn" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Movies - tv, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>star wars: thrawn</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>star-wars-thrawn</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jody Houser, Luke Ross, Paul Renaud</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/s/star-wars-thrawn/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>One of the most cunning and ruthless minds in all of the Star Wars, Grand Admiral Thrawn is back with his own six-issue miniseries! Written by Jody Houser (ROGUE ONE ADAPTATION) and drawn by Luke Ross (STAR WARS: DARTH MAUL, STAR WARS: THE FORCE AWAKENS ADAPTATION), follow the comic adaptation of Timothy Zahn's New York Times best-selling novel about Thrawn's rise in the Imperial ranks, on his way to becoming one of the most feared military tacticians in the galaxy far, far away.!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/star-wars-thrawn-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="ben reilly: scarlet spider" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>ben reilly: scarlet spider</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>ben-reilly-scarlet-spider</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Peter David, Mark Bagley</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/b/ben-reilly-the-scarlet-spider/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>One of the most controversial characters in comics has returned and the controversy has only BEGUN! In the aftermath of THE CLONE CONSPIRACY, Ben has a new take on life... and he's not the same Scarlet Spider he was before. Come witness what will be the most talked about comic of the year!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/ben-reilly-scarlet-spider-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="falcon (2017)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>falcon (2017)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>falcon-2017</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Rodney Barnes, Joshua Cassara, Jesus Saiz</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/f/falcon-(2017)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>In the wake of SECRET EMPIRE, Sam Wilson has laid down the shield and taken to the sky once again! Reborn and recommitted, THE FALCON takes flight on a personal mission to reconnect with the American people and train his new partner THE PATRIOT. But when a gang war overtakes the streets of Chicago, Sam finds himself stuck in the middle of a situation far more dangerous than he could've imagined one with its roots in an unexpected corner of the Marvel Universe!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/falcon-2017-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="batman: sins of the father" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>batman: sins of the father</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>batman-sins-of-the-father</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Christos N. Gage, Raffaele Ienco, Guy Major</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/b/batman-sins-of-the-father/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Based on the acclaimed videogame series from Telltale Games, this new digital-first comic tells the story of events between the first and second seasons. Someone is killing people associated with Arkham Asylum during the time Thomas Wayne was forcibly committing people there. Suspicion falls on the families suing Bruce Wayne to pay for the harm caused by his father. Batman has other ideas, but his investigation leads to him becoming the target of a deadly assassin.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/batman-sins-of-the-father-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="x-men: red" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>x-men: red</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>x-men-red</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Tom Taylor, Mahmud Asrar, Travis Charset</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/x/x-men-red-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>THE FIRST SENSATIONAL ARC OF AN ALL-NEW TEAM OF X-MEN STARTS HERE! JEAN GREY is back! Returned to a world she doesn't recognize, the First Lady of the X-MEN gathers an unlikely team - NIGHTCRAWLER, NAMOR and LAURA KINNEY (A.K.A. ALL-NEW WOLVERINE) - to face an evil that threatens to tear down XAVIER's dream by any means necessary!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/x-men-red-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="harley and ivy meet betty and veronica" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Comedy, Crossover, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>harley and ivy meet betty and veronica</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>harley-and-ivy-meet-betty-and-veronica</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Marc Andreyko, Paul Dini, Laura Braga, Amanda Conner, Paul Mounts</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/h/harley--ivy-meet-betty-and-veronica/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Free college tuition for all Riverdale residents?! That's the plan-after the town drains the wetlands that lie between it and Gotham City and then builds a new campus. The only snag? A certain botany-obsessed super-villain. When Poison Ivy enlists her bestie, Harley, to kidnap both Veronica Lodge, daughter of Riverdale's most important citizen, and her friend Betty, she's counting on some assistance-and the mayhem that ensues will probably work as well! DC Comics and Archie are proud to present the adventure of a lifetime for all these best pals. Their hijinks are brought to you by the real-life team-up of Paul Dini (HARLEY QUINN) and Marc Andreyko (WONDER WOMAN '77), with art by Laura Braga (DC BOMBSHELLS)!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Completed/harley-and-ivy-meet-betty-and-veronica-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="grass kings" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Drama, Mystery" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>grass kings</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>grass-kings</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Matt Kindt, Tyler Jenkins</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/g/grass-kings/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Eldest brother Robert leads a grief-stricken life, having lost his daughter to a tragic accident, followed by his wife disappearing one morning never to return. When an enigmatic young woman named Maria flees to their community in search of safe haven, Robert takes her in. Will his decision lead to ruin and retribution dooming the Kingdom? Perfect for fans of Justified or The Fade Out. Oversized first issue featuring 30 pages of story!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/grass-kings-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="invader zim" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Adventure, Fantasy, Horror" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>invader zim</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>invader-zim</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jhonen Vasquez, Aaron Alexovich</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/i/invader-zim/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>ZIM and his filthy evil ways have been gone for what feels like years. But Dib KNOWS the alien menace will rear his head again, and he won`t leave the house, or his 900.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/invader-zim-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="chasing hitler" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Drama, Historical" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic - read from left to right">
		<ten_truyen>chasing hitler</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>chasing-hitler</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Hayley Nitz, Jai Nitz, Jethro Morales, Marie Enger</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/c/chasing-hitler/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>As WWII draws to an end and the Allies surround Berlin, Adolf Hitler realizes that all is lost. Or is it? Two allied service men are tasked with verifying Hitler's death. When they can't the chase begins.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Completed/chasing-hitler-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
</danh_sach_truyen>