<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<danh_sach_truyen>
	<truyen ten="infidel" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Horror, Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>infidel</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>infidel</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Pornsak Pichetshote, Aaron Campbell, Jose Villarrubia</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/i/infidel/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>A haunted house story for the 21st century, INFIDEL follows an American Muslim woman and her multiracial neighbors who move into a building haunted by entities that feed off xenophobia.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/infidel-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="punks not dead" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Life sucks, Sci-fi, Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>punks not dead</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>punks-not-dead</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>David Barnett, Martin Simmonds</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/p/punks-not-dead/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>As if being an awkward, bullied 15-year-old isn't bad enough, 'Fergie' Ferguson suddenly discovers he can see dead people. Well, one dead person specifically-the ghost of a certain punk rocker named Sid. Sid's spirit was trapped in London's Heathrow Airport for 40 years until the day he met Fergie. Sid's ghost is now stuck to Fergie-as if Fergie doesn't have enough on his plate, being raised by a single mum whose idea of parenting is strictly fly-by-the-seat-of-your-pants. Now Fergie has to contend with an unruly ghost sidekick and some weird, uncontrollable new 'abilities'. How does the father Fergie never knew fit into this mayhem? And why is the Department for Extra-Usual Affairs showing an interest? Never Mind the Bollocks-all of this plus fish fingers, chunky chips, and endless pints of anarchy in the new monthly series PUNKS NOT DEAD!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/punks-not-dead-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="deathbed" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy, Horror, Mature, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>deathbed</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>deathbed</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Joshua Williamson, Riley Rossmo, Ivan Plascencia</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/deathbed/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Myth, hack, sex symbol, stark raving lunatic-all of these words have been used to describe Antonio Luna, the world's greatest living adventurer. Or at least he was until 20 years ago, when he mysteriously vanished from the public eye. Now the ninety-year-old has returned and claims to be on his deathbed. Which is where Valentine Richards, a failed novelist turned reporter, comes in. Val is hired to travel to Luna's remote castle home and uncover where the old star has been all these years, and just how much of what he says is actually true. But once Val starts to hear Luna's tale, she finds herself entering into an insane world of psychedelic violence and explosive supernatural adventure.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/deathbed-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="fence" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Drama" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>fence</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>fence</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>C.S. Pacat, Johanna the Mad</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/f/fence/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Sixteen-year-old Nicholas Cox is an outsider to the competitive fencing world. Filled with raw talent but lacking proper training, he signs up for a competition that puts him head-to-head with fencing prodigy Seiji Katayama... and on the road to the elite all-boys school Kings Row. A chance at a real team and a place to belong awaits him if he can make the cut!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/fence-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="exiles (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>exiles (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>exiles-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Saladin Ahmed, Javier Rodriguez, David Marquez</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/e/exiles-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>DON'T BLINK - THE EXILES ARE BACK! Fan-favorite X-Man Blink once joined a team destined to save not just the world, but the entire Multiverse. And now, her teleporting talents are needed once again! When a mysterious threat begins eating away at the fabric of the Multiverse, the Unseen - the man once known as Nick Fury who now can only observe Earth from a lofty post on the moon - must recruit a champion to save it. But she can't do it alone. Who will join Blink's new team - and can they ever go home again?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/exiles-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="green hornet (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Pulp, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>green hornet (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>green-hornet-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Amy Chu, German Erramouspe</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/g/green-hornet-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Britt Reid Jr., the scion of the Daily Sentinel publishing empire, vanishes during a wild party on his friend's yacht. Meanwhile, crime spikes in the streets of Century City with the mysterious criminal/secret vigilante the Green Hornet absent. It's only a matter of time before SOMEONE puts two and two together, and it's up to Kato, former partner of Britt's father, and his daughter Mulan to protect the city AND the Green Hornet legacy, while finding out what happened to Britt. Amy Chu (Red Sonja, Poison Ivy, KISS) picks up where Kevin Smith left off with an action packed mystery.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/green-hornet-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="james bond: the body" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Movies - tv, Spy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>james bond: the body</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>james-bond-the-body</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Ales Kot, Luca Casalanguida</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/j/james-bond-the-body/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>As Bond undergoes a post-mission medical examination, he relays the story of his previous mission to the examiner. Each cut, bruise, and broken bone connected to a specific event of the mission. A connection is made between two people with different purposes: one to save lives, the other to take them.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/james-bond-the-body-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="executive assistant: iris (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy, Leading ladies, Martial arts" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>executive assistant: iris (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>executive-assistant-iris-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Blake Northcott, Donny Tran</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/e/executive-assistant-iris-vol-5/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu> When a routine security job takes a turn for the worse, Executive Assistant Iris realizes she might be at the crossroads of her career! The world's deadliest assassin is faced with a choice: remain a freelance Executive Assistant, or join Magni Global-a mysterious corporation that has acquired nearly every private security firm on the planet. But, what fateful decisions may come from joining a giant conglomerate whose interests may spell doom for her?!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/executive-assistant-iris-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="moonshine" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Crime, Horror, Mystery" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>moonshine</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>moonshine</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Brian Azzarello, Eduardo Risso, Frank Miller</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/m/moonshine/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Set during Prohibition, and deep in the backwoods of Appalachia, MOONSHINE #1 tells the story of Lou Pirlo, a city-slick 'torpedo' sent from New York City to negotiate a deal with the best moonshiner in West Virginia, one Hiram Holt. What Lou doesn't figure on is that Holt is just as cunning and ruthless as any NYC crime boss. Because not only will Holt do anything to protect his illicit booze operation, he'll stop at nothing to protect a much darker family secret...a bloody, supernatural secret that must never see the light of day... or better still, the light of the full moon.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/moonshine-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="shanghai red" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Leading ladies, Western" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>shanghai red</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>shanghai-red</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Christopher Sebela, Hassan Otsmane-Elhaou, Joshua Hixson</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/s/shanghai-red/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Red is one of hundreds shanghaied out of Portland in the late 1800s. Drugged, kidnapped, and sold to a ship's captain, she wakes up on a boat headed out to sea for years, unable to escape or even reveal who she truly is. Now she's coming back in a boat covered in blood to find her family and track down the men responsible for stealing her life out from under her. Eisner-nominated writer CHRISTOPHER SEBELA (High Crimes, Heartthrob, We(l)come Back), JOSHUA HIXSON (The Black Woods) and HASSAN OTSMANE-ELHAOU (Felix and Macabber) bring you a tale of revenge, family, and identity that stretches from the deck of a ship outside Shanghai all the way to the bleak streets and secret tunnels of Portland, Oregon.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/shanghai-red-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="skyward (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Post-apocalyptic" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>skyward (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>skyward-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Joe Henderson, Antonio Fabela, Lee Garbett</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/s/skyward-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>One day, gravity on earth suddenly became a fraction of what it is now. Twenty years later, humanity has adapted to its new low-gravity reality. And to Willa Fowler, a woman born just after G-day, it's... well, it's pretty awesome, actually. You can fly through the air! I mean, sure, you can also die if you jump too high. So you just don't jump too high. And maybe don't stumble into a dangerous plan to bring gravity back that could get you killed.... From writer JOE HENDERSON (showrunner of Fox's Lucifer) and artist LEE GARBETT (Lucifer, Loki: Agent of Asgard), SKYWARD is an adventure-filled exploration of our world turned upside down and a young woman's journey to find her place in it.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/skyward-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="the beef" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>the beef</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>the-beef</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Tyler Shainline, Richard Starkings, Shaky Kane, John Roshel</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/b/beef/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The creator of ELEPHANTMEN and the creator of The A-Men join forces with TYLER SHAINLINE (Liberty Justice) to bring you the story of Meat Men! Chuck is a mild-mannered meat factory worker who is a little in love with a strawberry picker named Mary Lynn. But everything changes when Mary Lynn falls victim to the Vodino Brothers...</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Completed/the-beef-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="barbarella (2017)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>barbarella (2017)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>barbarella-2017</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Mike Carey, Kenan Yarar</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/b/barbarella-(2017)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Earth's star-crossed daughter is back! When Barbarella wanders into a war zone, the theocratic rulers of Parosia arrest and imprison her. A prison break is brewing, but now that she knows what the Parosians do to their own citizens Barbarella decides to make this fight her own...</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/barbarella-2017-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="shadow roads" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy, Western" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>shadow roads</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>shadow-roads</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Cullen Bunn, Brian Hurtt, A.C. Zamudio</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/s/shadow-roads/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The world is thinnest at The Crossroads, a mythical plane that serves as a doorway throughout the universe. It is here that a band of adventurers throughout the Wild West gather, brought together by Gord Cantrell and Abigail Redmayne with a singular purpose: to fight back against the creatures that would endanger the sanctity of all creation.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/shadow-roads-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="gasolina" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Crime, Suspense" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>gasolina</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>gasolina</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Sean Mackiewicz, Mat Lopes, Niko Walter</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/g/gasolina/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Fugitives. Rebels. Newlyweds. In their journey south from El Norte, Amalia and Randy have played many roles in order to survive. Now, they must become unlikely leaders in the fight against a new cartel who uses inhuman tactics to ignite the most monstrous war Mexico and the world has ever seen. Everything burns in this new series from SEAN MACKIEWICZ and NIKO WALTER, where love and devotion can only be measured in fire and blood.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/gasolina-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="her infernal descent" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>her infernal descent</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>her-infernal-descent</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Lonnie Nadler, Zac Thompson, Kyle Charles, Ryan Ferrier</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/h/her-infernal-descent/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>A tale of loss told in five parts. Any good mom would march through the inferno of HELL to get her family back. Unable to cope with the burden of grief, a middle-aged mom descends the nine circles of hell to retrieve her forsaken family. Guided by the ghosts of William Blake and Agatha Christie, this no-nonsense mother journeys deep into a bizarre underworld filled with celebrity sinners, surreal landscapes, and absurd tasks. HER INFERNAL DESCENT is a retelling of Dante's Inferno that updates the themes for a modern audience. From the writers of the break-out hit The Dregs, and the artist of Roche Limit, this is HELL like you've never seen before.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/her-infernal-descent-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="mata hari (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Crime, Fantasy, Leading ladies, Literature, Mature" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>mata hari (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>mata-hari-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Emma Beeby, Ariela Kristantina, Pat Masioni</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/m/mata-hari-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Dancer. Courtesan. Spy. Executed by a French firing squad in 1917. 100 years on from her death, questions are still raised about her conviction. Now, the lesser-known, often tragic story of the woman who claimed she was born a princess, and died a figure of public hatred with no one to claim her body, is told by breakout talent writer Emma Beeby (Judge Dredd), artist Ariela Kristantina (Insexts), and colorist Pat Masioni drawing on biographies and released MI5 files. In this first part of a five-issue miniseries, we meet Mata Hari in prison at the end of her life as she writes her memoir--part romantic tale of a Javanese princess who performed 'sacred' nude dances for Europe's elite, and part real-life saga of a disgraced wife and mother, who had everything she loved taken from her. But, as she sits trial for treason and espionage, we hear another tale: one of a flamboyant Dutch woman who became 'the most dangerous spy France has ever captured' a double agent who whored herself for secrets, lived a life of scandal, and loved only money. Leading us to ask... who was the real Mata Hari?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/mata-hari-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="bedtime games" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Horror, Leading ladies" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>bedtime games</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>bedtime-games</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Tini Howard, Celor, K. Michael Russell, Tim Seeley</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/b/bedtime-games/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>As summer comes to an end, three friends start senior year with a bang by exploring the mysterious past of their school. But before the night is over, their adventure turns into trouble when the kids set loose an evil that seeks to prey on their worst nightmares. </gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/bedtime-games-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="cyber force (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>cyber force (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>cyber-force-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Matt Hawkins, Bryan Edward Hill, Atilio Rojo, Marc Silvestri</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/c/cyber-force-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>TO PROTECT THE FUTURE, WHAT WILL WE BECOME? The classic series returns in a reimagining overseen by creator MARC SILVESTRI. In a modern world where humanity is defined by the technology it creates, a terrorist strikes at the heart of human progress. One of the few survivors of the attack is a man named Morgan Stryker. Mortally wounded, Stryker's life is saved by his employers...but the price could be his humanity itself.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/cyber-force-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="black cloud" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Leading ladies, Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>black cloud</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>black-cloud</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jason Latour, Ivan Brandon, Greg Hinkle, Matt Wilson</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/b/black-cloud/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Zelda was born in a world of dreams, and hers burned bigger than anyone had ever seen. Now she's on the run in our world, the dreams broken in her hands. But the pieces are for sale, the rich and the powerful are buying, and suddenly her world isn't the only place Zelda's running from. From the creators that brought you Spider-Gwen, SOUTHERN BASTARDS, and DRIFTER, and the incredible colorist of THE WICKED + THE DIVINE, comes a place where dreams come true--and today, they go to war.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/black-cloud-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="hack/slash: resurrection" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Horror, Leading ladies" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>hack/slash: resurrection</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>hack-slash-resurrection</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Tini Howard, Celor, K. Michael Russell, Tim Seeley</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/h/hackslash-resurrection/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The fan-favorite title returns with hot new writer, TINI HOWARD! Cassie Hack has been living off the grid, but when a new monstrous threat arises to torment promiscuous teens, it's time for Cassie to pick up the baseball bat once again! Gory, sexy, twisted, and funny... HACK IS BACK!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/hack-slash-resurrection-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="lucy dreaming" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>lucy dreaming</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>lucy-dreaming</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Max Bemis, Michael Dialynas</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/l/lucy-dreaming/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Max Bemis (Moon Knight writer and lead singer of Say Anything) and Michael Dialynas (The Woods) present a sweeping, coming-of-age fantasy about living your dreams-literally. In her dreams, Lucy is the hero of all her favorite stories, living each night as a grand adventure. These journeys will teach her more about herself and the real world around her than she ever expected.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/lucy-dreaming-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="harrow county" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Adventure, Fantasy, Graphic novels, Horror" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>harrow county</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>harrow-county</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Cullen Bunn, Owen Gieni, Tyler Crook</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/h/harrow-county/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>This town will make your skin crawl! Emmy always knew that the deep, dark woods surrounding her home crawled with ghosts, goblins, and zombies. But on the eve of her eighteenth birthday, she learns that she is connected to these creatures-and to the land itself-in a way she never imagined.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/harrow-county-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="descender" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>descender</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>descender</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jeff Lemire, Dustin Nguyen</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/descender/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>One young robot's struggle to stay alive in a universe where all androids have been outlawed and bounty hunters lurk on every planet. A rip-roaring and heart-felt cosmic odyssey that pits humanity against machine, and world against world, to create a sprawling space opera from the creators of Trillium, Sweet Tooth, and Little Gotham.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/descender-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="motherlands" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>motherlands</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>motherlands</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Simon Spurrier, Rachael Stott</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/m/motherlands/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>In a crazed future where unhinged technologies and interconnected parallel Earths have given rise to a spectacular class of super-criminal, the most beloved celebrities aren't actors or rock stars, but the bounty hunters who traverse an exotic multiverse in search of impossible prey! But when the spotlight-shunning, strait-laced tracer known as Tab finds herself in an ultra-violent race for her greatest prize yet, she's forced to work with her greatest enemy, the only person capable of IDing him: her own elderly, overbearing and hypercritical mother, who was once the most fabulous and celebrated bounty hunter of them all.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/motherlands-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="deuce of hearts" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Comedy, Fantasy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>deuce of hearts</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>deuce-of-hearts</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Ricardo Mo, Tony Gregori, Claudia Aguirre</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/deuce-of-hearts/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Sullivan Husk's life changed the day he was introduced to the Heartbreakr app and the notion that love is just another tradeable commodity. What started as a Faustian bargain to restore the good health of a dying man has become a collector's habit. But all the upgrades the app has to offer might not be enough to save Sully from this latest upset spouse.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/deuce-of-hearts-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="blackwood" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Crime, Fantasy, Horror" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>blackwood</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>blackwood</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Evan Dorkin, Veronica Fish</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/b/blackwood/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>When four teenagers with haunted pasts enroll in Blackwood College--a school that trains students in the occult--their desire to enhance their supernatural abilities and bond with others is hampered by an undead dean's curse, ghosts in their dorm, a mischievous two-headed mummy-chimp, a plague of mutant insects, and the discovery of an ancient evil that forces our heroes to undergo a crash course in the occult for the sake of the world.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/blackwood-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="dodge city" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>dodge city</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>dodge-city</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Josh Trujillo, Cara McGee</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/dodge-city/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Josh Trujillo (Adventure Time) and Cara McGee (Over the Garden Wall) team up for a new series about the high-energy chaos of competitive dodgeball! Tomas is the new captain of the Jazz Pandas dodgeball team, and he's got a certain knack for keeping an eye on on the ball (or several!). However, he's untested and still not quite part of the team. If the disorganized Jazz Pandas want to make it to summer regional championships they'll have to pull together under Tomas leadership.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/dodge-city-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="spidey: school's out" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>spidey: school's out</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>spidey-school-s-out</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>John Barber, Todd Nauck, Rachelle Rosenberg</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/s/spidey-schools-out/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Peter Parker just survived his first year as the Amazing Spider-Man AND a year of high school! What is he going to do next? He's going to Stark science camp! A week indoors with the coolest technology in the world is a dream come true for Peter--and a bonanza for one Spider-foe who's seriously upgraded his arsenal. Can Spider-Man keep the camp safe, and keep his identity secret from his first dorm mate, while Peter Parker makes new friends and finishes his project on time?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/spidey-school-s-out-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="the life of captain marvel" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Leading ladies, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>the life of captain marvel</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>the-life-of-captain-marvel</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Margaret Stohl, Carlos Pacheco, Rafael Fonteriz</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/the-life-of-captain-marvel/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>THE DEFINITIVE ORIGIN OF CAPTAIN MARVEL! Carol Danvers was just a girl from the Boston suburbs who loved science and the Red Sox until a chance encounter with a Kree hero gave her incredible super-powers. Now, she's a leader in the Avengers and the commander of Alpha Flight. But what if there were more to the story? When crippling anxiety attacks put her on the sidelines in the middle of a fight, Carol finds herself reliving memories of a life she thought was far behind her. You can't outrun where you're from - and sometimes, you HAVE to go home again. But there are skeletons in Captain Marvel's closet - and what she discovers will change her entire world.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/the-life-of-captain-marvel-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
</danh_sach_truyen>