<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<danh_sach_truyen>
	<truyen ten="star trek: discovery: succession" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Movies - tv, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>star trek: discovery: succession</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>star-trek-discovery-succession</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Kirsten Beyer, Mike Johnston, Angel Hernandez</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/s/star-trek-discovery-succession/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>In this, the second Discovery miniseries from IDW Publishing, your favorite characters from the hit CBS All Access series dive into an adventure tied directly into the second half of the first season!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/star-trek-discovery-succession-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="ghostbusters: crossing over" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Horror, Movies - tv, Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>ghostbusters: crossing over</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>ghostbusters-crossing-over</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Erik Burnham, Dan Schoening</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/g/ghostbusters-crossing-over/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>For a while now, the original Ghostbusters have had access to an interdimensional portal that has given them all-new ways to research the paranormal and consult with Ghostbusters throughout the multiverse... but they haven't shared this tech with any of those other Ghostbusters, and some don't think that's fair. That's why, after a chance meeting, Jillian Holtzmann and Ron Alexander have decided to right this wrong and cobble together their own working portal... which unintentionally unleashes the contents of the Ghostbusters' Containment Unit! That's a lot of ghosts, and it's going to take a lot of Ghostbusters to recapture them. In fact, it's going to take ALL of them. Crossing Over starts here!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/ghostbusters-crossing-over-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="paradiso" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Mystery" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>paradiso</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>paradiso</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Ram V, Dearbhla Kelly, Dev Pramanik, Christian Ward</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/p/paradiso/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The Midnight Event forever changed the world. Now, centuries later, Jack Kryznan arrives on the outskirts of Paradiso City, haunted by fragments of childhood memories and in possession of a mysterious device one with the power to change the destiny of this living breathing metropolis, the people who dwell within, and the guardians who strive for and against it.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/paradiso-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="prism stalker" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>prism stalker</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>prism-stalker</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Sloane Long, Darius Ou</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/p/prism-stalker/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>For fans of Octavia Butler, Sailor Moon, and the biopunk horror of David Cronenberg comes PRISM STALKER, an ongoing sci-fi adventure series by SLOANE LEONG. Vep is a young refugee raised away from her devastated home planet as an indentured citizen in a foreign colony. She works tirelessly for her insectoid hosts, but there is no exit in sight in this viscous, dripping citynest. The eye of opportunity is closing. Her duty is to her family and her siblings, but what more can she do for them here? The answer appears faster than she is ready for.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/prism-stalker-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="the last siege" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Crime, Fantasy, Martial arts" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>the last siege</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>the-last-siege</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Landry Q. Walker, Justin Greenwood, Nick Dragotta</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/the-last-siege/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>A tale of blood, desperation, and loss. New York Times bestselling author LANDRY Q. WALKER joins artist JUSTIN GREENWOOD for an all-new ONGOING SERIES-THE LAST SIEGE! Spaghetti Western storytelling meets Game of Thrones atmosphere in this gritty medieval war story, as a mysterious stranger arrives at a castle overrun with brutal soldiers bent on usurping the throne of the rightful heir-an 11-year-old girl. An action-packed, genre-twisting epic, THE LAST SIEGE begins!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/the-last-siege-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="hillbilly" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy, Mythology, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>hillbilly</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>hillbilly</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Eric Powell</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/h/hillbilly/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>An Appalachian Mountain fantasy epic that tells the story of Rondel. A lonely figure who wanders the wooded hills among witches and magical creatures as a folktale hero to those who dwell in this gritty dream world.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/hillbilly-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="jirni (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>jirni (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>jirni-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>J.T. Krul, Michael Santamaria, John Starr</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/j/jirni-vol-3/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Aspen's popular fantasy adventure series, JIRNI, returns for an epic third volume! As Ara's quest to find her kidnapped mother continues, she finds solace in a remote village, but do they have their own demons to worry about? Meanwhile, Torinthal continues on his own search to unlock the mysteries of the D'jinn and their celestial origin. Don't miss out on the biggest quest for Ara yet! Created by New York Times Best-Selling author J.T. Krul (Michael Turner's Soulfire, Green Arrow) with art by newcomer Michael Santamaria, this next exciting chapter of Jirni will once again return readers to a land of untapped wonder!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/jirni-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="isola" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>isola</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>isola</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Brenden Fletcher, Karl Kerschl, MSASSYK</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/i/isola/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Childhood friends BRENDEN FLETCHER (MOTOR CRUSH) and Eisner Award-winning storyteller KARL KERSCHL (Gotham Academy) reunite on the comics page with a breathtaking fantasy adventure two decades in the making! The captain of the Royal Guard has fled the capital city with the Queen of Maar, suffering under the effects of an evil spell. Captain Rook's only hope of returning Queen Olwyn to her throne and saving the kingdom from impending war lies on an island half a world away-a place known in myth as Isola, land of the dead. Featuring lush color work by MSASSYK (Gotham Academy) and letters by ADITYA BIDIKAR (MOTOR CRUSH). Recommended for fans of Studio Ghibli and the work of Hayao Miyazaki.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/isola-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="die!die!die!" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Horror, Suspense" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>die!die!die!</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>die-die-die</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Chris Burnham, Robert Kirkman, Scott Gimple</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/diediedie/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Blood will flow, Bullets will fly and the mayhem will never end, Die!Die!Die! brings all the action you could ever want.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/die-die-die-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="the curse of brimstone" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>the curse of brimstone</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>the-curse-of-brimstone</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Justin Jordan, Philip Tan</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/the-curse-of-brimstone/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Joe Chamberlain would do anything to save his small, forgotten town-even make a deal with the devil. But things get worse, and Joe finds himself cursed with the power of BRIMSTONE. With the power of fire and destruction coursing through his hands, Joe must now track down and destroy the demon he made his deal with before the power he now wields destroys the town he was trying to save.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/the-curse-of-brimstone-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="cloak and dagger (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>cloak and dagger (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>cloak-and-dagger-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Dennis Hopeless, David Messina</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/c/cloak-and-dagger-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>For years, Tyrone Johnson and Tandy Bowen were the super hero duo called CLOAK AND DAGGER - waging a citywide war on drugs, organized crime and corporate greed. In recent years, their crusade has taken them across the globe, fighting alongside Spider-Man, The X-Men and even The Avengers, and though they've drifted apart, a dangerous threat from their past has resurfaced - one that will force Cloak and Dagger to reunite and come to terms with their truest feelings for one another and the past they share!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/cloak-and-dagger-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="halo: collateral damage" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Sci-fi, Video games" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>halo: collateral damage</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>halo-collateral-damage</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Alex Irvine, Dave Crosland, Leionard O'Grady</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/h/halo-collateral-damage/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The Master Chief and Blue Team are deployed by the UNSC to Alpha Corvi II, a precarious human colony world, seeking to halt the Covenant's efforts to uncover something hidden below the planet's surface. The Spartan strike team quickly finds out that they will have to rely on each other and a small cadre of human rebels in order to survive and complete their mission.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/halo-collateral-damage-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="kiss/army of darkness" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Fantasy, Movies - tv, Music" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>kiss/army of darkness</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>kiss-army-of-darkness</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Chad Bowers, Chris Sims, Ruairi Coleman</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/k/kissarmy-of-darkness/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>KISS is on top of the world and rocking faces until the night disciples of The Destroyer show up and the band disappears. With the tour canceled, a young Ash misses one of the most important events of his life that will change his destiny. Now the Chosen One has to get back on the right path and join the KISS ARMY OF DARKNESS!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/kiss-army-of-darkness-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="world of tanks: citadel" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Video games" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>world of tanks: citadel</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>world-of-tanks-citadel</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Garth Ennis, PJ Holden</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/w/world-of-tanks-citadel/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The Eastern Front, 1943: as the cataclysmic Battle of Kursk looms large, Captain Piotr Piotrowicz and his driver, Natalya 'Ginger' Pulkhova, prepare their unit for action- equipped with the worst tanks in the Russian inventory. On the opposite side, German tankers Karl Kraft and Freddie Stadler brace for the onslaught-well aware that failure here will put their Soviet enemy on the road to Berlin. Garth Ennis and PJ Holden present a second action-packed story of armored warfare, inspired by the phenomenally popular game World of Tanks.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/world-of-tanks-citadel-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="astonisher" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>astonisher</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>astonisher</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Alex de Campi, Jessica Kholinne, Pop Mhan</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/c/catalyst-prime-astonisher/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Magnus Atitarn, heir to the Atitarn Satellite Corp., tried to save the world with his experimental one-man spaceship and ended up a broken man. Now a celebrity joke suffering from post-traumatic stress disorder, Magnus has the power to travel inside the minds of superpowered people, where he discovers nightmares which threaten the entire human race. The strangest corners of the Catalyst Prime Universe are explored in this new series!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/astonisher-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="charismagic (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>charismagic (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>charismagic-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Vince Hernandez, Federico Blee, Mark Roslan, Joey Vazquez</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/c/charismagic-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The forces of magic have returned-and this time no magical being is safe! Aspen's magical action-adventure series returns for its epic third volume! Las Vegas magician Hank Medley and his talking cat Sparkles attempt to put the pieces of their life back together, as society has taken a hardline approach to magic and its destructive results. Meanwhile, Sudana uncovers a more sinister plot brewing in the confines of a secret Government's facility in the Nevada desert, as a new form of magic is taking shape that will not only spell the end for mankind-but also magical beings everywhere! The age of the Magic Harvester has arrived!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Completed/charismagic-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="bloodshot salvation" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>bloodshot salvation</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>bloodshot-salvation</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jeff Lemire, Lewis Larosa</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/b/bloodshot-salvation/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Now: In the arms of his beloved girlfriend Magic, Bloodshot has finally found hope for the future... in the form the couple's unborn child. But when Magic's estranged family - a cruel and sadistic clan of white supremacist criminals re-emerge to lay claim to their lost daughter, Bloodshot will be pushed back to the brink of madness, mayhem, and warfare... Soon: Eight years from today, Bloodshot's daughter has inherited her father's incredible abilities. Hunted by a high-tech kill squad called Omen, Jessie must hone her powers... and learn how to survive before the world is swallowed whole by the darkness that now pervades America...</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/bloodshot-salvation-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="nancy drew (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Drama, Mystery" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>nancy drew (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>nancy-drew-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Kelly Thompson, Jenn St-Onge</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/n/nancy-drew-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Nancy Drew is seventeen and good at everything... ESPECIALLY solving crimes. But her totally-in-control-and-obviously-running-perfectly-smooth-(but-not-really) life hits a snag when a mysterious message drags her back to the hometown she left behind. There she'll have to find out which of her friends are still her friends, which are enemies, and who exactly is trying to kill her... and (hopefully) stop them before they succeed. KELLY THOMPSON (Hawkeye, Star Wars, Rogue and Gambit) and JENN ST-ONGE (Giant Days, The Misfits) team up to present an all-new modern spin on a classic mystery icon!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/nancy-drew-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="wasted space" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>wasted space</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>wasted-space</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Michael Moreci, Hayden Sherman</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/w/wasted-space/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Billy Bane is a prophet who got it all wrong, and the galaxy has been burning ever since. All he wants is to waste away in the darkest corner of space with his best pal Dust, a supercharged Fuq bot. But when a new prophet comes calling, Billy is summoned to save the galaxy he's at least partially responsible for destroying. Too bad he couldn't care less.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/wasted-space-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="teenage mutant ninja turtles: urban legends" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Anthropomorphic, Martial arts, Movies - tv, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>teenage mutant ninja turtles: urban legends</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-urban-legends</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Gary Carlson, Frank Fosco</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-urban-legends/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>This is it, fans! You demanded it, and IDW Publishing listened! The entire Image Comics TMNT run (a.k.a TMNT Volume 3) reproduced for the first time ever in full, four-color glory! Join creators Gary Carlson and Frank Fosco as they take the Heroes in a Half-Shell on some of their most amazing and dangerous and bizarre adventures ever... culminating in three brand-new issues by Carlson and Fosco to properly close out this long-beloved storyline at last! In this premiere issue, the TMNT and Master Splinter are attacked in their lair by a group of cyborgs led by the female ninja called Pimiko. Before the attack is over, one family member will fall... and one will be lost! Don't miss your chance to get in on the ground floor of the entire TMNT Image experience!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-urban-legends-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="jasmine: crown of kings" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy, Suspense" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>jasmine: crown of kings</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>jasmine-crown-of-kings</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Howard Mackie, Deivis Goetten</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/j/jasmine-crown-of-kings/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>New Series Starts Here! When a fiery explosion erupts in the ancient city of Petra, Jasmine races against the terrorist group THE FORTY THIEVES to prevent the shattered pieces of the Crown of Kings, an object that haunts her past from being reunited and unleashing an unearthly power on the world and all that she holds dear.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/jasmine-crown-of-kings-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="aliens: dust to dust" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>aliens: dust to dust</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>aliens-dust-to-dust</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Gabriel Hardman</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/a/aliens-dust-to-dust/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The Trono colony on LV-871 is under attack. Emergency evacuations are ordered. Evac shuttles are taking off. All twelve-year-old Maxon and his mom have to do is make it to the spaceport. Except between them and it are... Aliens! A terrifying coming-of-age story by master storyteller Gabriel Hardman.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/aliens-dust-to-dust-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="robocop: citizens arrest" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Movies - tv, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>robocop: citizens arrest</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>robocop-citizens-arrest</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Brian Wood, Jorge Coelho</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/r/robocop-citizens-arrest/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Brian Wood, the visionary writer behind DMZ and Briggs Land, and Jorge Coelho (Venom, Rocket Raccoon) present a provocative vision of a future where justice is crowdsourced... and lethal. It's been decades since the RoboCop program first began. Corporations have taken over the schools and the government and law enforcement is the biggest private contract of all. Traditional police forces no longer exist as all citizens are encouraged-and rewarded-to spy on their neighbors. There is only one authority on the streets: ROBOCOP.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/robocop-citizens-arrest-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="xena: warrior princess (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy, Movies - tv" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>xena: warrior princess (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>xena-warrior-princess-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Meredith Finch, Vicente Cifuentes</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/x/xena-warrior-princess(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The path to redemption is never easy, and the journey of a warrior princess seeking to wash the blood of innocents from her hands is no exception. Xena travels to Athens, to plead for redemption in the temple of Eleos. But some things can never be forgiven and the shadows of past sins are long. Will Xena find redemption or betrayal waiting for her in the temple of the gods? The power, the passion, the danger... her courage would change the world. Xena: Warrior Princess.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/xena-warrior-princess-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="monstress" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Drama, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>monstress</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>monstress</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Marjorie Liu, Sana Takeda</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/m/monstress/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Steampunk meets Kaiju in this original fantasy epic for mature readers, as young Maika risks everything to control her psychic link with a monster of tremendous power, placing her in the center of a devastating war between human and otherworldly forces.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/monstress-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="plastic man (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>plastic man (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>plastic-man-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Gail Simone, Adriana Melo</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/p/plastic-man-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Meet Eel O'Brian: a petty thug, thief and con artist who runs a strip club. Hey, he's also dead, at least according to the gang that tossed him out like last week's garbage. Literally. Don't worry, though he bounced back from all that, and now he's trying to make a new life for himself, but the effort is stretching him pretty thin.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/plastic-man-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="domino (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Leading ladies, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>domino (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>domino-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Gail Simone, David Baldeon, Greg Land</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/domino-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Impossible curves. Impossible shots. Impossible targets. Marvel's #1 soldier of fortune is back in an explosive new ongoing series! The product of a failed super-soldier program, Neena Thurman always made her own luck as the sharpshooting mercenary known as Domino... but what happens when her own powers betray her? The hunter becomes the hunted as every mercenary in the game smells blood in the water! Plus: A pair of beloved Marvel characters return!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/domino-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="dejah thoris (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Leading ladies, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>dejah thoris (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>dejah-thoris-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Amy Chu, Pasquale Qualano</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/dejah-thoris-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The untold story of the Red Martian princess! After learning of the legendary Gardens of Mars from her grandfather, Dejah Thoris, Princess of Helium, sets off on a dangerous scientific expedition to save her dying planet. But things don't go the way she planned when she encounters a mysterious Green Martian prisoner... A prequel to Edgar Rice Burroughs' beloved book A Princess of Mars.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/dejah-thoris-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="dejah thoris (2016)" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy, Graphic novels, Mythology, Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>dejah thoris (2016)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>dejah-thoris-2016</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Frank J. Barbiere, Francesco Manna, Morgan Hickman, Erica Schultz, Nen</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/dejah-thoris/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Prepare yourself for Dejah Thoris as you've never seen her before! A shocking conspiracy unravels in Helium as Dejah's father has gone missing. In the wake of assuming the throne, Dejah learns secret information from her past that will have resounding effects on the kingdom - and her life! Join Frank J. Barbiere (The Howling Commandos of SHIELD, The Precinct) and Francesco Manna (Vampirella #100) as Dejah discovers a secret past that will have her leaving Helium for an all-new adventure on her own!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Completed/dejah-thoris-2016-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="dc nation" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>dc nation</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>dc-nation</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Brian Michael Bendis, Tom King, Scott Snyder, James Tynion IV, Joshua Williamson, Jose Luis Garcia-Lopez, Jorge Jimenez, Clay Mann</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/dc-nation-(2018)/0_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>DC Nation features three brand-new stories from a lineup of superstar talent that will appear only in this comic book and will not be reprinted in another comic book before each series' collected editions.-and each tale serves as a prelude to some of the biggest DC events of 2018!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/dc-nation-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
</danh_sach_truyen>