<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<danh_sach_truyen>
	<truyen ten="hawkman (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>hawkman (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>hawkman-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jeff Lemire, Robert Venditti, Bryan Hitch, Andrew currie, Alex Sinclair</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/h/hawkman-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Spinning out of the events of DARK NIGHTS: METAL, Carter Hall returns to the DC Universe! An explorer of the ancient and unknown, Hawkman finds himself embroiled in a long-standing mission to discover the true purpose of his many reincarnations. Carter races around the globe trying to piece together an ancient prophecy, but will he be able to face down his past lives lurking around every corner?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/hawkman-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="fathom (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>fathom (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>fathom-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Ron Marz, Siya Oum, Peter Steigerwald</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/f/fathom-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>This all-new adventure for Aspen's preeminent hero sees her attempt to navigate an ever-changing world where The Blue are not only present above the surface-but exploited in new and dangerous ways. When a rival nation to The States decides to take control of the global landscape by tapping into the power of The Blue, Aspen Matthews discovers that a new adversary has risen to challenge the notion that she is the most powerful person on the planet-and humanity may suffer the consequences!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/fathom-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="crossed plus one hundred: mimic" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Horror, Post-apocalyptic" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>crossed plus one hundred: mimic</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>crossed-plus-one-hundred-mimic</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Christos N. Gage, Patrick Shand, Emiliano Urdinola, Raulo Caceres</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/c/crossed-plus-100-mimic/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Crossed + One Hundred: Mimic continues to story of the disciples of Beau Salt, the serial killer who despite being infected fully retained his sanity, invading military bases to take their best and turn them to the Crossed side.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/crossed-plus-one-hundred-mimic-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="thanos legacy" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>thanos legacy</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>thanos-legacy</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Donny Cates, Gerry Duggan, Brian Level, Cory Smith</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/thanos-legacy/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>THANOS WINS... AGAIN! Rising star Donny Cates returns to the Mad Titan to bring the story bridging the gap between his best-selling 'Thanos Wins' and the worldshattering INFINITY WARS! How did Thanos' journey back from the future lead to the events of INFINITY WARS PRIME? Now it can be told!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Completed/thanos-legacy-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="asgardians of the galaxy" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>asgardians of the galaxy</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>asgardians-of-the-galaxy</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Cullen Bunn, Matteo Lolli</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/a/asgardians-of-the-galaxy/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Spinning out of the events of INFINITY WARS comes an epic space opera from DEADPOOL veterans Cullen Bunn and Matteo Lolli! Angela, the not-so-beloved half-sister of Thor. The hotheaded Valkyrie - and the human who shares her form, Annabelle Riggs. Skurge the Executioner, freshly returned from Hel. Throg, the mightiest frog of thunder. Kevin Masterson, the boy who took his father's mace to become the hero Thunderstrike. And the Destroyer, the Asgardian armor built to take down Celestials - its wielder unknown. The events of INFINITY WARS set NEBULA off on a quest to rule the galaxy - wielding an Asgardian weapon even Thor would fear - and it's up to this team of gods, assassins, frogs and heroes to stop her.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/asgardians-of-the-galaxy-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="starcraft: scavengers" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Sci-fi, Video games" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>starcraft: scavengers</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>starcraft-scavengers</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jody Houser, Gabriel Guzman</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/s/starcraft-scavengers/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>A group of terran space scavengers hope to pull off the job of their lifetimes, ignoring a recent United Earth Directorate treaty to pillage a derelict protoss ship.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/starcraft-scavengers-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="batman: kings of fear" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>batman: kings of fear</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>batman-kings-of-fear</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Scott Peterson, Kelley Jones</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/b/batman-kings-of-fear/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Batman's been overseeing Gotham City for years now and isn't sure how much of a difference he's making. Doubt, fear and insecurity are starting to take over. And as all of those negative feelings set in the Scarecrow orchestrates a riot at Arkham Asylum to give the Dark Knight one of his greatest challenges yet! This six-issue miniseries will see the Scarecrow in a horrifying new way that you'll have to read to believe.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/batman-kings-of-fear-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="edge of spider-geddon" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>edge of spider-geddon</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>edge-of-spider-geddon</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jed McKay, Gerardo Sandoval</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/e/edge-of-spider-geddon/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Spider-Punk is back and better than ever. After SPIDER-VERSE, Hobie Brown was a Web Warrior, but that didn't mean things back in his universe were solved. The writer of the SPIDER-PUNK story in SPIDER-VERSE is back and joined by VENOM'S Gerardo Sandoval! Spider-Punk's Earth is under attack both on the ground and from space, meaning his responsibility seems to outweigh his power.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/edge-of-spider-geddon-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="extermination (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>extermination (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>extermination-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Ed Brisson, Pepe Larraz</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/e/extermination-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>EXTERMINATE THE PAST. ELIMINATE THE FUTURE. Cyclops. Iceman. Angel. Beast. Marvel Girl. The original team of teen mutants brought together by Professor Charles Xavier many years ago have been shunted through time to find a world they barely recognize but were determined to help. Now, finding themselves targeted for death, the future of mutantkind lies squarely in the hands of its past.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/extermination-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="mr. and mrs. x" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>mr. and mrs. x</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>mr-and-mrs-x</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Kelly Thompson, Oscar Bazaldua</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/m/mr-and-mrs-x/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Straight from the pages of X-MEN GOLD... to the surprise of everyone, the Marvel Universe's hottest couple has finally tied the knot! In their extraordinary lives, they've faced nearly every challenge imaginable, but how will they fare against former flames making trouble? An entire galaxy in jeopardy? You want it? We got it, as Kelly Thompson (HAWKEYE, ROGUE and GAMBIT) and Oscar Bazaldua (SPIDER-MAN, STAR WARS: ROGUE ONE) bring you the tantalizing tale of a modern marriage... X-MEN STYLE!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/mr-and-mrs-x-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="the silencer" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>the silencer</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>the-silencer</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Dan Abnett, John Romita Jr., Sandra Hope</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/the-silencer/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>She's one of the DC Universe's deadliest assassins... and you've never heard of her. Super-strong, highly trained, armed with devastating and stealthy meta-human abilities, the Silencer is virtually invincible. Or at least she was. After decades as Leviathan's chief assassin, Honor Guest put in her time and managed to get out with her skin intact. Now she lives a normal life with a normal family in a normal house on a normal street. But the past has come back to haunt her in the form of her old employer and a deadly new mission... and Talia Al Ghul won't take no for an answer.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/the-silencer-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="the punisher (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>the punisher (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>the-punisher-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Matt Rosenberg, Szymon Kudranski</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/p/punisher-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>YOU CAN TAKE THE PUNISHER OUT OF THE WAR MACHINE... Punisher no longer has the War Machine armor, but he retained his newly acquired taste for big game, and he's hungry for more. However, the paths to such perilous pursuits are fraught with dangers bigger than any Frank has faced before, and this lone wolf could use otherworldly help on his way up to the world stage.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/the-punisher-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="injustice vs. masters of the universe" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>injustice vs. masters of the universe</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>injustice-vs-masters-of-the-universe</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Tim Seeley, Freddie E. Williams II, Jeremy Colwell</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/i/injustice-vs-masters-of-the-universe/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Believing He-man and the Masters of the Universe defeated, a robotic impostor has seized control of Eternia-but not for long! After freeing his kingdom from this strongman's rule, Prince Adam learns not everyone is pleased to see the pretender deposed-but Adam knows the value of freedom. So when heroes from another dimension ask his aid in deposing a super-hero turned dictator, he agrees. Teaming up with Batman against the Superman of the Injustice Universe, He-man and his new allies face dangerous and familiar enemies in a battle where no world is safe!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/injustice-vs-masters-of-the-universe-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="multiple man" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>multiple man</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>multiple-man</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Matthew Rosenburg, Andy MacDonald</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/m/multiple-man-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>MATTHEW ROSENBERG and ANDY MACDONALD BRING MULTIPLE MAN BACK FROM THE DEAD...SORT OF...MAYBE? A handful of people's favorite X-Man - Jamie Madrox - was alive for a while. Then he was dead. Now he's not. But he will be again if he doesn't kill himself trying to make sure he doesn't die. It makes sense when you read it. Trust us. In his fight to not die, Jamie has stumbled across a threat even greater than his own death, but fixing it might make it worse. Can he save the world from himself? On top of all that, the X-Men are mad at him now, and a mysterious new group of foes is after him, too. We can't tell you who they are, but they're pretty great.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/multiple-man-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="revenge of wonderland" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy, Leading ladies" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>revenge of wonderland</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>revenge-of-wonderland</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Joe Brusha, Ralph Tedesco, Dave Franchini, Raven Gregory, Allan Otero, Grostieta</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/r/revenge-of-wonderland/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The realm of madness is back with a brand new twisted tale of love, loss and vengeance! It's been a long time since Alice Liddle's daughter, Calie, finally escaped the twisted world that her mother was pulled into many years before her. But the insanity of Wonderland has returned and this time around things are much more dangerous and horrifying than ever before. Originally the realm of dreams, but now a realm made up of nightmares, Wonderland has been purged of its original denizens and a new ruler has emerged. The Duchess has been kidnapping people from this world and re-shaping them in her image to use as her personal playthings. Can Calie and her daughter team up to stop a new madness from emerging from Wonderland and invading our world or is it too late to stop the inevitable? Find out here is this insane first issue of a whole new Wonderland!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/revenge-of-wonderland-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="fantastic four (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>fantastic four (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>fantastic-four-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Dan Slott, Simone Bianchi, Sara Pichelli, Elisabetta D'Amico, Skottie Young</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/f/fantastic-four-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Since the end of SECRET WARS, there's been a gap in the Marvel Universe. A void no other team can fill. And it's time for the world to move on. But can it? A life-changing decision by the Thing! A momentous declaration by the Human Torch! A clarion call-to-arms that summons Doctor Doom! And a signal in the sky that heralds the return of hope to the Marvel Universe! All this, and Alicia Masters adopts kittens! So cute! Plus, the Impossible Man!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/fantastic-four-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="catwoman (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>catwoman (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>catwoman-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Joelle Jones</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/c/catwoman-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The wedding night's barely over, but Catwoman's back on the streets, this time to expose a copycat who's pulling heists around Gotham City. As Selina cracks the whip on her former criminal cohorts, she's attracting unwanted attention from one of Gotham's most dangerous groups. The mob? Nope. Try the GCPD. And as if the Bat-Bride didn't have enough problems, don't miss the debut of an all-new villain determined to make trouble for all nine of Selina's lives.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/catwoman-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="predator: hunters ii" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>predator: hunters ii</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>predator-hunters-ii</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Chris Warner, Neeraj Menon, Agustin Padilla</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/p/predator-hunters-ii/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>From the islands of the South Pacific to the mountains of Afghanistan, the Hunters go wherever the Predators appear--even if it's in a war zone and into conflict with a mysterious government group hunting the same prey! Despite the casualties suffered during their first mission, the Predator Hunters are on the prowl again!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/predator-hunters-ii-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="captain america (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>captain america (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>captain-america-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Ta-Nehisi Coates, Leinil Francis Yu, Gerry Alanguilan, Sunny Gho</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/c/captain-america-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>IT IS WINTER IN AMERICA.For over 70 years, he has stood in stalwart defense of our country and its people. But in the aftermath of Hydra's takeover of the nation, Captain America is a figure of controversy, carrying a tarnished shield...and a new enemy is rising! Who are the Power Elite? And how do they intend to co-opt and corrupt the symbol that is Captain America?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/captain-america-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="portal bound" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>portal bound</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>portal-bound</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Gabe Carrasco, Mark Roslan, Alex Arizmendi, Wes Hartman, Adam Archer</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/p/portal-bound/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Their Future Depends on Each Other. A parallel otherworld exists as a mirror to our own, where science is melded with nature and a warrior spirit defines their true value. A teenage soldier princess, Sybil, is sent off with her Uncle Horuk in an effort to stop her megalomaniac father, Emperor Atilus from destroying two Earths. With a deadly array of monstrous creatures in hot pursuit, Sybil and her uncle race to activate a portal to Earth to find a savior who is also figuring out how to survive... being a teenager!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/portal-bound-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="fissure" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Drama, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>fissure</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>fissure</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Tim Daniel, Patricio Delpeche</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/f/fissure/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>El Sueno, Texas was a single street town withering under the shadow of the Mexico-U.S. Barrier. Then the pavement split, and a massive crack spread from one end to the other, rapidly swallowing El Sueno whole. Young couple Avery Lee Olmos and Hark Wright fight to escape the mysterious sinkhole and the malevolent force that beckons from its depths.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/fissure-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="infinity wars  " tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>infinity wars  </ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>infinity-wars</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Gerry Duggan, Mike Deodato Jr.</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/i/infinity-wars-prime/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>As the Infinity Stones come to Earth, so too comes the war for control over them. But none who wield the stones know the truth about the power they contain...or what it would take to bring them to their END. The nature of the universe itself hangs in the balance as we learn the answer to the question on everyone's lips since 'Infinity Wars Prime': WHO IS REQUIEM?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/infinity-wars-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="adventures of the super sons" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>adventures of the super sons</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>adventures-of-the-super-sons</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Peter J. Tomasi, Carlo Barberi</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/a/adventures-of-the-super-sons/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The Super Sons are back in an all-new 12-issue miniseries written by Peter J. Tomasi! Check out the lost and secret adventures of Damian Wayne (Robin) and Jon Kent (Superboy) in this flashback miniseries that takes a deep dive into the bombastic bromance between the sons of the DC Universe's greatest heroes. It's an epic dual storyline that transcends current events, as Superboy and Robin find themselves targets of an interstellar team of young badasses called the Gang.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/adventures-of-the-super-sons-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="death of the inhumans" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>death of the inhumans</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>death-of-the-inhumans</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Donny Cates, Ariel Olivetti, Jordie Bellaire</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/death-of-the-inhumans/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>THE TITLE SAYS IT ALL - HERE LIE THE INHUMANS. The Kree have gone murdering, leaving behind a message: Join or die. Thousands of Inhumans have already made their choice - the evidence floats bleeding in space. Black Bolt and his family are next. Rising star Donny Cates and PUNISHER: WAR JOURNAL artist Ariel Olivetti bring their brutal talents to the Inhumans!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/death-of-the-inhumans-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="ant-man and the wasp (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>ant-man and the wasp (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>ant-man-and-the-wasp-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Mark Waid, Javier Garron, David Nakayama</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/a/ant-man--the-wasp-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Wasp was just trying to help Ant-Man get home to Earth to see his daughter...but a little problem got in the way. Very little. Subatomic, in fact, as Scott Lang was lost in the vast spaces between atoms! Now, Nadia is his only hope of rescue...if only he would listen long enough for her to save them!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/ant-man-and-the-wasp-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="teenage mutant ninja turtles universe" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Anthropomorphic, Fantasy, Movies-tv, Sci-fi, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>teenage mutant ninja turtles universe</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-universe</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Kevin Eastman, Paul Allor, Tom Waltz, Damian Couceiro, Bill Sienkiewicz, Freddie E. Williams</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-universe/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Introducing a new era in TMNT! This series will explore characters and story-lines that are pivotal to the IDW TMNT universe! When a mysterious new mutant targets Baxter Stockman, it will be up to the TMNT to reluctantly save him. Little does everyone know that a larger trap is being laid by a new arch-foe! Plus a back-up story from TMNT co-creator Kevin Eastman and comics legend Bill Sienkiewicz!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-universe-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="deep roots" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>deep roots</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>deep-roots</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Dan Watters, Val Rodrigues, Triona Farrell</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/deep-roots/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Roots, once suffocating under cement, tear through the streets of London to throttle buildings. Vegetable homunculi hold up banks with automatic weapons. There is a green and blooming world beyond our own, fighting back against the human pollutant. We will launch a rescue mission to this Otherworld. But it is cruel and unknowable, and should we become tangled in its vines, more than cities will fall. From Dan Watters (Limbo, The Shadow, Assassin's Creed) and Val Rodrigues comes a story of two worlds, of myth and man, of science and fiction, and the roots they share.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/deep-roots-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="kick-ass (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>kick-ass (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>kick-ass-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Mark Millar, John Romita Jr.</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/k/kick-ass-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>KICK-ASS IS BACK-ready to wipe out the city's criminal lowlives, destroy its gangs, and save its communities from decay. But there's a new face beneath the old mask, a new figure wearing that famous green and yellow spandex. Who is this new vigilante superhero? Who can fill Dave Lizewski's shoes? WHO IS THE NEW KICK-ASS? Find out in the first issue of this new, ongoing monthly series. Comic book legends MARK MILLAR and JOHN ROMITA, JR. reunite for the next chapter of the greatest superhero comic of all time.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/kick-ass-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="death of love" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>death of love</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>death-of-love</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Justin Jordan, Donal Delay, Omar Trucu Estevez</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/death-of-love/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Love sucks. Philo Harris is going to do something about it. After gaining the ability to see the Cupidae that make love work-after a particularly bad drunken decision-Philo ends up going to war with love itself. With a chainsaw.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/death-of-love-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="copperhead" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Crime, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>copperhead</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>copperhead</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jay Faerber, Scott Godlewski</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/c/copperhead/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Welcome to Copperhead, a grimy mining town on the edge of a backwater planet. Single mom Clara Bronson is the new sheriff, and on her first day she'll have to contend with a resentful deputy, a shady mining tycoon, and a family of alien hillbillies. And did we mention the massacre?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/copperhead-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="dry county" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Crime" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>dry county</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>dry-county</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Rich Tommaso</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/dry-county/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>RICH TOMMASO is taking a short hiatus on SPY SEAL and releasing a new crime series in the meantime, one set in the late 1980s of Miami that follows a young Generation Xer who plays amateur detective in order to find a missing lady he's recently fallen hard for.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/dry-county-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="infinity countdown: black widow" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>infinity countdown: black widow</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>infinity-countdown-black-widow</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Gerry Duggan, Nik Virella, Yasmine Putri</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/i/infinity-countdown-black-widow/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Given the incredibly powerful Space Stone to look after by an old friend, Black Widow has no intention of letting it fall into the wrong hands... but is even the top espionage agent in the world ready to handle cosmic responsibility?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/infinity-countdown-black-widow-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="quicksilver: no surrender" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>quicksilver: no surrender</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>quicksilver-no-surrender</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Saladin Ahmed, Eric Nguyen</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/q/quicksilver-no-surrender/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Quicksilver's super-speed and abrasive personality have always isolated him, but he's never been truly alone... until now. Trapped beyond the perception of friends, family and allies, Quicksilver wages a one-man guerilla war against a monster that he's not even sure is real, to save a world that he may never be a part of again. Saladin Ahmed (BLACK BOLT) and Eric Nguyen (OLD MAN LOGAN) team up to bring you a psychedelic survival thriller unlike anything you've seen before!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/quicksilver-no-surrender-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="b.p.r.d. the devil you know" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>b.p.r.d. the devil you know</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>b-p-r-d-the-devil-you-know</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jeff Lemire, Lewis Larosa, Mico Suayan</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/b/bprd-the-devil-you-know/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Before they were vanquished by the BPRD, Lovecraftian monsters created a Hell on Earth. Now Liz Sherman leads a crew through monster-infested ruins on the most important rescue mission of her life. As society tries to rebuild, strange cults vie for influence, and a demon emerges to lead the way...</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/b-p-r-d-the-devil-you-know-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="betrothed" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>betrothed</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>betrothed</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Sean Lewis, Steve Uy, Simon Bowland</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/b/betrothed/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Welcome to the World of Betrothed! Kieron and Tamara are both seniors at the same high school. They've never paid much attention to each other, even though they are the only kids at school who are orphans. On the eve of their eighteenth birthdays, they discover a lifelong secret: in a dimension far away, they are each the leader of an army that is at war with one another... and what's more, when they turn eighteen, they're to be Betrothed or Fight to the Death!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/betrothed-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="evolution  " tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>evolution  </ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>evolution</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>James Asmus, Joesph Keatinge, Christopher Sebela, Joshua Williamson, Jordan Boyd, Joe Infurnari</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/e/evolution/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Human evolution has taken millions of years to get to this stage. But next week, we become something new. Around the world, humanity is undergoing rapid and unpredictable changes, and only three individuals seem to notice that their world is being reborn. But what can they do about it?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/evolution-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="proxima centauri" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>proxima centauri</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>proxima-centauri</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Farel Dalrymple</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/p/proxima-centauri/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>4.243 light-years from Earth, the teenage wizard adventurer Sherwood Breadcoat is stuck in the confounding spectral zone on the manufactured dimensional sphere, Proxima Centauri, looking for escape and a way back to his brother while dealing with his confusing emotions, alien creatures, and all sorts of unknown, fantastic dangers.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/proxima-centauri-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="the fix" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Crime, Drama, Mature" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>the fix</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>the-fix</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Nick Spencer, Steve Lieber</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/the-fix/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>A story of the crooked cops, scheming mobsters, and corrupt politicians that run things-and the sex toy that can bring them all down. Oh, and the hero is a drug-sniffing beagle named Pretzels. Bad people do bad things to each other in this frenetic, outrageous, sometimes off-putting new caper! If you liked classic crime comics like CRIMINAL and 100 Bullets we apologize in advance for letting you down!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/the-fix-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="cave carson has an interstellar eye" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>cave carson has an interstellar eye</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>cave-carson-has-an-interstellar-eye</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jon Rivera, Paul Maybury, Michael Avon Oeming</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/c/cave-carson-has-an-interstellar-eye/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>After a year of multiverse-hopping and fighting in the Milk Wars, returning to a normal life of digging and cave-diving just isn't the same for explorer Cave Carson. Sure, he's got his podcast, family and that cybernetic eye, but reminiscing about times gone by isn't the same as living. Luckily for Cave Carson and his daughter Chloe, they're about to get sucked into an all-new adventure-literally-when they go spelunking in a black hole! But what's caused this black hole to appears and what's its connection to the intergalactic music sensation Star Adam?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/cave-carson-has-an-interstellar-eye-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="new challengers" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>new challengers</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>new-challengers</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Aaron Gillespie, Scott Snyder, Andy Kubert</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/n/new-challengers-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Challengers Mountain has returned to the DC Universe and chosen a new team of explorers! Five misfit strangers are given a second chance at life, but only if they obey the orders of the mysterious Professor and execute deadly missions in the most unexplored corners of the multiverse! And if the new Challengers of the Unknown fail... it will be more than just their own lives that hang in the balance!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/new-challengers-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="hit-girl (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Leading ladies, Mature, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>hit-girl (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>hit-girl-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Mark Millar, Ricardo Lopez Ortiz</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/h/hit-girl-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The pint-sized Punisher-meets-Polly-Pocket has left America behind and set off to serve justice around the world. First stop: Colombia. A mother seeking vengeance for the murder of her child enlists Hit-Girl to destroy his killer, but Mindy has bigger plans for Colombia's most feared hitman.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/hit-girl-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="curse words" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>curse words</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>curse-words</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Charles Soule, Jordan Boyd, Ryan Browne</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/c/curse-words/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>A wizard has appeared in New York City, and he's casting wonderful spells, getting famous, getting rich-it's great! But it's not. This wizard has everyone fooled. He is actually an EVIL WIZARD, and EVIL THINGS are on the way. CURSE WORDS is a gonzo modern fantasy, full of darkness, light... and MAGIC.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/curse-words-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="the lost city explorers" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>the lost city explorers</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>the-lost-city-explorers</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Zack Kaplan, Alvaro Sarraseca, Chris Blythe</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/l/lost-city-explorers/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Lost cities aren't just the stuff of myths. They exist hidden right under our noses. But when a mysterious expedition is disrupted by supernatural activity, and an antiquities professor goes missing, his teenage daughter and her friends must become underground urban explorers, follow his tracks on a coming-of-age journey through subterranean tunnels, and ultimately find the holy grail of lost city: Atlantis buried right under New York City!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/the-lost-city-explorers-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="infidel" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Horror, Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>infidel</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>infidel</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Pornsak Pichetshote, Aaron Campbell, Jose Villarrubia</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/i/infidel/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>A haunted house story for the 21st century, INFIDEL follows an American Muslim woman and her multiracial neighbors who move into a building haunted by entities that feed off xenophobia.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/infidel-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="punks not dead" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Life sucks, Sci-fi, Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>punks not dead</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>punks-not-dead</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>David Barnett, Martin Simmonds</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/p/punks-not-dead/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>As if being an awkward, bullied 15-year-old isn't bad enough, 'Fergie' Ferguson suddenly discovers he can see dead people. Well, one dead person specifically-the ghost of a certain punk rocker named Sid. Sid's spirit was trapped in London's Heathrow Airport for 40 years until the day he met Fergie. Sid's ghost is now stuck to Fergie-as if Fergie doesn't have enough on his plate, being raised by a single mum whose idea of parenting is strictly fly-by-the-seat-of-your-pants. Now Fergie has to contend with an unruly ghost sidekick and some weird, uncontrollable new 'abilities'. How does the father Fergie never knew fit into this mayhem? And why is the Department for Extra-Usual Affairs showing an interest? Never Mind the Bollocks-all of this plus fish fingers, chunky chips, and endless pints of anarchy in the new monthly series PUNKS NOT DEAD!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/punks-not-dead-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
</danh_sach_truyen>