<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<danh_sach_truyen>
	<truyen ten="the weatherman" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>the weatherman</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>the-weatherman</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jody LeHeup, Nathan Fox, Marcos Martin</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/the-weatherman/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Nathan Bright had it all: an awesome girlfriend, a kickass dog, and a job as the number one weatherman on terraformed Mars. But when he's accused of carrying out the worst terrorist attack in human history-an event that wiped out nearly the entire population of Earth-Nathan becomes the most wanted man alive and a target of a manhunt that spans the galaxy. But is Nathan truly responsible for such a horrific crime? And why can't he remember? Writer JODY LEHEUP (SHIRTLESS BEAR-FIGHTER!), artist NATHAN FOX (DMZ, HAUNT, Dark Reign: Zodiac), and colorist DAVE STEWART (Hellboy, RUMBLE) present a full-throttle, widescreen science fiction epic about the damage we do in the name of justice and what it truly means to be redeemed...You don't want to miss THE WEATHERMAN!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/the-weatherman-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="stellar" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>stellar</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>stellar</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Joseph Keatinge, Bret Blevins</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/s/stellar/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Stellar was taken as a child and transformed into the ultimate weapon, one that would end an intergalactic war. She succeeded... at everything except finding peace. Reduced to a bounty hunter, she scours the worlds she's broken, searching for redemption. But there are other weapons loose in the galaxy, who just can't leave the war behind them.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/stellar-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="the magic order" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Fantasy, Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>the magic order</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>the-magic-order</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Mark Millar, Olivier Coipel, Adam Hughes</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/the-magic-order/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>We live in a world where we've never seen a monster, and The Magic Order is the reason we sleep safely in our beds. Magic meets the mob in THE MAGIC ORDER, as five families of magicians-sworn to protect our world for generations-must battle an enemy who's picking them off one by one. By day, they live among us as our neighbors, friends, and co-workers, but by night, they are the sorcerers, magicians, and wizards that protect us from the forces of darkness... unless the darkness gets them first.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/the-magic-order-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="witchfinder: the gates of heaven" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Horror" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>witchfinder: the gates of heaven</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>witchfinder-the-gates-of-heaven</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Mike Mignola, Chris Roberson, D'Israeli, Michelle Madsen</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/w/witchfinder-the-gates-of-heaven/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>A series of occult events mystifies the man known as the Witchfinder, but even more surprising is the revelation that he is not alone in exploring the paranormal in London. When a personal invitation arrives from the palace, Sir Edward Grey is pulled even deeper into underground supernatural exploration alongside new allies in the race to stop a mad scientist from destroying London in his pursuit of mystical power.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/witchfinder-the-gates-of-heaven-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="justice league (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>justice league (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>justice-league-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Scott Snyder, Jim Cheung, Mark Morales</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/j/justice-league-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>A brand-new era begins here! Comics legends Scott Snyder and Jim Cheung launch the Justice League into a cosmos-shaking mystery that will draw out their most terrible foes... in ways our heroes couldn't possibly imagine! In this debut issue, Martian Manhunter struggles to protect the team from an incoming threat that will shatter the world as they know it, while a familiar face strikes out on a dark path...</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/justice-league-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="tony stark: iron man" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>tony stark: iron man</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>tony-stark-iron-man</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Dan Slott, Valerio Schiti, Alexandro Lozano</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/tony-stark-iron-man/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>TAKE FLIGHT WITH DAN SLOTT and VALERIO SCHITI! From the cusp of tomorrow's dreams to the forefront of imagination, one man always soars on the cutting edge of adventure! You know his name. Tony Stark is Iron Man. And Iron Man... is an idea. Always changing. Always evolving. An idea without limit! Take wing with DAN SLOTT (AMAZING SPIDER-MAN) and VALERIO SCHITI (GUARDIANS OF THE GALAXY) as they propel the ultimate Self-Made Hero to new heights of inventiveness! Tony Stark is Iron Man. The future is now. Strap in!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/tony-stark-iron-man-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="damage (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>damage (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>damage-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Robert Venditti, Tony Salvador Daniel, Danny Miki, Tomeu Morey</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/damage/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Ethan 'Elvis' Avery just wanted to serve his country. Instead, he's been changed into a monster! Tasked as the government's own living, breathing, ticking time bomb, Ethan retains no control when the monster takes over. Cheaper than a nuclear warhead and twice as effective, Ethan fights to rein in the damage he unleashes when the beast inside him springs free for one hour a day. With everyone around him in danger, Ethan struggles to contain the DAMAGE he inflicts on the DC Universe.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/damage-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="x-23 (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Leading ladies, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>x-23 (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>x-23-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Mariko Tamaki, Juann Cabal, Mike Choi</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/x/x-23-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Cloned from a warrior, raised as a killer, Laura Kinney has gone through hell and come out the other side a hero. After a stint as the All-New Wolverine, she returns to her roots as X-23 to make sure no one ever has to go through the horrors she did. With her sister Gabby and their pet Jonathan in tow, X-23 forges her own destiny in this new series by Mariko Tamaki (HULK, HUNT FOR WOLVERINE: CLAWS OF A KILLER) and Juann Cabal (ALL-NEW WOLVERINE, ELEKTRA).</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/x-23-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="robotech (2017)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Drama, Mecha, Movies - tv, Romance, Sci-fi, Space opera" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>robotech (2017)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>robotech-2017</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Brian Wood, Marco Turini, Marco Lesko, John Workman</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/r/robotech/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Not just another retelling of the Macross saga... the story continues as we bring Carl Macek's original vision full circle. Taking into account every iteration of the series, this new Robotech casts a fresh eye over classic characters like Rick Hunter, Lisa Hayes, Lynn Minmei, Roy Fokker, Claudia Grant, and Henry Gloval. Brian Wood and Marco Turini take us back to a Macross Island where 'nothing' can be taken for granted.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/robotech-2017-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="quantum and woody! (2017)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>quantum and woody! (2017)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>quantum-and-woody-2017</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Nick Spencer, Ryan Ottley</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/q/quantum-and-woody-(2017)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Sometimes...you embrace your destiny. And sometimes... you and your trouble-making adopted brother find yourselves trapped in a scientific lab explosion that grants you ****ing awesome super-powers. As a result of their accident, Eric and Woody Henderson - aka Quantum and Woody - must 'klang' their wristbands together every 24 hours or both dissipate into nothingness. Which makes superhero-ing pretty awkward when you're not on speaking terms at the moment. See, Eric has been keeping a pretty big secret: He knows who Woody's birth father really is...and where he's been hiding all these years. With great power comes great sibling rivalry! This winter, you'll believe two men and one goat can split a one-bedroom apartment and still be a credible threat to evil and injustice everywhere when QUANTUM AND WOODY make headlines and take names!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/quantum-and-woody-2017-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="the ballad of sang" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Crime, Martial arts" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>the ballad of sang</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>the-ballad-of-sang</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Ed Brisson, Alessandro Micelli, Shari Chankhamma</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/the-ballad-of-sang/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Kidnapped off the streets of the Philippines as an infant and trained as a child assassin, Sang has never had a childhood. All he's ever known is killing and the kindness of his master, Chen, the closest thing Sang has to a father. When Sang's enthusiasm botches a job, it brings the wrath of Don Minchella down on the pair, resulting in Chen's murder. Barely escaping with his own life -- and with Minchella's severed arm in tow -- Sang swears revenge, while every gang in the city mobilizes to return him to Minchella, dead or alive.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/the-ballad-of-sang-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="gideon falls" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Horror, Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>gideon falls</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>gideon-falls</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jeff Lemire, Andrea Sorrentino, Jock</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/g/gideon-falls/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>A brand-new ongoing series from the acclaimed bestselling creative team of Old Man Logan and Green Arrow! The lives of a reclusive young man obsessed with a conspiracy in the city's trash, and a washed-up Catholic priest arriving in a small town full of dark secrets, become intertwined around the mysterious legend of The Black Barn, an otherworldly building that is alleged to have appeared in both the city and the small town, throughout history, bringing death and madness in its wake. Rural mystery and urban horror collide in this character-driven meditation on obsession, mental illness, and faith.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/gideon-falls-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="the amazing spider-man (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>the amazing spider-man (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>the-amazing-spider-man-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Nick Spencer, Ryan Ottley</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/a/amazing-spider-man-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>An alien invasion hits New York City and the only one who can stop it is... Spider-Man?! And if even that's not enough, you'll see a new roommate, new love interests - and a new villain!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/the-amazing-spider-man-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="superman (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>superman (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>superman-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Brian Michael Bendis, Ivan Reis</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/s/superman-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>A bold new chapter for the greatest superhero of all time begins here as the superstar team of writer Brian Michael Bendis and artist Ivan Reis begin their run on the all-new SUPERMAN! The fallout from the Man of Steel miniseries has Clark Kent looking at the world through new eyes... with new ideas about what Superman could and should do for the city of Metropolis and the planet Earth.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/superman-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="tomb raider: inferno" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Video games" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>tomb raider: inferno</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>tomb-raider-inferno</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Collin Kelly, Jackson Lazing, Phillip Sevy</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/tomb-raider-inferno/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Trinity is on high alert--they know Lara Croft is coming and now, under the shrewd command of a new officer, they're ready for any surprises, but Lara is steadfast in her quest to uncover their secrets. Though typically equally prepared, this time Lara may just find herself one step behind.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/tomb-raider-inferno-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="pestilence: a story of satan" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Fantasy, Horror" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>pestilence: a story of satan</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>pestilence-a-story-of-satan</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Frank Tieri, Oleg Okunev</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/p/pestilence-a-story-of-satan/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The year is 1353. The fugitive Roderick Helms has retreated to a life of hidden seclusion after failing to expose the Church's role in the Black Death. But something threatens to bring him back into action. Something that has risen which will threaten to transform the waning plague into a far more darker and sinister crisis. And that something is none other than Satan himself!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/pestilence-a-story-of-satan-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="transformers: unicron" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Mecha, Movies - tv, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>transformers: unicron</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>transformers-unicron</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>John Barber, Alex Milne</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/transformers-unicron/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Not a whimper, nor a bang--the end comes with a squall of entropy shrieking from the ravenous maw of death itself. The message is clear: Unicron has arrived. The Transformers lock into a desperate bid to save Rom's homeworld from the world-killer--but why has Unicron chosen this world on his path to Cybertron... and Earth? The biggest story in the history of Transformers starts now: for Unicron's arrival can mean nothing less than the end of a universe.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/transformers-unicron-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="transformers: lost light" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Mecha, Movies - tv, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>transformers: lost light</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>transformers-lost-light</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>James Roberts, Jack Lawrence</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/transformers-lost-light/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Five years ago, Rodimus and a collection of traumatised, lovelorn and/or sarcastic Autobots set off on a quest to find Cyberutopia. So far, they've made a right hash of it. They've misplaced their map. They've lost their ship, the Lost Light, to a mutinous escapologist. Oh, and they're dead.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/transformers-lost-light-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="pathfinder: spiral of bones" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>pathfinder: spiral of bones</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>pathfinder-spiral-of-bones</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Crystal Frasier, Rob McCreary, Diego Galindo, Tom Garcia</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/p/pathfinder-spiral-of-bones/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>As the Pathfinder plunge into the history and mysteries below Kaer Maga-the no-holds-barred 'City of Strangers'-Valeros plunges far deeper into the great beyond, defending his immortal soul in the courts of the dead! From Pathfinder author Crystal Frasier comes this scintillating tale of life, death, and what lingers when we're gone. Bonus: Starfinder backup story! Thousands of years in Pathfinder's future, the Starfinder Society spreads adventure across the solar system!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/pathfinder-spiral-of-bones-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="weird love" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Horror, Romance" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>weird love</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>weird-love</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Various, Vinnie Colletta, Jose Luis Garcia-Lopez, Norman Nodel, Al Tewks, Ogden Whitney, Joe Gill</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/w/weird-love/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>From the people that bring you the acclaimed Haunted Horror comic comes a horror like no other... WEIRD Love! WEIRD Love presents the most sexy, bizarro, sick, twisted, politically incorrect, kinky 'romance' comics of the 1950s and beyond. No wonder the censors wanted this stuff banned! Sure to be must-have big-buzz comics!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/weird-love-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="the unexpected" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>the unexpected</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>the-unexpected</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Steve Orlando, Cary Nord, Ryan Sook, Mick Gray, Wade von Grawbadger</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/the-unexpected-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>In the aftermath of DARK NIGHTS: METAL, the DC Universe has been forever changed as new heroes are called out of the shadows. Amid this all is Janet Fals...Firebrand! Once a paramedic dedicated to saving lives, she must now start a fight once every 24 hours to feed the Conflict Engine that's replaced her heart. But Janet's heart isn't just a curse-it's a beacon, drawing out both the mysterious Neon the Unknown and the seductive, malevolent Bad Samaritan. One of them wants to cut out her heart, the other wants to save it-but neither of them knows the true danger hidden within that will kick off a superhero manhunt ranging from Thanagar to the deepest heart of the Dark Multiverse!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/the-unexpected-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="judge dredd: under siege" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Crime, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>judge dredd: under siege</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>judge-dredd-under-siege</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Mark Russell, Max Dunbar</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/j/judge-dredd-under-siege/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>When all contact with the Patrick Swayze Block is lost, Dredd and Judge Beeny are tasked with investigating. As they battle lawlessness and rampant criminality, they discover a threat to the city that they must contain at all costs...</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/judge-dredd-under-siege-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="sword daughter" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>sword daughter</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>sword-daughter</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Brian Wood, Mack Chater, Lauren Affe</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/s/sword-daughter/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The Forty Swords came at night and murdered the entire village, save for two people: the infant Elsbeth and her grief-stricken father, Dag. Setting off on a revenge quest that will span the width of Viking Age Europe, they find the key to repairing their damaged relationship lies in the swords they carry. Created by Brian Wood (Northlanders, The Massive, DMZ) and Mack Chater (Briggs Land, Lazarus), Sword Daughter is a visually stunning, emotionally poignant story of parental guilt and acceptance of loss.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/sword-daughter-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="brother nash" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Horror, Mystery, Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>brother nash</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>brother-nash</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Bridgit Connell</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/b/brother-nash/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Werewolves! Truckers! Magic! Monstrous cicadas! The unquiet dead! It's all here... on the road! Nash is a haunted trucker who can see ghosts, can talk with spirits, senses evil, and hides a dark secret... When Nash takes on a mysterious hitchhiker heading for Tucson, he and his friends are dragged head first into his biggest and most dangerous adventure yet.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/brother-nash-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="eternity girl" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>eternity girl</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>eternity-girl</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Magdalene Visaggio, Sonny Liew, Chris Chuckry</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/e/eternity-girl/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Caroline Sharp has been a lot of things, including both a superhero and a super-spy. But now, with those days behind her and her powers proving unreliable, Caroline finds herself stuck in a life weighed down by her depression and an inability to change. You see, Caroline is going to live forever, and there is no escape to be had. The very act of living reminds her that, to the rest of existence, she is an anomaly. All of that could change, however, when her old foe, Madame Atom, comes to her with an intriguing offer. Madame Atom can give Caroline the power to end her life; she just has to destroy the rest of the world.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/eternity-girl-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="oblivion song" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>oblivion song</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>oblivion-song</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Robert Kirkman, Lorenzo De Felici, Annalisa Leoni</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/o/oblivion-song/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>A decade ago, 300,000 citizens of Philadelphia were suddenly lost in Oblivion. The government made every attempt to recover them, but after many years, they gave up. Nathan Cole...won't. He makes daily trips, risking his life to try and rescue those still living in the apocalyptic hellscape of Oblivion. But maybe...Nathan is looking for something else? Why can't he resist the siren call of the Oblivion Song?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/oblivion-song-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="port of earth" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>port of earth</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>port-of-earth</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Zachary Kaplan, Andrea Mutti</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/p/port-of-earth/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Imagine if aliens came to Earth not in war or peace, but with a business deal: open up a spaceport here on Earth in exchange for advanced technology. But when our alien visitors break Port restrictions and wreak havoc in our cities, it falls to the newly formed Earth Security Agents to hunt down and safely deport the dangerous rogue aliens back to the Port of Earth.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/port-of-earth-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="coda  " tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Fantasy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>coda  </ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>coda</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Simon Spurrier, Matias Bergara, Michael Doig</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/c/coda/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Simon Spurrier (The Spire, Godshaper) and Matias Bergara (Cannibal, Supergirl) present a broken fantasy world that's perfect for fans of Mad Max and The Lord of the Rings. In the aftermath of an apocalypse which wiped out nearly all magic from a once-wondrous fantasy world, a former bard named Hum (a man of few words, so nicknamed because his standard reply is 'hm') seeks a way to save the soul of his wife with nothing but a foul-tempered mutant unicorn and his wits to protect him... but is unwillingly drawn into a brutal power struggle which will decide forever who rules the Weird Wasteland.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/coda-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="thief of thieves" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Crime, Drama, Life sucks, Psychological" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>thief of thieves</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>thief-of-thieves</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Nick Spencer, Robert Kirkman, Shawn Martinbrough</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/e/e2/Thief_of_Thieves.jpg/200px-Thief_of_Thieves.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Conrad Paulson lives a secret double life as master thief Redmond. There is nothing he can't steal, nothing he can't have... except for the life he left behind. Now, with a grown son he hardly knows, and an ex-wife he never stopped loving, Conrad must try to piece together what's left of his life, before the FBI finally catch up to him... but it appears they are the least of his worries.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/thief-of-thieves-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="pumpkinhead" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Fantasy, Horror, Movies - tv, Mythology" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>pumpkinhead</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>pumpkinhead</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Cullen Bunn, Blacky Shepherd, Kyle Strahm</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/p/pumpkinhead/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>For thirty years, the demon of vengeance has been still, its corpse buried in a pumpkin patch graveyard in the hills. But when a reckless driver accidentally kills a pair of children, the creature is called up once more. This time, though, the monster's intended target is protected by a cruel backwoods crime family. They hatch their own supernatural plans for dealing with Pumpkinhead. For each of man's sins, a special demon exists, and when seven infernal creatures roam the hills and the hollows, no one-guilty or otherwise-is safe.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/pumpkinhead-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
</danh_sach_truyen>