<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<danh_sach_truyen>
	<truyen ten="isuca" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Comedy, Ecchi, Harem, Mature, Romance, School life, Seinen, Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>isuca</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>isuca</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Takahashi Osamu</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/4307/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Shinichirou decides to look for a job in order to pay his rent, and his teacher suggests that he work for someone at their house, doing housekeeping. However, the person who hired him was Sakuya, a girl who is the 37th head of the Shimazu family, and her job is to exorcise and eliminate unwanted creatures. Shinichirou accidentally releases one of the creatures that Sakuya captures and they cooperate to catch it. A story of comedic creature hunting begins!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/isuca-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="sugars" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Romance, Shoujo." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>sugars</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>sugars</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Kurosaki Minori</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/9565/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Rita Hoshiyama is a second year in middle school and claims to be a rock musician! However, her parents disagree and insist that Rita take up cooking and their family business. But when Sakuya-kun, her idol and family's new dishwasher, ask her to do a live performance the next day, she couldn't help but agree! The problem is, there's only two people in her band...</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/sugars-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="ookami shoujo to kuro ouji" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Drama, Romance, School life, Shoujo." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>ookami shoujo to kuro ouji</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>ookami-shoujo-to-kuro-ouji</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Hatta Ayuko</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/7366/9/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Erika lied to her friends about having a boyfriend by showing a picture of an annonymous guy who turned out to be a a schoolmate of hers and was shortly recognized by her friends. Their conversations then was overheard by the guy, Sata Kyouya. Erika went to explain and proposed her idea of faking as lovers. However, Sata who gave off the nice-charming feelings guy turns out to be a black prince and used her reasons to blackmail her instead.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/ookami-shoujo-to-kuro-ouji-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="konjiki no moji tsukai - yuusha yonin ni makikomareta unique cheat" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Comedy, Fantasy, Harem, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>konjiki no moji tsukai - yuusha yonin ni makikomareta unique cheat</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>konjiki-no-moji-tsukai-yuusha-yonin-ni-makikomareta-unique-cheat</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Tomoto Sui, Ozaki Yuusuke</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/29695/4/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>There has been much conflict between the races of the 'Humas', the 'Gabranth', and the 'Evila'. To combat the 'Evila' race's Demon King, the kingdom summons five high school students from 21st century Japan who have the power of Heroes. However, only four out of five of those students had the status title of 'Hero'. Okamura Hiiro was summoned by accident since he sat near the other four students in class. Unlike them, he did not have the title of a 'Hero' but instead he had the title of 'Word Master' and 'Innocent Bystander'. Seeing through the 'Humas' kingdom's deceit and insanity, Hiiro decides that he has no wish to partake in their selfish war. Leaving the castle, Hiiro decides to join the Adventurer's Guild and does whatever he feels like. Who knows? Maybe there is some merit to being a 'Word Master' and an 'Innocent Bystander'.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/konjiki-no-moji-tsukai-yuusha-yonin-ni-makikomareta-unique-cheat-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="gleipnir" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Ecchi, Fantasy, Romance, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>gleipnir</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>gleipnir</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Takeda Sun</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/36253/3/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Shuichi Kagaya isn't human. He has an unnatural sense of smell, and can transform into an incredibly powerful beast... of sorts. He does all he can to avoid standing out and being discovered, but no good deed goes unpunished, and his decision to use his power to save a girl spells the end for his quiet life.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/gleipnir-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="megami no libra" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Romance, Shoujo." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>megami no libra</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>megami-no-libra</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Sakou Watari</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/28214/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Yuuki Tsumire was raised by her single mother, who always told her to keep smiling, no matter what hardships she endured. The two of them were a family, until Tsumire's mother died from illness. Tsumire soon learned that she had a family she knew nothing about: a cold, rich family that disowned her kindhearted mother when she became pregnant. Tsumire now must go live with this family, even though none of them seem to want her there. She doesn't have to switch schools, so she at least has her friends to help her through this difficult time. However, she doesn't have the heart to confide in her friends with even more problems, so she tries to keep it bottled up inside. To her surprise, the Yuuki family lawyer, a young man named Hino, soon becomes her emotional support in this difficult situation. However, Tsumire's reactions to him might mean that she wishes he were something more... Thanks go to tethysdust for the summary.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/megami-no-libra-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="getter robot devolution - uchuu saigo no 3-bunkan" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Mecha, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>getter robot devolution - uchuu saigo no 3-bunkan</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>getter-robot-devolution-uchuu-saigo-no-3-bunkan</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Ishikawa Ken, Shimizu Eiichi, Shimoguchi Tomohiro</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/38781/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Three young pilots connected by the Getter Rays (Ryoma Nagare, Hayato Jin, and Musashi Tomoe) are recruited by Dr. Saotome to fight the Devolved beings appearing from spatial distortions using the only weapon that can face these monsters, the Getter Robo. The Saotome Institute however holds a dangerous secret, a fragment of the being called Emperor which connects the Getter and its pilots to parallel worlds, including the presence of people from those worlds such as an older Hayato and Dr. Shikishima.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/getter-robot-devolution-uchuu-saigo-no-3-bunkan-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="rain  " tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Drama, Fantasy, Romance, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>rain  </ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>rain</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Yoshino Takumi, Sumikawa Megumi</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>http://www.mangadeep.com/wp-content/manga/cover/tbn/rain_200x0.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>The small country Sunkwoll is in a tight spot because it's under attack of the great country Zarmine. But the general, Rain, who's reputed to be an exceptionally gifted swordsman, is against the war and won't enter the battle. But how is one supposed to wage a war like this anyway?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/rain-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="kimi to kore kara" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Drama, Romance, Shounen ai, Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>kimi to kore kara</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>kimi-to-kore-kara</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Yamamoto Kotetsuko</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/28219/3/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Here starts the Konya spinoff series, focusing more on Gorou and Verde! There's plenty of Endou and Rikiya as well, but this story will spend more time telling the story of these heretofore side characters. The story takes place immediately after the last Konya chapter, so you can think of this as Chapter 20, just less focus on Endo/Rikiya and more on Gorou/Verde.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/kimi-to-kore-kara-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="gigant" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Drama, Mature, Romance, School life, Sci-fi, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>gigant</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>gigant</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Oku Hiroya</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-comic-4.anyacg.co/thumbs/w300/96/04/9604402428c74a40bce9f9d31ae89b5d05c4aa17_29170_200_310.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Yamada Yoko, a high school boy who has a movie producer father. One day, while out with friends to shoot a film that he plans to enter into a film festival, a poster of Papiko, an adult video actress with big breasts, catches his eye.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/gigant-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="trinity blood" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Comedy, Drama, Mystery, Romance, Sci-fi, Shoujo., Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>trinity blood</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>trinity-blood</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Kyujyo Kiyo, Yoshida Sunao</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/10486/3/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>The background is in the distant future, a post-apocalyptic world after the destruction brought about by Armageddon. The war between humans (Terran) and vampires (Methuselah) continues, as a struggle between two factions: the Vatican and the New Human Empire. Yet, amidst the bloodshed and violence, many desire a peaceful co-existence between the two species. However, standing between them and this goal is the Rosenkreuz Orden, a group of vampire extremists who manipulate the two sides and pit them against each other. To combat them, the Vatican special operations group 'AX,' led by Cardinal Caterina, must use everything they have - even a vampire who preys on the blood of other vampires.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/trinity-blood-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="hajimete datteba!" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Ecchi, Romance, School life, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>hajimete datteba!</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>hajimete-datteba</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Saki Kaori</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/3363/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>There is first time at everything, and you don't know anything about it. Not about your partner, not about yourself and even how to advance in love. In a certain port city, energetic high schooler Kana, and firm high schooler Kouki live. Two of them experiencing first time at every thing they do. Author of 'Smash!', Saki Kaori presents, Hajimete Datte ba!. A heartful love story has now began.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/hajimete-datteba-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="world customize creator" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Comedy, Drama, Fantasy, Romance, Sci-fi, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>world customize creator</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>world-customize-creator</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Hero Tennki, Hijikata Yuu</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/26898/5/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Tagami Yusuke, led by a mysterious voice, is summoned to another world, 'Caltsio'. He was just a young video-game lover, but Fate decided to make him become the 'Evil God of Calamity' of this world, obtaining the ability to create and customize everything, Customize Creation.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/world-customize-creator-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="cross account" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Romance, School life, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>cross account</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>cross-account</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Date Tsunehiro</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/50309/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>A romantic comedy about a boy and his social media rage; a story of social media and the crossing fates of a young man and a young woman who were never supposed to meet.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/cross-account-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="king golf" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Comedy, Shounen., Sports" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>king golf</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>king-golf</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Sasaki Takeshi</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/5066/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>In Teirin High School, you are either part of a gang or an elite sports player. Sousuke Youki, called 'the predator,' is an undefeated master at fighting. One morning, as he finishes up a fight, Kazumi, a prodigy amateur golf player, took a look at Sousuke, ignored him, and walked right by. Infuriated, Sousuke sets out to get revenge on Kazumi for dissing him but Sousuke's revenge takes a detour as he gets himself involved in playing golf by the thuggish golf coach. Will this delinquent break legends and become 'the King of Golf'? King Golf also won the 56th Shogakukan Manga Award in January 2011 in the boys category.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/king-golf-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="gou - himetachi no sengoku" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Drama, Historical, Romance, Shoujo." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>gou - himetachi no sengoku</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>gou-himetachi-no-sengoku</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Tabuchi Kumiko, Akatsuki Kaori</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/3228/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>The 50th NHK Taiga drama is Gou. The story focuses on the life of Gou, a wife of the second Tokugawa shogun Hidetada. Gou was the third daughter of the daimyo Azai Nagamasa, who was married to the sister of Oda Nobunaga. One of Gou's older sisters was the wife of Toyotomi Hideyoshi, while the other married the daimyo Kyogoku Takatsugu.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/gou-himetachi-no-sengoku-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="uchuu kyoudai" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Drama, Psychological, Sci-fi, Seinen, Slice of life" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>uchuu kyoudai</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>uchuu-kyoudaii</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Koyama Chuuya</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/73/8/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>One night in 2006, when they were young, the two brothers Mutta (born 1993) and Hibito (born 1996) saw what appeared to be a UFO heading for the moon. They decided that night to both become astronauts and travel out into space. In 2025, Hibito has become an astronaut, and he's going to go to the moon. Mutta ended up following a more traditional career path with an auto development company. However, Mutta just ruined his career through a violent altercation with his boss. Now, not only has he lost his job, he appears to be blacklisted in the entire industry. Maybe this is a rare opportunity for Mutta to once again chase his childhood dream and become an astronaut like his little brother! Nominated for the 2nd and 3rd Manga Taisho Award and won the 56th Shogakukan Manga Award and 35th Kodansha Manga Award in the General Category.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/uchuu-kyoudaii-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="saenai kanojo no sodatekata - koisuru metronome" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Drama, Romance, School life, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>saenai kanojo no sodatekata - koisuru metronome</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>saenai-kanojo-no-sodatekata-koisuru-metronome</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Maruto Fumiaki, Musha Sabu</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/27524/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Famed author Kasumigaoka Utaha had always struggled with her novel series, 'Koisuru Metronome' until she met Tomoyo Aki; her biggest fan who inspires her to give it a proper conclusion and later becomes her personal editor. Now with Tomoya's passion and Kasumigaoka's determination combined, the two work together on their latest series while also discovering their true feelings and finding parallels between themselves and the characters within Kasumigaoka's novels.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/saenai-kanojo-no-sodatekata-koisuru-metronome-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="seikon no qwaser" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Drama, Harem, Mature, School life, Shounen., Supernatural, Yuri" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>seikon no qwaser</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>seikon-no-qwaser</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Yoshino Hiroyuki, Satou Kenetsu</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/8688/5/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Balud Cornelius is the son of a noble of the Mauricia kingdom and inside him also dwell the souls of the niggardly warring states commander Oka Sadatoshi and animal ear otaku high schooler Oka Masaharu. With these 3 souls in a single body, he can exhibit extraordinary abilities when it comes to combat or managing the domain.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/seikon-no-qwaser-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="isekai tensei soudouki" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Adventure, Comedy, Drama, Fantasy, Harem, Romance" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>isekai tensei soudouki</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>isekai-tensei-soudouki</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Takami Ryousen, Honoji</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/32865/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Balud Cornelius is the son of a noble of the Mauricia kingdom and inside him also dwell the souls of the niggardly warring states commander Oka Sadatoshi and animal ear otaku high schooler Oka Masaharu. With these 3 souls in a single body, he can exhibit extraordinary abilities when it comes to combat or managing the domain.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/isekai-tensei-soudouki-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="maou-jou de oyasumi" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Fantasy, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>maou-jou de oyasumi</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>maou-jou-de-oyasumi</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Kumanomata Kagiji</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/41990/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>The princess of the human kingdom has been kidnapped by the demon king! But all she wants to do is get a good night's sleep!?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/maou-jou-de-oyasumi-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="sun-ken rock" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adult, Comedy, Drama, Ecchi, Martial arts, Mature, Psychological, Romance, Seinen, Tragedy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>sun-ken rock</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>sun-ken-rock</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Boichi</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/9638/4/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Ken is a Japanese man, and Ken's love interest Yumin moves to Korea to become a police officer. He then decides to follow her to also become a police officer but instead ends up becoming the leader of a small Korean gang. What will happend to Ken?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/sun-ken-rock-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="ragna crimson" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Fantasy, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>ragna crimson</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>ragna-crimson</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Kobayashi Daiki</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/49622/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Ragna is a dragon hunter along with his partner, the strongest dragon hunter Leo. He didn't have much talent at hunting dragons but he had decided to entrust his whole life for her. However he was shown the feel of true despair by his future self on what would happen if he stays weak as he is now. With that, it seems that the reaper of the dragons had now appeared earlier than the original history, but will it be enough to change future?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/ragna-crimson-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="silver spoon" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Drama, Romance, School life, Shounen., Slice of life" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>silver spoon</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>silver-spoon</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Arakawa Hiromu</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/38842/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Yugo Hachiken aspires to live separated from his family, so he takes the initiative by enrolling in an agriculture school. He thinks, with his talent in studying, no problems will arise no matter what kind of school he attends. He is quickly proven wrong. Raised as a city boy, he is forced to uncover the inconvenient truth about agricultural life. Enjoy the story of Hachiken, as he tries to keep up with his new friends, farmers' heirs, who are already accustomed to harsh world of farming. The story of a sweat, tear, and mud-stained youth begins!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/silver-spoon-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="ichigo 100%" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Drama, Ecchi, Harem, Romance, School life, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>ichigo 100%</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>ichigo-100</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Kawashita Mizuki</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://i.imgur.com/msPWICD.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>The hero (me, Junpei Manaka!) sneaks up to the roof to see the sunset. When he opens the door, he startles a mysterious beauty. She panics and runs away, but not before Junpei has caught sight of her adorable strawberry print panties... in EXTREME close-up. With that vision forever burned into his memory, Junpei embarks on a quest to find the girl, and the panties, of his dreams!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/ichigo-100-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="taboo-tattoo" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adult, Comedy, Ecchi, Martial arts, Mystery, Romance, School life, Seinen, Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>taboo-tattoo</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>taboo-tattoo</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Shinjirou</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/9742/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Seigi, a martial arts trained middle schooler, often feels driven to protect the weaker people around him. One day, he defends a homeless man against some punks, and the man gives him a strange tattoo on his palm in return. The tattoo is a secret weapon produced in the arms race between America and the Serinistan Kingdom. Seigi finds himself in over his head when a powerful girl, using the same secret weapon, violently pursues him in order to retrieve it. His skill at martial arts may not be enough to keep him alive, but will he be able to learn how to trigger the power of his tattoo in time?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/taboo-tattoo-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="onideka" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Seinen, Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>onideka</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>onideka</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Yatera Keita</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/43458/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Kiryuin Hanasei is the idol of her school. But when she suddenly becomes a giantess, she is forced to return to her old ways in order to protect her city.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/onideka-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="tohai" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Drama, Psychological, Romance, Seinen, Sports" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>tohai</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>tohai</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Shinasaka Koji</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/38140/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Not a lot of people know that one of the most talented and ruthless Mahjong players in the city is a young high school boy. Kei is a teenager of few words, but his observation skills, unwavering will and experience in the game allows him to survive in a world full of powerful, rich and dangerous characters. Kei is currently hiding a girl named Amina who has entered the country illegally and protecting her from being deported. He spends his days sleeping through class and his nights playing high-stakes Mahjong, waiting for when a worthy opponent arrives.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/tohai-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="yomekura" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Ecchi, Harem, Romance, School life, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>yomekura</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>yomekura</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Chiaki Tarou</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/43502/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Before she died, Taga Reiji's mother made arrangements to ensure her son would not be alone. What Taga did not know about these 'arrangements' was that he would be enrolled into a special class at the school his mother founded where prospective fiance candidates would all vie for his hand in marriage. How will Taga's new life of constantly being surrounded by girls unfold and will he be able to choose just one?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/yomekura-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="back street girls - washira idol hajimemashita." tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Ecchi, Gender bender, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>back street girls - washira idol hajimemashita.</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>back-street-girls-washira-idol-hajimemashita</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Jasmine Gyuh</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/42569/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>A group of 3 yakuza failed their boss for the last time. After messing up an important job, the boss gives them 2 choices: Honorably committing suicide, or go to Thailand to get a sex reassignment surgery in order to becomes 'female' idols. After a gruesome year long training to become idols, they successfully debut, with overwhelming popularity, much to their dismay. This is where their tragedy truly begins.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/back-street-girls-washira-idol-hajimemashita-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
</danh_sach_truyen>