<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<danh_sach_truyen>
	<truyen ten="waratte! sotomura-san" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="4 koma, Comedy, School life, Seinen, Slice of life" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>waratte! sotomura-san</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>waratte-sotomura-san</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Minamori Minamo</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/10968/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Sotomura is a high-school girl widely regarded as a delinquent, feared and avoided by many of the school body. From her light-brown hair down to her long skirt and harsh manner of speaking, she completely seems the part. But after Sotomura rescues a girl named Haruno from some bullies, Haruno decides to try to get to know her better. Haruno is surprised to find out that Sotomura isn't a delinquent at all and is, in fact, just a very socially awkward girl that's bad with words and wants to make friends. She enjoys cooking, handicrafts, and hitting the supermarket sales. She also loves cute and fancy things, but she tries to hide that fact because she feels they don't suit her looks. Haruno's first step in helping Sotomura is to try to teach her how to smile, because whenever she tries, it ends up as a scary grin. Thus begins the story of Sotomura's attempts to make new friends.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/waratte-sotomura-san-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="biorg trinity" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Romance, Sci-fi, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>biorg trinity</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>biorg-trinity</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Maijou Outarou, Oh! Great</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/1195/4/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Biorg Trinity follows Fujii, a high-school student who is in love with Enomoto Fumiho. He lives in a world where people are touched by a rare "illness" called the Biorg Bug. One day Fujii catches the bug which makes holes in the shape of hearts on his hands. What will happen to him now?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/biorg-trinity-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="velvet kiss" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Adult, Drama, Ecchi, Harem, Mature, Romance, Seinen, Smut" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>velvet kiss</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>velvet-kiss</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Harumi Chihiro</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/10850/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Nitta Shin finds himself saddled with a sudden, crushing debt. His loan agent tells him he can escape repayment if he keeps a particular woman company. He gradually learns that this arrangement might not be as easy as he once thought.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/velvet-kiss-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="boku to kimi to de niji ni naru" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Romance, School life, Shoujo." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>boku to kimi to de niji ni naru</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>boku-to-kimi-to-de-niji-ni-naru</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Fujisawa Shizuki</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/1382/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Because she loved the word "wisdom", Rui hated the words "waste" and "fuzzy". One day, a guy named Shou appeared on her life. And thank to that encounter, Rui will suddenly change... And that's the beginning of a "rainbow school daze" between that super dry girl and that careless guy.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/boku-to-kimi-to-de-niji-ni-naru-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="ane no onaka o fukuramaseru wa boku" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Romance, Seinen, Slice of life" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>ane no onaka o fukuramaseru wa boku</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>ane-no-onaka-o-fukuramaseru-wa-boku</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Sakai Onta, Onda Chiro</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/42784/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>This is the story of a pair of step-siblings who are now living alone together. The high-school-age older sister, Kyoko, is pretty wild (and is even into pro-wrestling), while the elementary-school-age little brother is a fairly serious kid. He is often embarrassed by her teasing. The two of them pass their daily life together, every day cooking for one another.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/ane-no-onaka-o-fukuramaseru-wa-boku-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="akaiito" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Romance, School life, Shoujo." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>akaiito</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>akaiito</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Miyasaka Kaho</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/475/3/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>I like you. But, I kept on thinking that I should hate him. I like you. But, you look like a different guy to me. I like you. But, you told me that I'm like 'your younger sister'. I like you. But, you kissed that person in front of me. Numerous 'red threads' intertwine. Brewing a few romances. This is the willfully unrestrained, youth idol drama of 7 guys and girls.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/akaiito-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="idol na kanojo to wotaku na boku to" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Mature, Romance, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>idol na kanojo to wotaku na boku to</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>idol-na-kanojo-to-wotaku-na-boku-to</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Kasuga Shun</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/42688/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>She is a famous idol. On the other hand, I am just a nerd. We have to keep our relationship a secret.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/idol-na-kanojo-to-wotaku-na-boku-to-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="koneko-chan, kocchi ni oide" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Josei, Romance, Slice of life, Smut" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>koneko-chan, kocchi ni oide</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>koneko-chan-kocchi-ni-oide</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Watabe Mihou</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/43102/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>After Yuko graduated from junior college, she ended up running a shop. Though her career is going well, she hasn't had time to work on her love life. One day, she's out drinking with her best friend Mikan, bemoaning her lack of a boyfriend for a Christmas date. When she trips and hurts her leg, Mikan asks her little brother Leo (an 18-year-old) to see Yuko home safely. When they arrive at her apartment, though, Yuko makes a move on him and they end up sleeping together. The next morning, she realizes that she not only slept with her best friend's little brother, she actually took his virginity! Leo isn't satisfied with it being a one-night stand, and they start having a completely sexual relationship. Will she be able to keep this from Mikan, and is it possible their relationship may grow to something more?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/koneko-chan-kocchi-ni-oide-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="aka akatoretachi no monogatari" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Drama, Ecchi, Mature, Romance, Shounen., Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>aka akatoretachi no monogatari</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>aka-akatoretachi-no-monogatari</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Kaishaku</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/27304/5/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Itsuki and Hayato, two brothers who grew up in a village nestled deep in the mountains, set out to hunt down a wolf that has been attacking the livestock of the village. Itsuki is about to go in for the kill when a gigantic beast appears out of nowhere, snatching up the wolf in its jaws and sucking the life out of it. The beast that stared Itsuki down was a gargantuan, blood-sucking vampire deer? Will the two brothers be able to return to the village alive?! Find out in this blood-filled action-packed story by extraordinary mangaka Kaishaku!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/aka-akatoretachi-no-monogatari-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="urami koi, koi, urami koi." tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Comedy, Drama, Romance, Shounen., Supernatural, Suspense, Tragedy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>urami koi, koi, urami koi.</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>urami-koi-koi-urami-koi</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Akitaka</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/27916/3/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>The Twelve City, a land governed by the leaders of the families who bear in their names the Chinese zodiac. In a city where youkai and humans coexist, the cat youkai who holds a grudge against the Rat Family appears in front of Nekuni Kyouichi, the head of the Rat Family. It's a malice-covered Hateful cat who is aiming for his life. But that youkai is Nekogasaki Natsuho, who's also extremely anxious around other people... Just like the saying "Curiosity killed the cat" goes, will these feelings also kill the cat?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/urami-koi-koi-urami-koi-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="seshiji o pin! to - shikakou kyougi dance-bu e youkoso" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, School life, Shounen., Sports" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>seshiji o pin! to - shikakou kyougi dance-bu e youkoso</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>seshiji-o-pin-to-shikakou-kyougi-dance-bu-e-youkoso</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Yokota Takuma</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/33171/7/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Masaharu Tsuchiya has just become a freshman in high school and he's looking to make a change in his life. He wants to be more active and more involved in school life, since the only club he was a part of in middle school he just coasted through. He'd also like to get over his lack of social skills when it comes to women. However, in his future, he'll soon be tossed into a strange and magical world full of dancing after he witnesses his school's competitive dance club in action...</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/seshiji-o-pin-to-shikakou-kyougi-dance-bu-e-youkoso-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="otoyomegatari" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Drama, Historical, Romance, Seinen, Slice of life" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>otoyomegatari</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>otoyomegatari</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Mori Kaoru</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/7554/4/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Set in Central Asia in a rural town near the Caspian Sea during the early 19th century, the story revolves around a young woman, Amir, who arrives from a distant village across the mountains to marry Karluk, a boy eight years her junior. The story unfolds among details of everyday family and community life. However, the peaceful atmosphere is disturbed when Amir's family demands to take her back to their village. Note: Won the 7th annual Manga Taishou Award in 2014 and the intergenerations prize at the Angouleme International Comics Festival in 2012.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/otoyomegatari-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="mahou tsukai no yome" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Drama, Fantasy, Romance, Shounen., Slice of life, Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>mahou tsukai no yome</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>mahou-tsukai-no-yome</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Yamazaki Kore</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/25056/8/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>With her mother dead and father long gone, Chise Hatori has spent her childhood being passed unwanted from relative to relative, until she finally makes her unfortunate way to a strange and improbable auction block. Offered as a "sleigh beggy" to the highest bidder, Chise is purchased by the (literally) boneheaded Elias Ainsworth, who promises to take her on as his apprentice. Elias is a mage, and his world is one of dragons and faeries - but before Chise can begin to get accustomed to all that nonsense, Elias drops another bombshell. Apparently Chise isn't just intended to be his apprentice - she will also be his bride. Nominated for the 8th Manga Taisho Award.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/mahou-tsukai-no-yome-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="black bullet" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Drama, Horror, Romance, Sci-fi, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>black bullet</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>black-bullet</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Kanzaki Shiden, Morino Hon</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/1226/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>In near future, mankind has been defeated by the viral parasites named "Gastrea." They have been exiled into a small territory and live in despair, side by side with terror. In this world trapped in darkness Rentaro, a boy living near Tokyo and a member of the "Civil Security"-an organization specializing in fighting against the Gastrea-is used to accomplishing dangerous tasks. His partner is Enju, a precocious young girl. They fight using their peculiar powers until one day, they receive a special assignment from the government. This top secret mission is to prevent the destruction of Tokyo. Set in a near future, this thrilling heroic-action story starts now.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/black-bullet-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="hazuki kanon wa amakunai." tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="4-koma, Comedy, Romance, School life, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>hazuki kanon wa amakunai.</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>hazuki-kanon-wa-amakunai</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Kobashiko</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/35341/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Hazuki Kanon is your average female High-School Delinquent. She is often late and skips class in the nurse office, occassionally talking to the male nurse BJ (Kuronada Jun). Tamaki Daiji likes to film stuff that captivates him the instant he encounters it, disregarding consequences. His friend Kihou Tomoka tries to snap him out of it, whenever she sees him stuck while he is late for something else. One day Kanon catches his interest while she stands on the roof of the opposite building. After asking Tomoka, he decides to head to the infirmary where Kanon sleeps occasionally. Kanon wakes up to some strange guy filming her. He even has the audacity to call her "thumb-suckling while sleeping" cute and captivating. So she decides to let him keep the footage if he promises to keep her secret.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/hazuki-kanon-wa-amakunai-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="seishun buta yarou wa bunny girl senpai no yume o minai" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Romance, School life, Seinen, Slice of life" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>seishun buta yarou wa bunny girl senpai no yume o minai</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>seishun-buta-yarou-wa-bunny-girl-senpai-no-yume-o-minai</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Kamoshida Hajime, Nanamiya Tsugumi</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/42856/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>"Hey, shall we kiss?" She who was teasing me with these seductive words temporarily disappeared before my eyes. There could not be a bunny girl inhabiting a library. Azusagawa Sakuta faced a scene that toppled common sense-he encountered a bunny girl, and she is nowhere a normal bunny girl. She is Sakurajima Mai senpai, a student studying at the same school as Sakuta and a retired yet renowned actress. It was said that starting from a few days ago, those around her could no longer see her anymore, and she came to the library just to confirm this. Is this related to the hit topic on the internet, the unimaginable phenomenon known as "the puberty syndrome"? Sakuta, wanting to know the reasons behind and get closer to Mai, decided to solve the puzzle. However, the situation then developed in an unexpected way-? In the city surrounded by the skies and the seas, the romance story of I and she began. The brand new romantic comedy presented by the Sakurasou combo.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/seishun-buta-yarou-wa-bunny-girl-senpai-no-yume-o-minai-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="sabaku no harem" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Drama, Fantasy, Harem, Historical, Romance, Shoujo." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>sabaku no harem</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>sabaku-no-harem</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Yumeki Mitsuru</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/25716/3/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Mishe a strong willed girl raised from poverty has caught Prince Kallum's attention. Attention as in, "you will become one of my concubines", thus begins Mishe's adventures into Prince Kallum's world.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/sabaku-no-harem-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="danberu nan kiro moteru?" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Fantasy, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>danberu nan kiro moteru?</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>danberu-nan-kiro-moteru</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Sandrovich Yabako, Maam</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/43182/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Sakura Hibiki is your average High-school girl, with a voracious appetite. Noticing her clothes tightening in lieu of her slowly expanding waist line she decides to look into enrolling in the nearby Silverman-Gym. There she runs into a girl from her grade named Souryuuin Akemi, who is also the Student Council President at her school. Akemi, who has a muscle fetish tries to get Hibiki to enroll in the Gym despite its high ratio of Macho-Men (which Akemi dislikes). Thankfully a beautiful Trainer named Machio appears and unknowingly convinces her to enroll and start her quest to a great body.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/danberu-nan-kiro-moteru-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="reincarnation no kaben" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Fantasy, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>reincarnation no kaben</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>reincarnation-no-kaben</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Konishi Mikihisa</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/27742/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>You're mediocre and talentless... but have no fear! You can acquire the talent from your previous life THROUGH THE POWER OF PETALS!!!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/reincarnation-no-kaben-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="dekisokonai no monster trainer" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Comedy, Fantasy, Romance, School life, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>dekisokonai no monster trainer</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>dekisokonai-no-monster-trainer</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Minami Takumi, Yui</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/42684/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>In a world where everyone has a monster crest from birth, a select few rise to become Monster Trainers. Reyn Erhardt, a slime trainer, the lowest of the low, cares nothing for status and just continues his daily regimen of training for his personal slime, Pem-Pem. Yet in school dominated monsters as grand as dragons, those who cannot hope to rise to the top take out their frustrations on the lowest ones, and Reyn and Pem-Pem make for easy marks. Or do they?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/dekisokonai-no-monster-trainer-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="kushuku gakkou no alice" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Romance, School life, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>kushuku gakkou no alice</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>kushuku-gakkou-no-alice</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Kaneda Yousuke</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/32389/4/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>"To Love, or not to Love" Juliet Percia and Inudzuka Romeo are archenemies. They lead two high-school dormitories from to two rivalling countries. Both factions are dead set on defeating the other to gain control over the island they have to share. Beneath the feuding exterior, however, Percia and Inudzuka long for love and peace for their budding relationship...</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/kushuku-gakkou-no-alice-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="kenja no mago" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Comedy, Drama, Fantasy, Romance, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>kenja no mago</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>kenja-no-mago</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Yoshioka Tsuyoshi, Ogata Shunsuke</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/41420/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>A young man who had surely died in an accident, was reborn in another world as a baby! After that, he was picked up by the patriot hero "Sage" Merlin Wolford and was given the name Shin. He was raised as a grandson by Merlin and soaked up Merlin's teachings earning him some shocking power however, when he became 15 his grandfather Merlin said: "I forgot to teach him common sense".</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/kenja-no-mago-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="renai metro" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Josei, Mature, Romance, Shoujo., Slice of life, Smut" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>renai metro</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>renai-metro</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Yamaguchi Nene</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/36292/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Nozomi has been in love with her senpai for years. She tries to get into the same university as he to confess her feeling, only to find him in a relationship with another girl. To make matters worst, she's being pushed by a guy named Atsushi, the younger brother of the girlfriend of her unrequited love, to confess quickly so the couple would break up.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/renai-metro-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="gokukoku no brynhildr" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Comedy, Drama, Ecchi, Harem, Mature, Romance, School life, Sci-fi, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>gokukoku no brynhildr</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>gokukoku-no-brynhildr</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Okamoto Lynn</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/3185/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>When he was a child, Murakami was infatuated with a girl he called Kuroneko. She insisted on knowing about aliens and having met them, but no one believed her, even young Murakami was skeptical. One day, she decides to show him the aliens, but an accident occurs and Kuroneko dies while Murakami is left seriously wounded in the hospital. Years go by and Murakami obsesses on finding proof of the existence of aliens because of a promise he had made with Kuroneko. Then, one day, a new transfer student comes to his class, who not only looks a lot like Kuroneko but is named Kuroha Neko. And even though she insists on never having met Murakami before, the girl has superhuman strength and seems to even be able to predict the future! How will Murakami's life change now that he has been saved by this mysterious girl that claims to be a magician?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/gokukoku-no-brynhildr-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="isekai maou to shoukan shoujo dorei majutsu" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Comedy, Ecchi, Fantasy, Harem, Romance, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>isekai maou to shoukan shoujo dorei majutsu</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>isekai-maou-to-shoukan-shoujo-dorei-majutsu</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Murasaki Yukiya</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/34933/3/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>In regards to the MMORPG Cross Reverie, Sakamoto Takuma boasted an overwhelming strength that was enough for him to be called the Demon King by the other players. One day, he gets summoned to another world with his appearance in the game. There, there are two people that insist, "I am the real summon master." Takuma gets slave-turning magic used for summoned beasts cast on him by the girls - However, the peculiar ability {Magic Reflection} was invoked! The ones that were turned to slaves were the girls! Takuma was bewildered. He's the strongest magician but, he doesn't have any communication skills. Panicking, the first words that came out were the ones that he used inside the game role playing the Demon King!? "I'm amazing you say? Of course I am. I am Diablo... The one feared as the Demon King!" This is the story the Demon King (acting) that would soon inspire the world and his other world adventure that he plunges through with his absolute strength, raise the curtain!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/isekai-maou-to-shoukan-shoujo-dorei-majutsu-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="dungeon ni deai o motomeru no wa machigatte iru darou ka" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Comedy, Ecchi, Fantasy, Harem, Romance, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>dungeon ni deai o motomeru no wa machigatte iru darou ka</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>dungeon-ni-deai-o-motomeru-no-wa-machigatte-iru-darou-ka</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Oomori Fujino, Kunieda</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/23265/12/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Bell Cranel is just trying to find his way in the world. Of course, in his case, the "world" is an enormous dungeon filled with monsters below a city run by gods and goddesses with way too much time on their hands. He's got big dreams but not much more when a roll on the random encounter die brings him face-to-face with the girl of his dreams-but what's an amateur adventurer got to offer a brilliant swordswoman? And what if the lonely goddess who sponsors his solo adventuring gets jealous?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/dungeon-ni-deai-o-motomeru-no-wa-machigatte-iru-darou-ka-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="kuro hakushaku wa hoshi o mederu" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Fantasy, Romance, Shoujo." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>kuro hakushaku wa hoshi o mederu</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>kuro-hakushaku-wa-hoshi-o-mederu</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Oto Hisamu</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/28269/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>A Cinderella story with a twist! Esther Mayfield is a normal sixteen year old girl in 19th Century London. Except, ever since she was a little girl, she could see 'ghosts'. She lives in a small part of town and sells flowers to earn a living. She thought that she would continue to live like this forever. Until, one day, a handsome young Count appears in front of her. And he wants Esther to be his bride? Is he really the Prince Charming she has been waiting for?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/kuro-hakushaku-wa-hoshi-o-mederu-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="mob psycho 100" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Comedy, Psychological, School life, Shounen., Slice of life, Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>mob psycho 100</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>mob-psycho-100</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>One</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/24660/7/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Kageyama Shigeo (a.k.a. "Mob") is a 8th grader with psychic abilities. He could bend spoons and lift objects with his mind from a young age, but he slowly began to withhold from using his abilities in public due to the negative attention he kept receiving. Now, the only thing he wants is to become friends with a girl in his class, Tsubomi. With his psychic "mentor" (who has no psychic powers), he continues his daily life, attempting to realize his purpose in life.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/mob-psycho-100-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="12 beast" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Comedy, Drama, Ecchi, Fantasy, Harem, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>12 beast</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>12-beast</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Okayado</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/138/5/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Three things you should know about Touga Eita, second-year high school student and heir to the Touga-style ninjutsu dojo: First, he really, really loves video games. Second, when given a choice between heroics and saving his own skin, he will always choose the latter. Third, he's never so much as kissed a girl. All this changes when a voluptuous girl with wings and taloned feet named Aero appears and calls on Eita to help save her people-the harpies of Re-Verse-from the merciless onslaught of giant robot monsters known as Gigas. Eita will follow his newfound harpy friend into a whole new world, filled with monster girls and fantastical creatures beyond his wildest dreams.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/12-beast-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="sayounara ryuusei, konnichiwa jinsei" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy, Harem, Romance, Shounen., Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga - read from right to left">
		<ten_truyen>sayounara ryuusei, konnichiwa jinsei</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>sayounara-ryuusei-konnichiwa-jinsei</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Tomofuji Yuu</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/41503/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>The oldest and strongest Dragon grew tired of living choose to die when the Heroes come for his life. When the Dragon's soul is waiting to drift toward the Sea of Soul, that is when its noticed its has been reborn into a Human baby. The Dragon then decide to live it's life as a Human to the fullest, and regained his will to live. The Dragon was born into the child of a farmer lives his live in the frontier possessing enormous amount of power due to his soul being a Dragon's. He then encounter the Demon of the Lamia race, fairies, Black Rose, and later enter the Magic Academy. The man whose soul is of a Dragon lives his life in joy going to Magic Academy, spending time with an old friend, The Earth Goddess, meets beautiful girls, strong classmates, the Dragon King and the Queen of Vampires.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/sayounara-ryuusei-konnichiwa-jinsei-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
</danh_sach_truyen>