<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<danh_sach_truyen>
	<truyen ten="knight's and magic" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Comedy, Drama, Fantasy, Harem, Mecha, Romance, School life, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>knight's and magic</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>knight-s-and-magic</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Amazake No Hisago, Katou Takuji, Kurogin</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/43546/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>A mecha otaku is reincarnated into another world as Ernesti Echevalier (Eru). In this world, exist huge humanoid weapon known as Silhouette Knight. Dreaming of piloting those robots, Eru, with childhood friends, Archid and Adeltrud Olter: together they will aim to become Knight Runner, pilot of Silhoutte Knight.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/knight-s-and-magic-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="gal gohan" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Romance, School life" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>gal gohan</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>gal-gohan</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Taiyou Marii</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/46625/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Home Economics Teacher, Shinji Yabe, is asked by the biggest gyaru in school, Miku Okazaki, to help her 'bake cookies to give to the teachers'. The principal told her to do this, after she flunked every subject and makeup-class they put her in. He gets her to successfully finish a batch of cookies after several mishaps and is touched by his students glee over her success. He decides to start a cooking club after this experience to get more time and connection with his students. Upon hearing this, Miku decides to join, since he was the first teacher that didn't shove her into makeup-lessons after her failings and pushed her to try harder instead.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/gal-gohan-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="area no kishi" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Drama, School life, Shounen., Sports, Tragedy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>area no kishi</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>area-no-kishi</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Igano Hiroaki, Tsukiyama Kaya</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/841/9/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Believing himself to be useless at football, Aizawa Kakeru opts to become the manager of his school's football team, while his brother Suguru is its ace, and is even good enough to represent Japan. However, Kakeru may be harbouring a strong talent within himself that only Suguru can see, and the two often get into arguments over Kakeru's denial of his skills. Things are made more complicated with the return of Seven, an old playmate of theirs that Kakeru has a crush on. Join the brothers in their journey to the national and even international championships!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/area-no-kishi-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="mr. and mrs. x" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>mr. and mrs. x</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>mr-and-mrs-x</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Kelly Thompson, Oscar Bazaldua</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/m/mr-and-mrs-x/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Straight from the pages of X-MEN GOLD... to the surprise of everyone, the Marvel Universe's hottest couple has finally tied the knot! In their extraordinary lives, they've faced nearly every challenge imaginable, but how will they fare against former flames making trouble? An entire galaxy in jeopardy? You want it? We got it, as Kelly Thompson (HAWKEYE, ROGUE and GAMBIT) and Oscar Bazaldua (SPIDER-MAN, STAR WARS: ROGUE ONE) bring you the tantalizing tale of a modern marriage... X-MEN STYLE!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/mr-and-mrs-x-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="the silencer" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>the silencer</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>the-silencer</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Dan Abnett, John Romita Jr., Sandra Hope</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/the-silencer/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>She's one of the DC Universe's deadliest assassins... and you've never heard of her. Super-strong, highly trained, armed with devastating and stealthy meta-human abilities, the Silencer is virtually invincible. Or at least she was. After decades as Leviathan's chief assassin, Honor Guest put in her time and managed to get out with her skin intact. Now she lives a normal life with a normal family in a normal house on a normal street. But the past has come back to haunt her in the form of her old employer and a deadly new mission... and Talia Al Ghul won't take no for an answer.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/the-silencer-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="the punisher (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>the punisher (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>the-punisher-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Matt Rosenberg, Szymon Kudranski</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/p/punisher-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>YOU CAN TAKE THE PUNISHER OUT OF THE WAR MACHINE... Punisher no longer has the War Machine armor, but he retained his newly acquired taste for big game, and he's hungry for more. However, the paths to such perilous pursuits are fraught with dangers bigger than any Frank has faced before, and this lone wolf could use otherworldly help on his way up to the world stage.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/the-punisher-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="eden's zero" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy, Martial arts, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>eden's zero</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>eden-s-zero</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Mashima Hiro</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-comic-5.anyacg.co/thumbs/w300/f3/af/f3af94f522f852c642881025fee569fb31bee89b_29037_225_334.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>The amusement park planet of Granbell Kingdom has been abandoned for 100 years. Rebecca and her talking cat Happy are the first visitors in years, causing excitement among the robot inhabitants. However, Rebecca soon discovers that she's not the only human in the park! Shiki has lived on Granbell for most of his life after being taken in by the Demon King robot, who became his grandfather-figure. Now he does repairs for the robots in the park. But the robots then strangely turn against Shiki to force him to leave the planet with Rebecca in order to fulfill their promise to the Demon King, who knew Shiki was destined for greatness. With the ancient powers of Ether Gear, Shiki begins his journey into space, where dragons roam the stars!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/eden-s-zero-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="tsuki ga michibiku isekai douchuu" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Comedy, Fantasy, Harem, Romance, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>tsuki ga michibiku isekai douchuu</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>tsuki-ga-michibiku-isekai-douchuu</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Azumi Kei, Kino Kotora</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/35174/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>High school student Misumi Makoto is called into a fantasy world by the god Tsukuyomi, in order to be a hero. However, powerful others in this world aren't as thrilled to have him there, and they kick him to the edge of the world just as Tsukuyomi declares that he must leave Makoto to find his own way. Now it's up to Makoto to find his own way!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/tsuki-ga-michibiku-isekai-douchuu-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="billy bat" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Ecchi, Romance, School life, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>billy bat</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>billy-bat</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Nekoguchi</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/6/65/Billy_bat_first_cover.jpg/220px-Billy_bat_first_cover.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Billy Bat is a comic-in-a-comic and the real protagonist is a Japanese-American artist named Kevin Yamagata who draws Billy Bat for 'Marble Comics'. Shortly after they transition to the artist in his studio with his assistant, two actual detectives, who look like Laurel and Hardy in Dick Tracy era suits and trench coats, knock on the door and appropriate Kevin's room for the purpose of conducting surveillance on a room in an adjacent building. One of the detectives, the skinny 'Laurel', sees Kevin's work and it turns out he's a Billy Bat fan. The other chubby 'Hardy' detective picks up a page and says that the characters look familiar and accuses Kevin of translating an old 'Jap' comic. As Hardy remembers the comic he thinks Kevin is ripping off, we make another Urasawaesque time jump to 1949 Tokyo. Billy Bat won the Max und Moritz Prize for 'Best international Comic' in 2014.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/billy-bat-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="injustice vs. masters of the universe" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>injustice vs. masters of the universe</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>injustice-vs-masters-of-the-universe</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Tim Seeley, Freddie E. Williams II, Jeremy Colwell</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/i/injustice-vs-masters-of-the-universe/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Believing He-man and the Masters of the Universe defeated, a robotic impostor has seized control of Eternia-but not for long! After freeing his kingdom from this strongman's rule, Prince Adam learns not everyone is pleased to see the pretender deposed-but Adam knows the value of freedom. So when heroes from another dimension ask his aid in deposing a super-hero turned dictator, he agrees. Teaming up with Batman against the Superman of the Injustice Universe, He-man and his new allies face dangerous and familiar enemies in a battle where no world is safe!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/injustice-vs-masters-of-the-universe-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="multiple man" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>multiple man</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>multiple-man</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Matthew Rosenburg, Andy MacDonald</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/m/multiple-man-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>MATTHEW ROSENBERG and ANDY MACDONALD BRING MULTIPLE MAN BACK FROM THE DEAD...SORT OF...MAYBE? A handful of people's favorite X-Man - Jamie Madrox - was alive for a while. Then he was dead. Now he's not. But he will be again if he doesn't kill himself trying to make sure he doesn't die. It makes sense when you read it. Trust us. In his fight to not die, Jamie has stumbled across a threat even greater than his own death, but fixing it might make it worse. Can he save the world from himself? On top of all that, the X-Men are mad at him now, and a mysterious new group of foes is after him, too. We can't tell you who they are, but they're pretty great.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/multiple-man-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="revenge of wonderland" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy, Leading ladies" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>revenge of wonderland</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>revenge-of-wonderland</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Joe Brusha, Ralph Tedesco, Dave Franchini, Raven Gregory, Allan Otero, Grostieta</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/r/revenge-of-wonderland/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The realm of madness is back with a brand new twisted tale of love, loss and vengeance! It's been a long time since Alice Liddle's daughter, Calie, finally escaped the twisted world that her mother was pulled into many years before her. But the insanity of Wonderland has returned and this time around things are much more dangerous and horrifying than ever before. Originally the realm of dreams, but now a realm made up of nightmares, Wonderland has been purged of its original denizens and a new ruler has emerged. The Duchess has been kidnapping people from this world and re-shaping them in her image to use as her personal playthings. Can Calie and her daughter team up to stop a new madness from emerging from Wonderland and invading our world or is it too late to stop the inevitable? Find out here is this insane first issue of a whole new Wonderland!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/revenge-of-wonderland-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="amano megumi wa suki darake!" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Ecchi, Romance, School life, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>amano megumi wa suki darake!</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>amano-megumi-wa-suki-darake</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Nekoguchi</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/40038/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Shindo Manabu is a student in a very prestigious high school who's goal is to get into Tokyo University. He studies constantly and tries to never lose sight of that goal. That is until his childhood friend , Amano Megumi, who goes to the same school starts to distract him. He only saw her as the tom-boy she was as a kid until they meet up again when she has become 'more developed'. As those two get closer to each other Manabu gets more and more distracted from his goal of getting into Tokyo U, so hilarity ensues.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/amano-megumi-wa-suki-darake-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="nozoki ana" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Adventure, Comedy, Ecchi, Fantasy, Harem, Mature, Romance, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>nozoki ana</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>nozoki-ana</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Seta Aomaru</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/7144/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Whilst searching for porn on the internet Sudo Kansuke, a 20-year-old university student, gets sucked into an RPG world called Munberdia. He is the chosen hero who carries the sword of light. Only the sword of light is not what you would expect.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/nozoki-ana-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="only sense online" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Comedy, Fantasy, Gender bender, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>only sense online</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>only-sense-online</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Aloha Zachou, Hani Kuraun</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/38819/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Utilizing a system called 'Sense,' each player aims to create their unique character in the VRMMORPG 'Only Sense Online.' Joining this realm is Yun, an absolute beginner in the world of gaming, equipped with some of the worst customized 'Sense' ever. While his two sisters, both veterans in this world, criticize his choices of equipment, he continues to delve into the skill sets he has acquired. Along his way, he meets the art of 'production' and people that have mastered this art. Watch as a total novice creates a revolution in the gaming world and create the 'ultimate' support class.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/only-sense-online-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="master in my dreams" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Mature, School life, Supernatural, Webtoons" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manhwa">
		<ten_truyen>master in my dreams</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>master-in-my-dreams</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Son Hwi-joon</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/35624/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>If your desire for a girl were fulfilled would you accept or refuse? Even though it's a dream...</gioi_thieu>
		<file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manhwa_Ongoing/master-in-my-dreams-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="googookaka" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Josei, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manhwa">
		<ten_truyen>googookaka</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>googookaka</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Haeni</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/43331/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>The struggle bus life of the hot Cheongdam girl Ina who got transported to the primitive era...</gioi_thieu>
		<file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manhwa_Ongoing/googookaka-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="tong" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Drama, Martial arts, Shounen., Webtoons" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manhwa">
		<ten_truyen>tong</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>tong</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Min, Baek Seung Hoon</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/43523/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Having lived as a fighting legend in Busan, he wanted to live peacefully in Seoul. However, we all know that wasn't how Lee Jung Woo lived. Showing off immense skills in the fight against the best fighters in the school, Lee Jung Woo takes over the area in no time at all. After that, the gangs nearby never leave the 'Tong' Lee Jung Woo alone. Although he is the 'Tong', since Lee Jung Woo did not wish to being harm to those not involved, he starts changing the way he lives. What exactly was Lee Jung Woo trying to protect through all that violence?</gioi_thieu>
		<file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manhwa_Ongoing/tong-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="wu dao kuang zhi shi" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Drama, Historical, Martial arts, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manhua">
		<ten_truyen>wu dao kuang zhi shi</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>wu-dao-kuang-zhi-shi</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Qiao Jingfu, Meng Ma Gong Zuo Shi</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
		<hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/27171/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>The story begins with an eradication of Qingcheng by a group of martial art fanatic from Wudong, whose master and disciples only has one belief - to become the strongest. In order to maintain the supremacy, it takes over all the other martial arts group and kill those refuse to yield themselves to it. Yan Heng, a young swordman in Qingcheng, was saved by 'Wudang Hunter' Jing Lie, who also lost his fellows because of Wudong. Being the only remnant of their groups, the two allied and start their journey of revenge.</gioi_thieu>
		<file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manhua_Ongoing/wu-dao-kuang-zhi-shi-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="the great conqueror" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Comedy, Drama, Fantasy, Martial arts, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manhua">
		<ten_truyen>the great conqueror</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>the-great-conqueror</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Skeleton Fairy, Sun Xi</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
		<hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/34336/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>A combat-game loving neet. full of hope, arrives in world ruled by the beast race. A story of a Different world, the same passion, one small step at a time, an unimportant person becomes the great conqueror. Moving, Explosive, Bloody forever!</gioi_thieu>
		<file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manhua_Ongoing/the-great-conqueror-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="lan chi" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Drama, Romance, School life, Shoujo." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manhua">
		<ten_truyen>lan chi</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>lan-chi</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Xu Lu Ako</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
		<hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/30661/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Ming Lan was adopted into a new family, but her foster mother Nan Xi treated her as a replacement for her dead daughter. However, her two new brothers, Ming Qing and Ming Jing did not welcome her. Ming Lan's quiet life under this new roof was disturbed by pranks and false smiles...</gioi_thieu>
		<file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manhua_Ongoing/lan-chi-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="fantastic four (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>fantastic four (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>fantastic-four-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Dan Slott, Simone Bianchi, Sara Pichelli, Elisabetta D'Amico, Skottie Young</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/f/fantastic-four-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Since the end of SECRET WARS, there's been a gap in the Marvel Universe. A void no other team can fill. And it's time for the world to move on. But can it? A life-changing decision by the Thing! A momentous declaration by the Human Torch! A clarion call-to-arms that summons Doctor Doom! And a signal in the sky that heralds the return of hope to the Marvel Universe! All this, and Alicia Masters adopts kittens! So cute! Plus, the Impossible Man!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/fantastic-four-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="catwoman (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>catwoman (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>catwoman-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Joelle Jones</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/c/catwoman-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The wedding night's barely over, but Catwoman's back on the streets, this time to expose a copycat who's pulling heists around Gotham City. As Selina cracks the whip on her former criminal cohorts, she's attracting unwanted attention from one of Gotham's most dangerous groups. The mob? Nope. Try the GCPD. And as if the Bat-Bride didn't have enough problems, don't miss the debut of an all-new villain determined to make trouble for all nine of Selina's lives.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/catwoman-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="predator: hunters ii" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>predator: hunters ii</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>predator-hunters-ii</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Chris Warner, Neeraj Menon, Agustin Padilla</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/p/predator-hunters-ii/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>From the islands of the South Pacific to the mountains of Afghanistan, the Hunters go wherever the Predators appear--even if it's in a war zone and into conflict with a mysterious government group hunting the same prey! Despite the casualties suffered during their first mission, the Predator Hunters are on the prowl again!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/predator-hunters-ii-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="blade play" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Adventure, Comedy, Ecchi, Fantasy, Harem, Mature, Romance, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>blade play</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>blade-play</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Seta Aomaru</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/1249/3/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Whilst searching for porn on the internet Sudo Kansuke, a 20-year-old university student, gets sucked into an RPG world called Munberdia. He is the chosen hero who carries the sword of light. Only the sword of light is not what you would expect.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/blade-play-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="ss sisters" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Adult, Comedy, Ecchi, Mature, Romance, School life, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>ss sisters</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>ss-sisters</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Ditama Bow</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/9458/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>This story is about a (un)lucky guy who gets sadistically and sexually tortured in unconventional ways.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/ss-sisters-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="black bird" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Comedy, Drama, Fantasy, Harem, Mystery, Romance, School life, Shoujo., Smut, Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>black bird</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>black-bird</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Sakurakouji Kanoko</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/1224/3/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>There is a world of myth and magic that intersects ours, and only a special few can see it. Misao Harada is one such person, and she wants nothing to do with magical realms. She just wants to have a normal high school life and maybe get a boyfriend. But she is the bride of demon prophecy, and her blood grants incredible powers, her flesh immortality. Now the demon realm is fighting over the right to her hand...or her life! Black Bird received the 2009 Shogakukan Manga Award for shoujo manga.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/black-bird-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="captain america (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>captain america (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>captain-america-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Ta-Nehisi Coates, Leinil Francis Yu, Gerry Alanguilan, Sunny Gho</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/c/captain-america-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>IT IS WINTER IN AMERICA.For over 70 years, he has stood in stalwart defense of our country and its people. But in the aftermath of Hydra's takeover of the nation, Captain America is a figure of controversy, carrying a tarnished shield...and a new enemy is rising! Who are the Power Elite? And how do they intend to co-opt and corrupt the symbol that is Captain America?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/captain-america-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="portal bound" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>portal bound</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>portal-bound</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Gabe Carrasco, Mark Roslan, Alex Arizmendi, Wes Hartman, Adam Archer</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/p/portal-bound/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Their Future Depends on Each Other. A parallel otherworld exists as a mirror to our own, where science is melded with nature and a warrior spirit defines their true value. A teenage soldier princess, Sybil, is sent off with her Uncle Horuk in an effort to stop her megalomaniac father, Emperor Atilus from destroying two Earths. With a deadly array of monstrous creatures in hot pursuit, Sybil and her uncle race to activate a portal to Earth to find a savior who is also figuring out how to survive... being a teenager!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/portal-bound-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="fissure" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Drama, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>fissure</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>fissure</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Tim Daniel, Patricio Delpeche</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/f/fissure/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>El Sueno, Texas was a single street town withering under the shadow of the Mexico-U.S. Barrier. Then the pavement split, and a massive crack spread from one end to the other, rapidly swallowing El Sueno whole. Young couple Avery Lee Olmos and Hark Wright fight to escape the mysterious sinkhole and the malevolent force that beckons from its depths.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/fissure-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="koi wo suru no ga shigoto desu" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Adult, Comedy, Ecchi, Mature, Romance, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>koi wo suru no ga shigoto desu</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>koi-wo-suru-no-ga-shigoto-desu</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Harumi Chihiro</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/5300/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Two lovebirds, Hatsuhi Ryou and Sawamura Minori, are both finally venturing out into the workplace together. Each landing a job at their own desired company. However, they quickly find out that they work for rival companies. And each company forbids their employees from associating with their rival's workers. Will they lose their jobs, or can they keep their relationship a secret?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/koi-wo-suru-no-ga-shigoto-desu-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="crayon days - daikirai na aitsu" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Romance, School life, Shoujo." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>crayon days - daikirai na aitsu</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>crayon-days-daikirai-na-aitsu</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Chiba Kozue</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/1958/3/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Because she loved drawing and wanted to do something special, she went to a famous art school. And there she met the handsome and cool guy...</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/crayon-days-daikirai-na-aitsu-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="kiss x sis" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Ecchi, Harem, Mature, Romance, School life, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>kiss x sis</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>kiss-x-sis</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Ditama Bow</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/5162/4/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Keita has two older (not blood-related) twin step-sisters who love him in a lustful way and have no problems expressing it. They even like to compete about it; much to the laughter of his friends (which he usually endures without problems). One day they come to his school to give him his lunch, resulting in him getting angry due to the atmosphere. To counteract his anger, they confess their tender feelings for him in front of everyone and leave. Feeling sorry he chases after them and says that he'll study hard in order to get in the same high school as them.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/kiss-x-sis-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="infinity wars  " tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>infinity wars  </ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>infinity-wars</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Gerry Duggan, Mike Deodato Jr.</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/i/infinity-wars-prime/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>As the Infinity Stones come to Earth, so too comes the war for control over them. But none who wield the stones know the truth about the power they contain...or what it would take to bring them to their END. The nature of the universe itself hangs in the balance as we learn the answer to the question on everyone's lips since 'Infinity Wars Prime': WHO IS REQUIEM?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/infinity-wars-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="adventures of the super sons" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>adventures of the super sons</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>adventures-of-the-super-sons</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Peter J. Tomasi, Carlo Barberi</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/a/adventures-of-the-super-sons/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The Super Sons are back in an all-new 12-issue miniseries written by Peter J. Tomasi! Check out the lost and secret adventures of Damian Wayne (Robin) and Jon Kent (Superboy) in this flashback miniseries that takes a deep dive into the bombastic bromance between the sons of the DC Universe's greatest heroes. It's an epic dual storyline that transcends current events, as Superboy and Robin find themselves targets of an interstellar team of young badasses called the Gang.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/adventures-of-the-super-sons-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="death of the inhumans" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>death of the inhumans</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>death-of-the-inhumans</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Donny Cates, Ariel Olivetti, Jordie Bellaire</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/death-of-the-inhumans/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>THE TITLE SAYS IT ALL - HERE LIE THE INHUMANS. The Kree have gone murdering, leaving behind a message: Join or die. Thousands of Inhumans have already made their choice - the evidence floats bleeding in space. Black Bolt and his family are next. Rising star Donny Cates and PUNISHER: WAR JOURNAL artist Ariel Olivetti bring their brutal talents to the Inhumans!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/death-of-the-inhumans-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="ubel blatt" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adult, Adventure, Fantasy, Mature, Seinen, Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>ubel blatt</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>ubel-blatt</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Shiono Etorouji</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/10628/7/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>When the black blade roars, all who stand in its path shall be torn asunder...! What is it that Koinzell, the mysterious young boy who wields the sword with such exceptional skill, desires? The fight against the 'Lances of Betrayal,' who were thought to have been defeated by the Seven Heroes, begins--And at battle's end, only the shocking truth will remain amid the pools of blood.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/ubel-blatt-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="aki-sora" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Drama, Ecchi, Gender bender, Harem, Mature, Romance, School life, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>aki-sora</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>aki-sora</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Itosugi Masahiro</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/508/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Aki Sora revolves around Aki Aoi and Sora Aoi, a pair of close siblings who have shared an intimate bond since childhood. During their coming of age, they each come to realize the true depth of the love they feel for each other and consummate that love in secret. They keep their younger sister, Nami, Sora's twin in the dark about their new relationship. Nami, clueless of what is happening in her household aims to set her brother up with her best friend, Kana Sumiya. Despite these relationships Nami seems to have feelings for someone near to her too but keeps them secret.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/aki-sora-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="apocalypse no toride" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Drama, Horror, Mystery, Psychological, Sci-fi, Shounen., Tragedy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>apocalypse no toride</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>apocalypse-no-toride</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Kuraishi Yuu, Inabe Kazu</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/6/5/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>What can you do when you get mistaken for murder? Nothing. You go to prison. Lucky you, your inmates are some of the biggest cutthroats in the prison. Seriously you are lucky. Expecially when zombies attack.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/apocalypse-no-toride-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="amentia" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Drama, Ecchi, Harem, Psychological, Romance, School life, Seinen, Supernatural, Webtoons" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manhwa">
		<ten_truyen>amentia</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>amentia</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Yang Hyeseok, Bak Hyein</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/38364/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Lee Wee-jin normally endures each of his his high school days as a servant his perfect sister Lee Wi-na. However, he has a secret he can't share with anyone-that he can materialize his delusions as he pleases. When he needs to relieve stress caused by his sister, he materializes a version of his own sister in order to punish her. But one day a black-haired transfer student says the following to Wee-jin while wielding a knife against him: 'You damn delusioner that materializes delusions, we wakers will get rid of all of you!'</gioi_thieu>
		<file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manhwa_Ongoing/amentia-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="inarime" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Fantasy, Webtoons" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manhwa">
		<ten_truyen>inarime</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>inarime</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Maria Ricco, Tommaso Bennato</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/41312/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Ancient Gods and new battles; the unborn Typhon's seventh daughter and her incredible adventures trying to understand who she is and why the Gods of Olympus are so hostile toward human beings. Warn you to believe at who says that they're just 'myths', they are more real than what you think, and they are among us.</gioi_thieu>
		<file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manhwa_Ongoing/inarime-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="balls friend" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Romance, Seinen, Slice of life, Webtoons" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manhwa">
		<ten_truyen>balls friend</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>balls-friend</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Hanla Gamgyul</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/42756/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>The protagonist is sucked in to a weird whirlpool in a river and somehow ends up in a island in another world with native elves that wear leaf clothes, have the knowledge of an new born, and have sex like rabbits. That also have a body as weak as butter. He decides to become the king of the place and rule with an iron fist and teach the naive elves cruelty, evil and watch as they kill each other.</gioi_thieu>
		<file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manhwa_Ongoing/balls-friend-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="feng qi cang lan" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Fantasy, Romance, Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manhua">
		<ten_truyen>feng qi cang lan</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>feng-qi-cang-lan</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Gu Xuan, Song Shu 200</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
		<hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/42847/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>When playing a virtual reality game called Cang Lan, Xiao Wan gets pushed off a cliff. She ends up in another game world. What will happen to Xiao Wan?</gioi_thieu>
		<file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manhua_Ongoing/feng-qi-cang-lan-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="ling bao zhi" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Horror, Romance, Shounen., Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manhua">
		<ten_truyen>ling bao zhi</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>ling-bao-zhi</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Ye Gu, Fep-xiao Zhao</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
		<hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/30168/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Due to all of the anger and emotions of humans, the world has been inhabited by ghosts that feed off humans. Unfortunately, these ghosts can't be seen by ordinary humans. A high schooler has the ability to see these ghosts...</gioi_thieu>
		<file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manhua_Ongoing/ling-bao-zhi-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="i don't want to say i'm a chicken" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Comedy, Fantasy, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manhua">
		<ten_truyen>i don't want to say i'm a chicken</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>i-don-t-want-to-say-i-m-a-chicken</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Jiang Ren</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
		<hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/34853/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>When the maid from the heaven failed to protect the Phoenix egg from a mysterious figure, she used her last power to send the Phoenix, king of all birds into a chicken egg and soon the Phoenix hatched into a chicken. Follow the Phoenix and his chicken sibling on an epic adventure!</gioi_thieu>
		<file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manhua_Ongoing/i-don-t-want-to-say-i-m-a-chicken-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
</danh_sach_truyen>