<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<danh_sach_truyen>
	<truyen ten="exlibrium" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>exlibrium</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>exlibrium</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Natalia Devova, Denis Popov, Andrey Rodin</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/e/exlibrium/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>...And the door will open. 'Exlibrium' (from the Latin 'ex libris', 'of the books' and 'equilibrium', 'balance') - a magic seal that helps the mysterious order of sorcerers to guard the border between the real world and the world of fiction. For many centuries members of the order have been successfully preventing creatures from the works of art and lliterature from escaping into our world. But sometimes the order fails to do so and some of those characters manage to break the walls between realities...</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/exlibrium-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="dark ark" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Horror" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>dark ark</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>dark ark</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Cullen Bunn, Juan Doe, Ryane Hill</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/dark-ark/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The wickedness of mankind has moved the Creator to destroy the world by way of the flood. Noah has been tasked with building an ark to save his family and the animals of the world. But this is not Noah's story. For darker powers have commanded the sorcerer Shrae to build his own ark and save the unnatural creatures of the world-such as the vampires, the dragons, the naga, and the manticore. But what will happen on a vessel crawling with monsters, where insidious intrigue and horrific violence are the rule of law?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/dark-ark-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="throwaways" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Crime, Life sucks" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>throwaways</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>throwaways</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Caitlin Kittredge, Maiko Kuzunishi</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/throwaways/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Abby Palmer and Dean Logan are two broken people-Abby a vet with severe PTSD and Dean a burnout trying to escape the shadow of his infamous father-when they are thrust into a modern-day MK-ULTRA conspiracy... and discover they are both ULTRA's human experiments.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/throwaways-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="incognegro: renaissance" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Crime, Literature" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>incognegro: renaissance</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>incognegro-renaissance</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Mat Johnson, Warren Pleece</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/i/incognegro-renaissance/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>After a black writer is found dead at a scandalous interracial party in 1920s New York, Harlem's cub reporter Zane Pinchback is the only one determined to solve the murder. Zane must go 'incognegro' for the first time--using his light appearance to pass as a white man--to find the true killer, in this prequel miniseries to the critically acclaimed Vertigo graphic novel, now available in a special new 10th Anniversary Edition. With a cryptic manuscript as his only clue, and a mysterious and beautiful woman as the murder's only witness, Zane finds himself on the hunt through the dark and dangerous streets of 'roaring twenties' Harlem in search for justice. A page-turning thriller of racial divide, Incognegro: Renaissance explores segregation, secrets, and self-image as our race-bending protagonist penetrates a world where he feels stranger than ever before.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Completed/incognegro-renaissance-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="konjiki no moji tsukai - yuusha yonin ni makikomareta unique cheat" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Comedy, Fantasy, Harem, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>konjiki no moji tsukai - yuusha yonin ni makikomareta unique cheat</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>konjiki-no-moji-tsukai-yuusha-yonin-ni-makikomareta-unique-cheat</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Tomoto Sui, Ozaki Yuusuke</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/29695/4/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>There has been much conflict between the races of the 'Humas', the 'Gabranth', and the 'Evila'. To combat the 'Evila' race's Demon King, the kingdom summons five high school students from 21st century Japan who have the power of Heroes. However, only four out of five of those students had the status title of 'Hero'. Okamura Hiiro was summoned by accident since he sat near the other four students in class. Unlike them, he did not have the title of a 'Hero' but instead he had the title of 'Word Master' and 'Innocent Bystander'. Seeing through the 'Humas' kingdom's deceit and insanity, Hiiro decides that he has no wish to partake in their selfish war. Leaving the castle, Hiiro decides to join the Adventurer's Guild and does whatever he feels like. Who knows? Maybe there is some merit to being a 'Word Master' and an 'Innocent Bystander'.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/konjiki-no-moji-tsukai-yuusha-yonin-ni-makikomareta-unique-cheat-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="gleipnir" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Ecchi, Fantasy, Romance, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>gleipnir</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>gleipnir</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Takeda Sun</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/36253/3/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Shuichi Kagaya isn't human. He has an unnatural sense of smell, and can transform into an incredibly powerful beast... of sorts. He does all he can to avoid standing out and being discovered, but no good deed goes unpunished, and his decision to use his power to save a girl spells the end for his quiet life.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/gleipnir-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="megami no libra" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Romance, Shoujo." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>megami no libra</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>megami-no-libra</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Sakou Watari</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/28214/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Yuuki Tsumire was raised by her single mother, who always told her to keep smiling, no matter what hardships she endured. The two of them were a family, until Tsumire's mother died from illness. Tsumire soon learned that she had a family she knew nothing about: a cold, rich family that disowned her kindhearted mother when she became pregnant. Tsumire now must go live with this family, even though none of them seem to want her there. She doesn't have to switch schools, so she at least has her friends to help her through this difficult time. However, she doesn't have the heart to confide in her friends with even more problems, so she tries to keep it bottled up inside. To her surprise, the Yuuki family lawyer, a young man named Hino, soon becomes her emotional support in this difficult situation. However, Tsumire's reactions to him might mean that she wishes he were something more... Thanks go to tethysdust for the summary.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/megami-no-libra-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="star trek: discovery: succession" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Movies - tv, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>star trek: discovery: succession</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>star-trek-discovery-succession</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Kirsten Beyer, Mike Johnston, Angel Hernandez</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/s/star-trek-discovery-succession/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>In this, the second Discovery miniseries from IDW Publishing, your favorite characters from the hit CBS All Access series dive into an adventure tied directly into the second half of the first season!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/star-trek-discovery-succession-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="ghostbusters: crossing over" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Horror, Movies - tv, Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>ghostbusters: crossing over</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>ghostbusters-crossing-over</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Erik Burnham, Dan Schoening</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/g/ghostbusters-crossing-over/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>For a while now, the original Ghostbusters have had access to an interdimensional portal that has given them all-new ways to research the paranormal and consult with Ghostbusters throughout the multiverse... but they haven't shared this tech with any of those other Ghostbusters, and some don't think that's fair. That's why, after a chance meeting, Jillian Holtzmann and Ron Alexander have decided to right this wrong and cobble together their own working portal... which unintentionally unleashes the contents of the Ghostbusters' Containment Unit! That's a lot of ghosts, and it's going to take a lot of Ghostbusters to recapture them. In fact, it's going to take ALL of them. Crossing Over starts here!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/ghostbusters-crossing-over-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="paradiso" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Mystery" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>paradiso</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>paradiso</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Ram V, Dearbhla Kelly, Dev Pramanik, Christian Ward</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/p/paradiso/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The Midnight Event forever changed the world. Now, centuries later, Jack Kryznan arrives on the outskirts of Paradiso City, haunted by fragments of childhood memories and in possession of a mysterious device one with the power to change the destiny of this living breathing metropolis, the people who dwell within, and the guardians who strive for and against it.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/paradiso-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="prism stalker" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>prism stalker</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>prism-stalker</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Sloane Long, Darius Ou</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/p/prism-stalker/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>For fans of Octavia Butler, Sailor Moon, and the biopunk horror of David Cronenberg comes PRISM STALKER, an ongoing sci-fi adventure series by SLOANE LEONG. Vep is a young refugee raised away from her devastated home planet as an indentured citizen in a foreign colony. She works tirelessly for her insectoid hosts, but there is no exit in sight in this viscous, dripping citynest. The eye of opportunity is closing. Her duty is to her family and her siblings, but what more can she do for them here? The answer appears faster than she is ready for.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/prism-stalker-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="the last siege" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Crime, Fantasy, Martial arts" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>the last siege</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>the-last-siege</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Landry Q. Walker, Justin Greenwood, Nick Dragotta</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/the-last-siege/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>A tale of blood, desperation, and loss. New York Times bestselling author LANDRY Q. WALKER joins artist JUSTIN GREENWOOD for an all-new ONGOING SERIES-THE LAST SIEGE! Spaghetti Western storytelling meets Game of Thrones atmosphere in this gritty medieval war story, as a mysterious stranger arrives at a castle overrun with brutal soldiers bent on usurping the throne of the rightful heir-an 11-year-old girl. An action-packed, genre-twisting epic, THE LAST SIEGE begins!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/the-last-siege-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="hillbilly" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy, Mythology, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>hillbilly</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>hillbilly</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Eric Powell</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/h/hillbilly/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>An Appalachian Mountain fantasy epic that tells the story of Rondel. A lonely figure who wanders the wooded hills among witches and magical creatures as a folktale hero to those who dwell in this gritty dream world.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/hillbilly-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="jirni (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>jirni (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>jirni-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>J.T. Krul, Michael Santamaria, John Starr</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/j/jirni-vol-3/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Aspen's popular fantasy adventure series, JIRNI, returns for an epic third volume! As Ara's quest to find her kidnapped mother continues, she finds solace in a remote village, but do they have their own demons to worry about? Meanwhile, Torinthal continues on his own search to unlock the mysteries of the D'jinn and their celestial origin. Don't miss out on the biggest quest for Ara yet! Created by New York Times Best-Selling author J.T. Krul (Michael Turner's Soulfire, Green Arrow) with art by newcomer Michael Santamaria, this next exciting chapter of Jirni will once again return readers to a land of untapped wonder!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/jirni-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="isola" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>isola</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>isola</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Brenden Fletcher, Karl Kerschl, MSASSYK</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/i/isola/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Childhood friends BRENDEN FLETCHER (MOTOR CRUSH) and Eisner Award-winning storyteller KARL KERSCHL (Gotham Academy) reunite on the comics page with a breathtaking fantasy adventure two decades in the making! The captain of the Royal Guard has fled the capital city with the Queen of Maar, suffering under the effects of an evil spell. Captain Rook's only hope of returning Queen Olwyn to her throne and saving the kingdom from impending war lies on an island half a world away-a place known in myth as Isola, land of the dead. Featuring lush color work by MSASSYK (Gotham Academy) and letters by ADITYA BIDIKAR (MOTOR CRUSH). Recommended for fans of Studio Ghibli and the work of Hayao Miyazaki.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/isola-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="die!die!die!" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Horror, Suspense" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>die!die!die!</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>diediedie</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Chris Burnham, Robert Kirkman, Scott Gimple</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/diediedie/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Blood will flow, Bullets will fly and the mayhem will never end, Die!Die!Die! brings all the action you could ever want.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/diediedie-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="getter robot devolution - uchuu saigo no 3-bunkan" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Mecha, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>getter robot devolution - uchuu saigo no 3-bunkan</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>getter-robot-devolution-uchuu-saigo-no-3-bunkan</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Ishikawa Ken, Shimizu Eiichi, Shimoguchi Tomohiro</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/38781/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Three young pilots connected by the Getter Rays (Ryoma Nagare, Hayato Jin, and Musashi Tomoe) are recruited by Dr. Saotome to fight the Devolved beings appearing from spatial distortions using the only weapon that can face these monsters, the Getter Robo. The Saotome Institute however holds a dangerous secret, a fragment of the being called Emperor which connects the Getter and its pilots to parallel worlds, including the presence of people from those worlds such as an older Hayato and Dr. Shikishima.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/getter-robot-devolution-uchuu-saigo-no-3-bunkan-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="rain  " tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Drama, Fantasy, Romance, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>rain  </ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>rain</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Yoshino Takumi, Sumikawa Megumi</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>http://www.mangadeep.com/wp-content/manga/cover/tbn/rain_200x0.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>The small country Sunkwoll is in a tight spot because it's under attack of the great country Zarmine. But the general, Rain, who's reputed to be an exceptionally gifted swordsman, is against the war and won't enter the battle. But how is one supposed to wage a war like this anyway?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/rain-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="kimi to kore kara" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Drama, Romance, Shounen ai, Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>kimi to kore kara</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>kimi-to-kore-kara</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Yamamoto Kotetsuko</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/28219/3/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Here starts the Konya spinoff series, focusing more on Gorou and Verde! There's plenty of Endou and Rikiya as well, but this story will spend more time telling the story of these heretofore side characters. The story takes place immediately after the last Konya chapter, so you can think of this as Chapter 20, just less focus on Endo/Rikiya and more on Gorou/Verde.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/kimi-to-kore-kara-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="the curse of brimstone" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>the curse of brimstone</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>the-curse-of-brimstone</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Justin Jordan, Philip Tan</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/the-curse-of-brimstone/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Joe Chamberlain would do anything to save his small, forgotten town-even make a deal with the devil. But things get worse, and Joe finds himself cursed with the power of BRIMSTONE. With the power of fire and destruction coursing through his hands, Joe must now track down and destroy the demon he made his deal with before the power he now wields destroys the town he was trying to save.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/the-curse-of-brimstone-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="cloak and dagger (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>cloak and dagger (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>cloak-and-dagger-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Dennis Hopeless, David Messina</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/c/cloak-and-dagger-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>For years, Tyrone Johnson and Tandy Bowen were the super hero duo called CLOAK AND DAGGER - waging a citywide war on drugs, organized crime and corporate greed. In recent years, their crusade has taken them across the globe, fighting alongside Spider-Man, The X-Men and even The Avengers, and though they've drifted apart, a dangerous threat from their past has resurfaced - one that will force Cloak and Dagger to reunite and come to terms with their truest feelings for one another and the past they share!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/cloak-and-dagger-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="halo: collateral damage" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Sci-fi, Video games" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>halo: collateral damage</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>halo-collateral-damage</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Alex Irvine, Dave Crosland, Leionard O'Grady</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/h/halo-collateral-damage/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The Master Chief and Blue Team are deployed by the UNSC to Alpha Corvi II, a precarious human colony world, seeking to halt the Covenant's efforts to uncover something hidden below the planet's surface. The Spartan strike team quickly finds out that they will have to rely on each other and a small cadre of human rebels in order to survive and complete their mission.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/halo-collateral-damage-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="kiss/army of darkness" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Fantasy, Movies - tv, Music" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>kiss/army of darkness</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>kiss-army-of-darkness</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Chad Bowers, Chris Sims, Ruairi Coleman</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/k/kissarmy-of-darkness/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>KISS is on top of the world and rocking faces until the night disciples of The Destroyer show up and the band disappears. With the tour canceled, a young Ash misses one of the most important events of his life that will change his destiny. Now the Chosen One has to get back on the right path and join the KISS ARMY OF DARKNESS!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/kiss-army-of-darkness-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="world of tanks: citadel" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Video games" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>world of tanks: citadel</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>world-of-tanks-citadel</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Garth Ennis, PJ Holden</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/w/world-of-tanks-citadel/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The Eastern Front, 1943: as the cataclysmic Battle of Kursk looms large, Captain Piotr Piotrowicz and his driver, Natalya 'Ginger' Pulkhova, prepare their unit for action- equipped with the worst tanks in the Russian inventory. On the opposite side, German tankers Karl Kraft and Freddie Stadler brace for the onslaught-well aware that failure here will put their Soviet enemy on the road to Berlin. Garth Ennis and PJ Holden present a second action-packed story of armored warfare, inspired by the phenomenally popular game World of Tanks.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/world-of-tanks-citadel-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="astonisher" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>astonisher</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>astonisher</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Alex de Campi, Jessica Kholinne, Pop Mhan</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/c/catalyst-prime-astonisher/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Magnus Atitarn, heir to the Atitarn Satellite Corp., tried to save the world with his experimental one-man spaceship and ended up a broken man. Now a celebrity joke suffering from post-traumatic stress disorder, Magnus has the power to travel inside the minds of superpowered people, where he discovers nightmares which threaten the entire human race. The strangest corners of the Catalyst Prime Universe are explored in this new series!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/astonisher-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="charismagic (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>charismagic (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>charismagic-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Vince Hernandez, Federico Blee, Mark Roslan, Joey Vazquez</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/c/charismagic-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The forces of magic have returned-and this time no magical being is safe! Aspen's magical action-adventure series returns for its epic third volume! Las Vegas magician Hank Medley and his talking cat Sparkles attempt to put the pieces of their life back together, as society has taken a hardline approach to magic and its destructive results. Meanwhile, Sudana uncovers a more sinister plot brewing in the confines of a secret Government's facility in the Nevada desert, as a new form of magic is taking shape that will not only spell the end for mankind-but also magical beings everywhere! The age of the Magic Harvester has arrived!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Completed/charismagic-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="bloodshot salvation" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>bloodshot salvation</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>bloodshot-salvation</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jeff Lemire, Lewis Larosa</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/b/bloodshot-salvation/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Now: In the arms of his beloved girlfriend Magic, Bloodshot has finally found hope for the future... in the form the couple's unborn child. But when Magic's estranged family - a cruel and sadistic clan of white supremacist criminals re-emerge to lay claim to their lost daughter, Bloodshot will be pushed back to the brink of madness, mayhem, and warfare... Soon: Eight years from today, Bloodshot's daughter has inherited her father's incredible abilities. Hunted by a high-tech kill squad called Omen, Jessie must hone her powers... and learn how to survive before the world is swallowed whole by the darkness that now pervades America...</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/bloodshot-salvation-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="nancy drew (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Drama, Mystery" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>nancy drew (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>nancy-drew-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Kelly Thompson, Jenn St-Onge</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/n/nancy-drew-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Nancy Drew is seventeen and good at everything... ESPECIALLY solving crimes. But her totally-in-control-and-obviously-running-perfectly-smooth-(but-not-really) life hits a snag when a mysterious message drags her back to the hometown she left behind. There she'll have to find out which of her friends are still her friends, which are enemies, and who exactly is trying to kill her... and (hopefully) stop them before they succeed. KELLY THOMPSON (Hawkeye, Star Wars, Rogue and Gambit) and JENN ST-ONGE (Giant Days, The Misfits) team up to present an all-new modern spin on a classic mystery icon!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/nancy-drew-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="wasted space" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>wasted space</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>wasted-space</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Michael Moreci, Hayden Sherman</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/w/wasted-space/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Billy Bane is a prophet who got it all wrong, and the galaxy has been burning ever since. All he wants is to waste away in the darkest corner of space with his best pal Dust, a supercharged Fuq bot. But when a new prophet comes calling, Billy is summoned to save the galaxy he's at least partially responsible for destroying. Too bad he couldn't care less.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/wasted-space-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="gigant" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Drama, Mature, Romance, School life, Sci-fi, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>gigant</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>gigant</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Oku Hiroya</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-comic-4.anyacg.co/thumbs/w300/96/04/9604402428c74a40bce9f9d31ae89b5d05c4aa17_29170_200_310.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Yamada Yoko, a high school boy who has a movie producer father. One day, while out with friends to shoot a film that he plans to enter into a film festival, a poster of Papiko, an adult video actress with big breasts, catches his eye.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/gigant-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
</danh_sach_truyen>