<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<danh_sach_truyen>
	<truyen ten="winter soldier (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>winter soldier (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>winter-soldier-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Kyle Higgins, Rod Reis</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/w/winter-soldier-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Bucky Barnes believes in second chances. Having escaped death, the loss of identity, and a life of murder, the man known as the Winter Soldier has worked hard to atone for his sins. But now...he's going to go one step further. What do you do when you've found redemption? You help others do the same. From KYLE HIGGINS (Nightwing, Power Rangers, C.O.W.L.) and ROD REIS (SECRET EMPIRE, DOCTOR STRANGE: DAMNATION, C.O.W.L.) comes the next chapter in the saga of the Winter Soldier. He's becoming a 'fixer,' working to help others leave behind lives of crime. It's Bucky's way of channeling his own pain in a productive, personal way...by helping others find the redemption that he found. However, as Bucky is going to learn, not all paths are the same... and not everyone can be 'saved.'</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/winter-soldier-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="robyn hood: outlaw" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>robyn hood: outlaw</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>robyn-hood-outlaw</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Howard Mackie, Babisu Kourtis</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/r/robyn-hood-outlaw/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Returning from her last adventure, Robyn is back in New York, and looking for some sort of normalcy. But not everyone feels she deserves any, the universe included. After a close friend is attacked, Robyn must take it upon herself to get to the bottom of this mystery as she is pitted against her greatest adversary yet, when she becomes public enemy number one, to the city she calls home. Don't miss this fast paced bare-knuckle, new series, Robyn Hood: Outlaw!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/robyn-hood-outlaw-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="transformers (2019)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Mecha, Movies-tv, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>transformers (2019)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>transformers-2019</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Brian Ruckley, Angel Hernandez, Cachet Whitman</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/transformers-(2019)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>A NEW ERA DAWNS! In the infinite universe, there exists a planet like no other: Cybertron! Home to the Transformers, and a thriving hub for inter-stellar commerce, it is a world brimming with organic and constructed diversity. Immense structures line its landscape. Mechanical giants roam across its surface. Starship-sized titans orbit its skies, keeping a constant protective watch above and below. Ancient Transformers merge into its very fabric. Small, mysterious creatures skulk in its shadows. It is a truly amazing realm, long untouched by war, and exuberantly reaching for the stars. This is the Cybertron that Optimus Prime and Megatron vie for in this bold new origin-a world of seemingly endless peace! All that changes when Bumblebee and Windblade take a newly-forged Cybertronian on his first voyage through this world of wonders-they are confronted by the hard reality of the first murder to have occurred on Cybertron in living memory!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/transformers-2019-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="grimm tales of terror (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Horror, Suspense" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>grimm tales of terror (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>grimm-tales-of-terror-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Joe Brusha, Sean Hill, Babisu Kourtis</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/g/grimm-tales-of-terror-vol-4/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The hit Zenescope horror series is back, and not only as a comic, but also as a soon-to-be-released motion picture. The first issue in this new volume ties into the upcoming film and continues the series tradition of delivering modern horror with truly terrifying twists.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/grimm-tales-of-terror-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="the stone king" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>the stone king</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>the-stone-king</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Kel McDonald, Tyler Crook</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/the-stone-king/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>When you become an adult, you have to prove yourself, at least that's how it works for the Stoneport thieves. Ave has decided to illegally harvest healing moss from the Stone King, a mighty giant who roams the lands. Her theft goes even better than she could have dreamed. The biggest gem she's ever seen is her prize. But is that prize worth the consequences? Part of the comiXology Originals line of exclusive digital content only available on comiXology and Kindle. This title is available as part of comiXology Unlimited, Kindle Unlimited and Prime Reading.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/the-stone-king-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="age of x-man: the marvelous x-men" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>age of x-man: the marvelous x-men</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>age-of-x-man-the-marvelous-x-men</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Lonnie Nadler, Zac Thompson, Marco Failla</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/a/age-of-x-man-the-marvelous-x-men/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>ENTER THE AGE OF X-MAN! In an age of utopia, the Summers Institute for Higher Learning is the premiere school for the mutant community across the globe. Attendance is mandatory for all mutant children, as they learn to become the next generation of marvelous X-Men. But even in a utopian society, teenagers will always find a way to rebel... Follow Glob, Armor, Anole and Rockslide as they discover what it really means to live in an age of peace and harmony!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/age-of-x-man-the-marvelous-x-men-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="the six million dollar man" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Movies-tv" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>the six million dollar man</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>the-six-million-dollar-man</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Christopher Hastings, David Hahn</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/the-six-million-dollar-man-(2019)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>CHRISTOPHER HASTINGS (The Unbelievable Gwenpool! Secret Agent Deadpool! Adventure Time! I Am Groot!) and DAVID HAHN (Batman '66! Bombshells: United!) proudly present a story from a time when there wasn't internet, but there WERE cyborgs! It's the 1970s. Things are going great. Steve Austen (used to be an astronaut, now has robo-parts and a laser eye) heads to Japan to help Secret Agent Niko Abe stop a madman with missiles. Steve figures, no sweat. But then...sweat. How's Steve going to complete his mission, when his fancy $6,000,000 body starts. DRASTICALLY) depreciating in value!?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/the-six-million-dollar-man-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="morning in america" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Horror, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>morning in america</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>morning-in-america</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Magdalene Visaggio, Claudia Aguirre</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/m/morning-in-america/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>A new Oni Press miniseries by powerhouse team of Magdalene Visaggio (ETERNITY GIRL) and Claudia Aguirre (KIM and KIM)! The year is 1983. A series of disappearances afflicts Tucker, Ohio following the opening of a mysterious new factory. But when the town finds itself under siege from strange monsters, it's up to intrepid girl gang of no-account teen girl delinquents to try and figure out what's happening -- and save everyone's lives before it's too late.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/morning-in-america-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="age of x-man: x-tremists" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>age of x-man: x-tremists</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>age-of-x-man-x-tremists</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Leah Williams, Georges Jeanty</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/a/age-of-x-man-x-tremists/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>ENTER THE AGE OF X-0MAN! A perfect world doesn't just...happen. It needs to be cultivated. That's where the X-Tremists come in. Psylocke, Iceman, Northstar, Blob, Jubilee and Moneta protect people from threats they won't even know existed, including the most insidious threat of all - love.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/age-of-x-man-x-tremists-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="star trek vs. transformers" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Movies-tv, Mecha, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>star trek vs. transformers</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>star-trek-vs-transformers</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>John Barber, Mike Johnson, Philip Murphy</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/s/star-trek-vs-transformers/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The Transformers '80s cartoon series meets Star Trek: The Animated Series in a no-holds-barred Saturday Morning mash-up for the ages! At the edge of Klingon space, the Starship Enterprise finds there's more to the final frontier than meets the eye, when Kirk and his crew come face to face with the strangest life forms of all: Cybertronians! This unprecedented crossover brings together two of the greatest science fiction universes of all time-in the style of their classic animated series! A five-year mission meets a four-million-year war!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Completed/star-trek-vs-transformers-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="the forgotten queen" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Historical, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>the forgotten queen</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>the-forgotten-queen</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Tini Howard, Amilcar Pinna</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/the-forgotten-queen/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>An ancient evil returns! Long ago, the mighty generals of the Mongol Empire rode from Siberia to Carpathia and conquered all who stood in their way. Legends tell of a witch who walked with them, who could infect the hearts of any warriors in her midst with an unquenchable thirst for battle and bloodshed...a War-Monger. And now she is walking again. This winter, an ancient evil will stir as superstar-in-the-making Tini Howard (Captain America Annual #1, Assassinistas) and powerhouse artist Amilcar Pinna (Generation X) unleash hell in a brand-new saga of honor, love, and savagery that's centuries in the making!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/the-forgotten-queen-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="age of x-man: alpha" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>age of x-man: alpha</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>age-of-x-man-alpha</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Lonnie Nadler, Zac Thompson, Ramon Rosanas</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/a/age-of-x-man/alpha_1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>THE AGE OF X-MAN DAWNS... AND THE X-MEN CANNOT STOP IT.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/age-of-x-man-alpha-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="old man quill" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>old man quill</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>old-man-quill</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Ethan Sacks, Robert Gill</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/o/old-man-quill/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>THE FAR-FLUNG SAGA OF THE ONCE AND FUTURE STAR-LORD BEGINS! Meet Peter Quill. He used to be Star-Lord - you know, the legendary outlaw - but it's been quite some time since he's gone by that name. Taking over for his father as the Emperor of Spartax, Quill put the life of spacefaring adventure behind him for one of leadership and responsibility. Quill grew up. But things didn't go as planned. Decades have passed, and Peter is haunted by tragedy. Down and out, Quill's existence means nothing...until the former GUARDIANS OF THE GALAXY drag Peter out of his funk for one last mission! The heist of a lifetime - and Quill's harrowing quest for redemption - begins here!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/old-man-quill-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="crackdown" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Video games" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>crackdown</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>crackdown</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jonathan David Goff, Ricardo Jaime</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/c/crackdown-(2019)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The hyper-powered world of Crackdown (Xbox) has made its way to the comic page! In the not-so-distant future, civilized society is more plugged-in and interconnected than ever - but criminal organizations are growing more connected as well, forming unholy alliances, and plotting for an unprecedented campaign against the world. When a series of devastating blackout attacks plunge major metropolitan areas into darkness and chaos, the global population is terrified, traditional law enforcement is overwhelmed - and it's up to The Agency, an elite international crime-fighting task force, to restore peace and deliver justice, by any means necessary.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/crackdown-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="wolverine: infinity watch" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>wolverine: infinity watch</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>wolverine-infinity-watch</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Gerry Duggan, Andy MacDonald</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/w/wolverine-infinity-watch/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>REVEALED AT LAST! HOW WOLVERINE GOT THE INFINITY STONE! Wolverine has finally returned, disentwined from the evil clutches of Soteira...but hang on, didn't he have an Infinity Stone? How did THAT happen?! And wasn't he popping up all over the place for a little while? The answers you seek are finally revealed as Logan goes cosmic alongside everyone's favorite god of lies and stories, Loki Laufeyson!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/wolverine-infinity-watch-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="hulkverines" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>hulkverines</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>hulkverines</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Greg Pak, Ario Anindito</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/h/hulkverines/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>At last! It's Weapon H versus his predecessors-Wolverine and the Hulk! Once, the Weapon X program sought to recreate the world's two greatest hunters. They ended up with Weapon H, a man of Adamantium claws and gamma-juiced blood. Now, Wolverine and the Hulk are back in action - and coming after the dangerous creation made in their name!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/hulkverines-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="doctor strange (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero, Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>doctor strange (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>doctor-strange-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Mark Waid, Jesus Saiz</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/doctor-strange-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>SORCERER SUPREME...OF THE GALAXY! The Eye of Agamotto is closed! Doctor Stephen Strange has lost his connection to the Earth's arcane power, and he can't wait to recover while nightmares press against the seams of our reality. Tony Stark offers a 21st-century solution: When astral travel fails, try astronautical travel. Enter Doctor Strange: Space-Explorer Supreme! New spells, allies and enemies - new and old - await Strange beyond the stars, along with corners and secrets of the Marvel Universe seen here for the first time! Space is endless, but time is short. After years of threats, Stephen's bill for magic use is coming due - who will come to collect?!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/doctor-strange-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="avengers: no road home" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>avengers: no road home</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>avengers-no-road-home</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Al Ewing, Mark Waid, Jim Zub, Paco Medina</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/a/avengers-no-road-home/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The team that brought you AVENGERS: NO SURRENDER REUNITES for an all-new weekly AVENGERS adventure! Night has fallen across the universe. Now seven Avengers - and one new addition - journey forth to bring back the light. But when the threat they face has destroyed even the gods...will anyone make it home?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/avengers-no-road-home-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="wonder twins" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>wonder twins</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>wonder-twins</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Mark Russell, Stephen Byrne</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/w/wonder-twins-(2019)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Exiled from their home planet, alien heroes Zan and Jayna must navigate life as teens on Earth at South Metropolis High School, where they're even bigger outsiders than the typical awkward young adults. Under the watchful eye of Superman, the brother and sister pull monitor duty at the Hall of Justice as interns, while also trying to overcome the pitfalls of Zan's brash confidence and Jayna's shy but streetwise persona. If you think you know the Wonder Twins, think again-this book takes the form of the unexpected.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/wonder-twins-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="age of x-man: nextgen" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>age of x-man: nextgen</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>age-of-x-man-nextgen</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Ed Brisson, Marcus To</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/a/age-of-x-man-nextgen/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>ENTER THE AGE OF X-MAN! The perfect heroes for a perfect world! The X-Men have helped make the world into a utopia where living in fear and hatred is a thing of the past. All people are united under the banner of mutantkind, and all of mutantkind idolizes the X-Men. Jean Grey! Colossus! Storm! X-23! X-Man! Nature Girl! Magneto! And of course, the amazing Nightcrawler! When danger threatens the world, the Marvelous X-Men set things right for the good of all. And no one dares say otherwise.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/age-of-x-man-nextgen-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="war is hell" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Life sucks, Military" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>war is hell</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>war-is-hell</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Howard Chaykin, Phillip K. Johnson, Howard Chaykin</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/w/war-is-hell-(2019)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>ALL-NEW WAR STORY! In honor of Marvel's 80th Anniversary and history with War Comics comes a brand new edition of WAR IS HELL with two fascinating and soul-crushing tales of War. 'In the Mood' by Howard Chaykin takes you to the skies as the Luftwaffe and RAF battle over the English Channel for a battle tale of bitter irony and 'War Glammer' by Phillip Kennedy Johnson brings you back to Earth in modern day Afghanistan with a story that will chill you to the bone.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Completed/war-is-hell-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="mysteries of love in space" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>mysteries of love in space</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>mysteries-of-love-in-space</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>James Tynion IV, Tom Grummett</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/m/mysteries-of-love-in-space/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Sometimes love can make you feel like you're from another planet...but what if you actually were? Join Superman, The New Gods, Green Lantern, Starro, Hawkgirl and even the Teen Titans' new sensation Crush for eight tales of romance that will whisk you to the moon and back!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Completed/mysteries-of-love-in-space-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="journey into unknown worlds" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>journey into unknown worlds</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>journey-into-unknown-worlds</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Cullen Bunn, Clay McLeod Chapman, Francesco Manna</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/j/journey-into-unknown-worlds/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>ALL-NEW SCI-FI STORY! In celebration of Marvel's 80th anniversary and the comic books that captivated hearts and minds across generations, join us for two scintillating sci-fi stories - the first an extraterrestrial adventure by Cullen Bunn the likes of which haven't been seen in this or any other decade, and the second a tale of terror by Clay McLeod Chapman that could take place in your very own back yard! The secrets of the universe lie waiting to be discovered, True-Believers, on a JOURNEY TO UNKNOWN WORLDS!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Completed/journey-into-unknown-worlds-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="guardians of the galaxy (2019)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Sci-fi, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>guardians of the galaxy (2019)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>guardians-of-the-galaxy-2019</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Donny Cates, Geoff Shaw</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/g/guardians-of-the-galaxy-(2019)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>WHO WILL STAND? The universe is on fire. Hundreds of worlds are at war. Never has there been such hatred and division across the cosmos. And in spite of all this, Thanos of Titan is still dead...or is he? Now, more than ever, the cosmos need the Guardians of the Galaxy...but in the aftermath of the Infinity Wars, who is left to answer the call? Featuring every cosmic super hero in the known universe by the THANOS WINS creative team of Donny Cates and Geoff Shaw!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/guardians-of-the-galaxy-2019-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="naomi" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>naomi</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>naomi</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Brian Michael Bendis, David F. Walker, Jamal Campbell</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/n/naomi/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>DC's biggest, newest mystery starts here! When a fight between Superman and Mongul crashes into a small Northwestern town, Naomi (last name?) begins a quest to uncover the last time a super-powered person visited her home-and how that might tie into her own origins and adoption. Follow Naomi's journey on a quest that will take her to the heart of the DC Universe and unfold a universe of ideas and stories that have never been seen before. Join writers Brian Michael Bendis, David Walker and breakout artist Jamal Campbell in Wonder Comics' massively ambitious new series and star... NAOMI.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/naomi-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="wolverine: the long night" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>wolverine: the long night</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>wolverine-the-long-night</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Benjamin Percy, Marcio Takara</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/w/wolverine-the-long-night-adaptation/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Following a string of mysterious deaths in Burns, Alaska, Special Agents Sally Pierce and Tad Marshall arrive to investigate. They soon find there's more going on than meets the eye... Marvel's hit scripted podcast, 'Wolverine: The Dark Night,' comes to life on the page! Chilling twists and turns, brought to you by the original author of the podcast, Benjamin Percy, and the art talents of Marcio Takara!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/wolverine-the-long-night-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="black widow (2019)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Leading ladies, Spy, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>black widow (2019)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>black-widow-2019</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jen Soska, Sylvia Soska, Flaviano</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/b/black-widow-(2019)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Natasha Romanoff was trained to kill. For years now she's tried to overcome that programming, to side with the angels...to be a hero. And where'd that get her? Killed. By one of the few true friends she allowed herself to have. Now she's back from the dead, angry as hell and finding those better angels harder and harder to hear. Jen and Sylvia Soska - the Twisted Twins of horror - join rising artist Flaviano to weave a web of vice, violence and vengeance that will net Natasha the biggest bad men she's ever faced... or put her back in the ground for good.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/black-widow-2019-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="barbarella / dejah thoris" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Fantasy, Leading ladies, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>barbarella / dejah thoris</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>barbarella-dejah-thoris</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Leah Williams, German Garcia</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/b/barbarelladejah-thoris/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>From opposite ends of time, two heroines unite for an otherworldly adventure! Barbarella, the siren of space, meets Dejah Thoris, Princess of Barsoom, and together they must solve a murder mystery that spans time and space in order to find their way home. Leah Williams (Adventure Time Comics, X-Men: Black) teams with German Garcia (Action Comics, X-men) for a fun, deadly, mind-bending epic!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/barbarella-dejah-thoris-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="babyteeth" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Horror" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>babyteeth</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>babyteeth</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Donny Cates, Garry Brown</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/b/babyteeth/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Sadie Ritter is sixteen years old, nine months pregnant, and scared out of her sweet nerdy mind. Having a baby that young is tough, but with the support of her loving family behind her, everything should be okay. OH YEAH, and also her baby is the antichrist and it's going to break open the barriers between the earthly and demonic planes and unleash eternal suffering to all of humankind. Other than that, though...should be fine.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/babyteeth-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="invaders (2019)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>invaders (2019)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>invaders-2019</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Chip Zdarsky, Butch Guice, Carlos Magno</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/i/invaders-(2019)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>THE GREATEST GENERATION OF MARVEL HEROES IS BACK - TO STOP ONE OF THEIR OWN! In commemoration of Marvel's 80th anniversary and springing from events in the pages of AVENGERS and THE BEST DEFENSE, the Marvel Universe's first super-team is back! CAPTAIN AMERICA. THE HUMAN TORCH. THE WINTER SOLDIER. NAMOR. They fought in WORLD WAR II together as THE INVADERS. But now NAMOR is the enemy, a global threat more powerful than ever. His deadly plans are as deep and far-reaching as the ocean and REVELATIONS about his past could THREATEN the MARVEL UNIVERSE! It's up to his old teammates to stop him, but what chance do they have against the man who knows their every move? 'War Ghost' begins here!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/invaders-2019-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="young justice (2019)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>young justice (2019)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>young-justice-2019</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Brian Michael Bendis, Patrick Gleason</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/y/young-justice-(2019)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Superboy! Wonder Girl! Robin! Impulse! Amethyst! They're all united in YOUNG JUSTICE #1, the debut issue of a brand-new series that also introduces new heroes Teen Lantern and Jinny Hex! When the nightmare dimension known as Gemworld invades Metropolis, these teen heroes reunite to deal with the situation-but they're shocked to discover the battle may be the key to the return of Conner Kent, a.k.a. Superboy! This mix of fan favorites and new legacy heroes will be the center point for some of the biggest goings-on at DC! As if that weren't enough, Bendis reunites with all-star artist Patrick Gleason (SUPERMAN, ACTION COMICS, GREEN LANTERN CORPS) to bring the new heroes of DC's Wonder Comics to life!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/young-justice-2019-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="infinity wars: infinity warps" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>infinity wars: infinity warps</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>infinity-wars-infinity-warps</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Ryan North, Mariko Tamaki, Jim Zub, Natacha Bustos, Francisco Herrera, Ozgur Yildirim</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/i/infinity-wars-infinity-warps/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>When you gaze into the warp...you get more stories of mad Two-In-One heroes! Read about the Star Siblings of the Warped Universe - MISTER INVISIBLE and HOT ROCKS, the TERRIFIC TWO! Then, see how the covert programs of the Green Room created the gamma-powered GREEN WIDOW! And join MOON SQUIRREL AND TIPPYSAUR as they save the planet from the most dangerous threat it's ever faced!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/infinity-wars-infinity-warps-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="champions (2019)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>champions (2019)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>champions-2019</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jim Zubkavich, Steven Cummings</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/c/champions-(2019)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>THE WORLD STILL NEEDS HEROES - AND THERE ARE HEROES ALL OVER THE WORLD! The Champions have gone global! The team has seen explosive growth under Ms. Marvel's leadership, with super-powered members ready to answer the call in a dozen different countries. They're saving people and improving lives across the planet while they inspire the next generation... but something sinister lurks beneath the surface of their expanded mission. It's a dark secret that could destroy the team and everything they stand for! Jim Zub (AVENGERS: NO SURRENDER, UNCANNY AVENGERS) and Steven Cummings (Wayward, Legends of the Dark Knight) ignite a new era of CHAMPIONS, filled to the brim with action, adventure and drama in the Mighty Marvel Manner!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/champions-2019-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="martian manhunter (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>martian manhunter (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>martian-manhunter-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Steve Orlando, Riley Rossmo</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/m/martian-manhunter-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The acclaimed team of writer Steve Orlando and artist Riley Rossmo (BATMAN / THE SHADOW, BATMAN: NIGHT OF THE MONSTER MEN) reteam for a reinvention of the Manhunter from Mars in this twisted, unexpected series. Back on Mars, J'onn was about as corrupt as a law officer can be, and when a reckoning comes for his entire society, he'll get a second chance he doesn't want or deserve! One shocking murder, and an unexpected fragment of the Mars he lost, will change his life-and the course of the Earth-forever!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/martian-manhunter-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="deadpool (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>deadpool (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>deadpool-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Skottie Young, Scott Hepburn, Nic Klein</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/deadpool-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>MERCIN' FOR A LIVING! Skottie Young and Nic Klein bring you the craziest tales of the Regeneratin' Degenerate yet! It's been a while since Deadpool's had to merc to make ends meet, but things are tough all over. While Deadpool tries to get his humble mercenary-for-hire business back off the ground, a catastrophic threat so unfathomably huge, so mind-breakingly cataclysmic it defies description, is heading toward Earth, and there's only ONE PERSON WHO CAN STOP IT!!! Oh no, wait... it's not Wade, is it? Oh, It's Wade.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/deadpool-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="man without fear" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>man without fear</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>man-without-fear</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jed Mackay, Danilo Beyruth</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/m/man-without-fear-(2019)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Daredevil is gone, but Hell's Kitchen is still a place of heroes and villains. Foggy Nelson will learn what it means to live in a world without a Daredevil. And without a Daredevil to protect it, has hell come for his city? Who is The Man Without Fear?!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/man-without-fear-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="doomsday clock" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>doomsday clock</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>doomsday-clock</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Geoff Johns, Gary Frank, Brad Anderson</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/doomsday-clock/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>DC Comics presents to you a 12-issue maxiseries from the critically acclaimed team of writer Geoff Johns, artist Gary Frank and colorist Brad Anderson. You are not prepared for what lies ahead within these pages, good readers.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/doomsday-clock-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="killmonger" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>killmonger</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>killmonger</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Bryan Hill, Juan E. Ferreyra</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/k/killmonger-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>THE BRUTAL TALE OF A MAN WHO WILL STOP AT NOTHING FOR FREEDOM...One day, Erik Killmonger will rise up and attempt to steal the throne of Wakanda. The throne he believes he is owed. But long before he became 'Killmonger', there was a boy known as N'Jadaka. A boy who was stolen from his home and taught only the world's cruelties. A boy who knew the Black Panther only as a fairy tale, a whisper from strangers. This is the story of a man who is driven by revenge. This is the legend of Killmonger.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/killmonger-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="x-force (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>x-force (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>x-force-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Ed Brisson, Dylan Burnett</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/x/x-force-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>FROM THE ASHES OF EXTERMINATION! Cable is dead...and now, the original X-Force team of Domino, Cannonball, Shatterstar, Boom Boom and Warpath. must hunt down the murderer of their former leader! The mutant militia are hot for blood... but when their target is the time-traveling younger version of their fallen mentor, is there a line they absolutely cannot cross? And what does Deathlok have to do with all of it? From Ed Brisson (EXTERMINATION, OLD MAN LOGAN) and Dylan Burnett (COSMIC GHOST RIDER), comes an all-new, high-octane mutant adventure! A reckoning will come!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/x-force-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="shazam! (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>shazam! (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>shazam-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Geoff Johns, Dale Eaglesham, Mayo 'SEN' Naito</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/s/shazam-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Teenager turned super-hero Billy Batson struggles to balance school and superheroics! (Guess which one is more fun?) But when Shazam unlocks a shocking secret deep within the Rock of Eternity, it challenges everything he knows about the worlds of magic and his family's future as its champions! Also, witness the bizarre team-up of Dr. Sivana and Mr. Mind as they set off to build a society all their own! Don't miss the start of an epic run in the making as 'Shazam and the Seven Realms' begins!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/shazam-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="superior spider-man (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>superior spider-man (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>superior-spider-man-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Christos N. Gage, Mike Hawthorne</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/s/superior-spider-man-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Otto Octavius leaves the moniker of Doctor Octopus behind and once again becomes THE SUPERIOR SPIDER-MAN! If you think you've already read the most intense and surprisingly heartbreaking Superior Spider-Man story, prepare to be wrong. Otto is going to prove to the world that he's the most effective and (to him at least) the best super hero in the world. But when a villain that overpowers him by so much shows up in San Francisco, there's no way Ock can win, right? Can you see Otto smirking from where you're reading this?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/superior-spider-man-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="freedom fighters (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>freedom fighters (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>freedom-fighters-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Robert Venditti, Eddy Barrows</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/f/freedom-fighters-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Line up for this all-new maxiseries set on Earth X, where the Nazis won World War II! Twenty years after invading and occupying America, Germany wiped out all metahuman resistance, including the original Freedom Fighters. Fast-forward to the present day, and a new team of Freedom Fighters emerges to challenge the Nazi occupation once again. But if they're to have any chance of victory, they're going to need Uncle Sam-who disappeared after his original team was killed. The 12-part epic 'Death of a Nation' storyline kicks off here!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/freedom-fighters-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="black panther vs. deadpool" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>black panther vs. deadpool</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>black-panther-vs-deadpool</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Daniel Kibblesmith, Ricardo Lopez Ortiz</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/m/miles-morales-spider-man-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>VIBRANIUM BULLETS AND REGROWING LIMBS - EVERYTHING YOU WANT FROM A COMIC IS HERE! Deadpool's teamed up with, taken down or taken a beating from just about every hero in the Marvel Universe - And no way is the Black Panther going to miss out on his turn! From Late Show writer Daniel Kibblesmith comes a hilarious romp through Wakanda as Deadpool goes on the hunt for the world's most valuable resource: Vibranium! When a beloved figure of the Marvel Universe becomes collateral damage in a fight between Deadpool and the Wrecker, the heroic Deadpool sets out to obtain a fragment of Vibranium that could save the victim's life. But his unconventional methods - ranging from poaching to dismemberment - don't sit well with the King of Wakanda, and Deadpool's about to learn that you don't bring a sword to a claw fight!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/black-panther-vs-deadpool-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="john wick" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Movies-tv, Suspense" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>john wick</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>john-wick</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Greg Pak, Giovanni Valletta</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/j/john-wick/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>When a young John Wick emerges from prison and embarks upon his first, epic vendetta, he comes up against a strange, powerful community of assassins and must learn how to master the Book of Rules that guides their lethal business. What are the Three Bills? Who is Calamity? And who was John Wick before he became the Baba Yaga? Here for the first time, read the thrilling origin story of John Wick, from 'Planet Hulk' writer Greg Pak and 'Dark Horse Presents' artist Giovanni Valletta.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/john-wick-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="miles morales: spider-man" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>miles morales: spider-man</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>miles-morales-spider-man</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Saladin Ahmed, Javier Garron</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/m/miles-morales-spider-man-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Balancing his normal life, school, parents, etc...and super-heroing has never been easy, but when the Rhino and a cadre of mysterious criminals start plaguing Brooklyn, things take a dark turn. And Miles doesn't even know the half of it yet. Eisner Award-winner Saladin Ahmed (BLACK BOLT) and Young Gun Javier Garron (ANT-MAN and THE WASP) bring you the latest incarnation of the coolest character in the Marvel Universe!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/miles-morales-spider-man-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
</danh_sach_truyen>