<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<danh_sach_truyen>
	<truyen ten="tokiwa kitareri!!" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Comedy, Drama, Ecchi, Harem, Romance, School life, Sci-fi, Shounen., Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>tokiwa kitareri!!</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>tokiwa-kitareri</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Matsuena Syun</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/29978/4/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Yasaka Tokiwa lives in an unusual time, and according to his dreams, it's about to become even stranger. He's been having a dream of a woman called Ri'in ever since the robot, who he calls Makina, came to his home. He and Makina attend the same school, where their other classmates include a secret ninja (Kusanagi Kanata) and a sorcerer (Yata Haruka). When Tokiwa, the robot, the ninja, and the sorcerer rush to rescue the student council president from a demon, the boys find that they've all been having the same dream! What is going to happen to their world?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/tokiwa-kitareri-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="kagerou daze" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Drama, Psychological, Romance, Shounen., Slice of life, Supernatural, Tragedy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>kagerou daze</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>kagerou-daze</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Jin (Shizennoteki-P), Shidu, Satou Mahiro</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/28205/3/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>A story based on the new popular series of songs by Jin (Shizennoteki-p) titled 'Kagerou Project (Heat-Haze Daze)'. Shintaro Kisaragi--a HikiNEET who shut himself inside his room for 2 years--has been living his life normally until he met a cyber girl named Ene, who appeared in his computer screen when someone anonymously sent him a mysterious e-mail with an attached file--which was Ene--one year ago. One day, Ene had been messing up with Shintaro's PC. which causing him to go to the outside world for the first time in 2 years.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/kagerou-daze-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="shinobi shijuusou" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Comedy, Drama, Harem, Romance, School life, Shoujo." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>shinobi shijuusou</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>shinobi-shijuusou</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Himuka Tohru</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/30413/3/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Chouko Manaka is the next heir to the prestigeous Manaka family. Now she is entering high school and she has had enough with being surrounded by bodyguards, who have prevented her from making any friends. Her father is still worried though, so he makes a deal with her. If she transfers to Mizuno-o high school, where many of the students are also studying to be shinobi, and can get one of these people to be her right-hand man before graduation, he'll consider her to be able to make decisions for herself. On the first day of school Chouko meets the son of their butler, who suddenly declares that he wants her to be his master?!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/shinobi-shijuusou-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="isobe isobee monogatari - ukiyo wa tsurai yo" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Historical,	Shounen., Slice of life" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>isobe isobee monogatari - ukiyo wa tsurai yo</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>isobe-isobee-monogatari-ukiyo-wa-tsurai-yo</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Nakama Ryou</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/43295/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>In this ukiyoe-style manga, Isobe Isobee is a lazy, slacker samurai with big dreams. He lives with his mother, who thinks highly of him. He lays around the house, sneakily looks at Edo-period pornography without his mother noticing, naps at school... but he plans to become a respectable samurai one day!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/isobe-isobee-monogatari-ukiyo-wa-tsurai-yo-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="chihayafuru" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Drama, Josei, Romance, School life, Slice of life, Sports" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>chihayafuru</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>chihayafuru</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Suetsugu Yuki</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/1716/10/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>All her life, Chihaya's dream was to see her model sister become Japan's best... That is, until a quiet, unassuming transfer student named Arata tells her otherwise. A dream, he explains to her, is something she needs to work at herself. Arata plays a competitive version of a traditional Japanese card game--known as Hyakunin Isshu--in a way Chihaya has never seen before. After taking Arata's place in a game, Chihaya discovers she has a passion for it. Now Chihaya wants to become number one in the world, the Queen of Karuta. Chihayafuru won the 2nd Manga Taisho Award. Winner of the 35th annual Kodansha Manga Award for Best Shoujo. Nominated for the 16th (2012) and 20th (2016) Tezuka Osamu Cultural Prize.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/chihayafuru-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="coffee and vanilla" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Ecchi, Romance, Shoujo., Smut" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>coffee and vanilla</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>coffee-and-vanilla</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Akegami Takara</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/37842/3/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Would you like an older man dressed in suits? She was never this popular before university but before she knew it, Risa was way out of everyone's league. The one who saves her from this cruel fate is a handsome man who can rock his suits, Fukami-san. What will he offer Risa, who is a beginner at love...!?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/coffee-and-vanilla-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="new prince of tennis" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Drama, School life, Shounen., Sports" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>new prince of tennis</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>new-prince-of-tennis</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Konomi Takeshi</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/6990/9/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>The purported advertisement from the Jump Square issue says that everything in The Prince of Tennis up to now has been 'prologue' and that 'a new legend for [the main character] Ryoma and the others will begin.' This continues what happened in the 'Prince of Tennis', after the end of the tournament . In 'The New Prince of Tennis', Ryoma and the others (team members and teams they faced) begin a new adventure when they are the only 50 middle school students to be invited to the Japanese High School Representatives Selection Camp where only the top potentials in the Japanese tennis world train.What will happen now?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/new-prince-of-tennis-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="prince of tennis " tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Comedy, Drama, School life, Shounen., Sports" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>prince of tennis </ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>prince-of-tennis</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Konomi Takeshi</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/7918/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Ryoma Echizen just joined the Seishun Academy's tennis team, which is known for being one of the most competitive teams in Japan. Its members are incredibly talented, gifted, and athletic. With rigorous and extremely intense practices, the upperclassmen of the team expect the very best from themselves and they expect even more from the new members of the team. While most of the freshmen are on pins and needles hoping they won't get cut from the team, Ryoma Echizen is confident, cool, and collected. Some might even say he's cocky, but at least he's got the skills to back up his attitude. With his virtually unreturnable 'twist serve', Ryoma is sure to make the starting team. Join Ryoma and the other first years, as they train hard, make friends, and try to find a place for themselves on the team. And meet Ryoma's cute but chronically shy classmate Sakuno Ryuzaki. She's got a big crush on Ryoma, but will he ever notice her? Ryoma Echizen is the Prince of Tennis. He may be ready for the Seishun Academy tennis team, but are they ready for him?!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/prince-of-tennis-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="zipang" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Drama, Historical, Sci-fi, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>zipang</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>zipang</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Kawaguchi Kaiji</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/11587/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>In the year 200X, a Japanese fleet consisting of 3 vessels leave on a mission to South America. After encountering a storm, the ship JDS Mirai find themselves without their escorts and in 1942, traveling towards the island of Midway to face the American fleet in one of largest battles in naval history. The crew of MIrai must decide whether or not to change the course of history by involving itself in WWII.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/zipang-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="happiness" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Drama, Horror, School life, Shounen., Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>happiness</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>happiness</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Oshimi Shuzo</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/30345/6/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Makoto Okazaki is your run of the mill high-schooler, a perfect bullying target and a closet pervert. One night he decides to return a DVD to a friend of his and ventures out into the darkness. He notices a person on a nearby rooftop. The person lunges at him before he is able to make sense of this, and bites into his neck, drinking his blood. The attacker stops. At this point Makoto notices that the attacker is a beautiful girl. She asks him: 'Do you want to die or become like me?' He decides to live...</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/happiness-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="ratman" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Comedy, Ecchi, Romance, School life, Sci-fi, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>ratman</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>ratman</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Inui Sekihiko</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/8106/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Meet Shooto. He's a big hero fan and wants to become a hero! The problem is that he's mocked for being too short. One day, his classmate Mizushima invites him to become a 'hero' at her home which is actually a criminal organization called Jackal. Shooto then gets tricked by Jackal's leader Crea to become their supervillian, Ratman! Now the world's smallest hero will embark on his battle against heroes and villains alike!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/ratman-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="accel world" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Comedy, Drama, Romance, School life, Sci-fi, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>accel world</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>accel-world</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Kawahara reki, Aigamo Hiroyuki</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/300/3/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>No matter how much the times change, bullied kids aren't going anywhere. And fat junior high school student Haruyuki is one of them. But one day, Haruyuki encounters Kuroyukihime, the most beautiful and elegant girl at school, who gives him a mysterious program: 'Brain Burst'...and the secret of the 'Accelerated World.' He may be at the bottom of the food chain at school, but Haruyuki and his destiny begin to 'accelerate' with incredible speed in the virtual realm as he aims for the top.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/accel-world-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="flying witch" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Fantasy, Shounen., Slice of life, Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>flying witch</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>flying-witch</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Ishizuka Chihiro</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/2769/3/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Kowata Makoto is an airhead with a bad sense of direction who just moved into her relative's house but is that all? A manga about the coming of age of a witch in modern day japan.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/flying-witch-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="nanba mg5" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Comedy, Drama, School life, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>nanba mg5</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>nanba-mg5</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Ozawa Toshio</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-comic-5.anyacg.co/thumbs/w300/e7/68/e768083f1f755f2ef4e5e5ddb703722e6dbcaa5e_18516_200_310.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Born in a family of delinquents, Nanba Tsuyoshi is expected to succeed his older brother as the strongest delinquent in school. Unbeknownst to his family however, he decides to enroll in the top high school in town to live as a normal high schooler. Can he maintain his double life as the strongest delinquent in town and as a normal high schooler?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/nanba-mg5-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="enigma" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Adventure, Drama, Horror, Mystery, Psychological, Shounen., Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>enigma</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>enigma</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Sakaki Kenji</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/2586/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Haiba Sumio is a student at a Tokyo High School with an interesting ability... He occasionally falls asleep and wakes up with premonitions of the future written out on his 'Dream Diary'. With this ability, Sumio helps out people in trouble before anything bad happens, until one day when his peaceful life completely changes.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/enigma-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="akb49 - renai kinshi jourei" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Drama, Ecchi, Gender bender, Romance, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>akb49 - renai kinshi jourei</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>akb49-renai-kinshi-jourei</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Motoazabu Factory, Miyajima Reiji</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/505/3/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>This series is about a guy called Urakawa Minoru crossdressing as a girl to participate in a female idol group audition (akb48). The main objective is to help the girl he likes, Yoshinaga Hiroko, pass the audition. Yoshinaga Hiroko's dream is to become like her favorite idol who is in the akb48 group. This audition happens to be her final try, so Minoru crossdresses as Minori and took part in the audition to make sure she realizes her dream. Hiroko got qualified eventually, however, the shocking news was Minoru was qualified as well. Thus, the road to becoming a female idol begins...</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/akb49-renai-kinshi-jourei-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="kurosagi" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Drama, Mystery, Psychological, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>kurosagi</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>kurosagi</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Takeshi Natsuhara, Kuromaru</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/5535/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>White swindlers (shirosagi) are those that cheat people to take their money, red swindlers (akasagi) are those that swindle the opposite sex, and black swindlers (kurosagi) are those that cheat the white and red swindlers. After his family is swindled by white swindlers, Kurosaki sets out to avenge them by becoming a black swindler. Kurosagi won the 2008 Shogakukan Manga Award for seinen/general manga along with Tetsuji Sekiya's Bambino!.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/kurosagi-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="mahou shoujo site" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Drama, Horror, Mature, Mystery, School life, Shounen., Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>mahou shoujo site</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>mahou-shoujo-site</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Sato Kentarou</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/23296/3/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Asagiri Aya, a girl bullied at school and at home. One day, an eerie website, Mahou Shoujo Site, flashes on her computer screen and welcomes her to the Mahou Shoujo World.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/mahou-shoujo-site-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="platinum end" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Drama, Ecchi, Mature, Mystery, Psychological, School life, Shounen., Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>platinum end</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>platinum-end</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Ohba Tsugumi, Obata Takeshi</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/36176/4/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>The story tells of a human and an angel, and centers around Mirai Kakehashi, a boy who 'does not seek out hope in order to live.'</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/platinum-end-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="p to jk" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Romance, School life, Shoujo." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>p to jk</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>p-to-jk</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Miyoshi Maki</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/27317/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Kako fell in love with Kouta, a guy who saved her in a mixer while she's posing as a 22-year-old girl, only to find out the next day that he's a police officer. Just when they were getting closer to each other, he realized she's actually a high school student and distanced himself from her. But Kako continued her advances and accidentally got injured while protecting him, so he eventually decided to give into his feelings and face the complications of a policeman having a relationship with a high school girl.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/p-to-jk-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="eyeshield 21" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Comedy, School life, Shounen., Sports" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>eyeshield 21</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>eyeshield-21</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Inagaki Riichiro, Murata Yuusuke</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/2658/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Wimpy Sena Kobayakawa has been running away from bullies all his life. But when the football gear comes on, things change--Sena's speed and uncanny ability to elude big bullies just might give him what it takes to become a great high school football hero! Enjoy all the bone-crushing action and slapstick comedy that this heartwarming coming-of-age story has to offer.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/eyeshield-21-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="to you, the immortal" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Adventure, Drama, Fantasy, Supernatural, Tragedy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>to you, the immortal</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>to-you-the-immortal</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Oima Yoshitoki</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/45063/5/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>An immortal being was sent to the surface of the earth and met a boy living alone in the middle of tundra. The being can take the shape of dying things, but only if the 'impetus' is stronger than the previous one. What sort of experiences and meetings will the being encounter while living forever?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/to-you-the-immortal-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="kusumi-kun, kuuki yometemasu ka?" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Romance, School life" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>kusumi-kun, kuuki yometemasu ka?</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>kusumi-kun-kuuki-yometemasu-ka</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Mosuko</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/42058/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Erika Sakura is the school's most popular female high schooler, and only met with envious gazes since she is out of everyone's league. However, she is recently interested in a certain male high schooler who can't read between the lines, Kuzumi. While having a relationship between the two is out of the question, her unrequited love will soon change in this romantic comedy. Follow this new inevitably heart pounding, out-of-contact short love comedy!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/kusumi-kun-kuuki-yometemasu-ka-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="haruka 17" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Drama, Mature, Seinen, Slice of life" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>haruka 17</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>haruka-17</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Yamazaki Sayaka</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/3557/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Haruka is about to graduate from a first-rate college and is looking for work but no one wants to hire her. Faced with the prospect of becoming a 'shuushoku rounin' she finally lowers her expectations and decides to apply at a tiny talent agency for a job as an agent. When she shows up for the interview however, it's like no interview she's ever had before. She's asked all sorts of embarrasing questions and asked to say lines in front of a camera. Later she finds out that they thought she was interviewing to become a talent, and the agent position she wanted has already been given away. However, they think she has that special quality that can make someone a star. She refuses at first, but finally gives in. Thus starts Haruka's career in the entertainment industry.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/haruka-17-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="kakegurui" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Drama, Psychological, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>kakegurui</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>kakegurui</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Kawamoto Homura, Naomura Tooru</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/26758/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Hyakkaou Academy, a prestigious private school. Here in this academy, students are divided into social strata. Standing above all others is the student council, who rules over the students with their Gambles. It's heaven if you win, and hell if you lose. Those adept at gambling are the envy of all, while the weak are left to suffer the madness of the academy. One girl transfers to this academy. Her name is Jyabami Yumeko.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/kakegurui-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="houseki no kuni" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Fantasy, Psychological, Seinen, Tragedy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>houseki no kuni</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>houseki-no-kuni</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Ichikawa Haruko</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/27295/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>In the distant future, a new life form called Houseki (gems) are born. The 28 Houseki must fight against the moon dwellers who want to attack them and turn them into decorations, thus each gem is assigned a role such as a fighter or a medic. Though they hope to fight the moon dwellers, Phos is a gem who is given no assignment until the gems' master Adamantine asks them to edit a natural history magazine.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/houseki-no-kuni-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="radiant" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Comedy, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>radiant</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>radiant</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Tony Valente</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/36054/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Seth is an apprentice sorcerer from the Pompo Hills. Like all sorcerers, he's an 'infected', one of the few people having survived an encounter with a Nemesis, those creatures falling from the sky and destroying everything around them. Being immune to them, Seth wants to become a Hunter and fight the Nemesis. But what Seth really wants is to find the source of all Nemesis, the Radiant. Helped by his fellow sorcerers, he will seek the Radiant, under the harsh scrutiny of the Inquisition...</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/radiant-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="beastars" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Fantasy, School life, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>beastars</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>beastars</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Itagaki Paru</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/47885/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>In a world populated by anthropomorphic animals, herbivores and carnivores coexist with each other. For the adolescences of the Cherryton School, school life is filled with hope, romance, distrust, and uneasiness. The main character is Legosi the wolf, a member of the drama club. Despite his menacing appearance, he has a very gentle heart. Throughout most of his life, he has always been an object of fear and hatred by other animals, and he's been quite accustomed to that lifestyle. But soon, he finds himself becoming more involved with his fellow classmates who have their own share of insecurities and finds his life in school changing slowly.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/beastars-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="chi no wadachi" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Drama, Psychological, School life, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>chi no wadachi</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>chi-no-wadachi</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Oshimi Shuzo</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/47610/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>he illusion of that person leads me astray. Mother and son. This is the ultimate favoritism.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/chi-no-wadachi-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="violence action" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Drama, Mature, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>violence action</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>violence-action</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Sawada Shin, Asai Renji</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/50492/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Are you in need of revenge? Is there someone that you need out of your way? The Pururun All-Natural-Girls Express Service would be more than pleased to help you achieve these things. 'Kay' is one such cute girl that works for Pururun, and when duty calls, she is there to eliminate anyone her client wants -- whether it's with knives, guns, or acid! How did she come to be a killing specialist, what kinds of people will she meet -- and what are her goals?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/violence-action-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
</danh_sach_truyen>