<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<danh_sach_truyen>
	<truyen ten="batman: last knight on earth" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Mystery, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>batman: last knight on earth</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>batman-last-knight-on-earth</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Scott Snyder, Greg Capullo</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/b/batman-last-knight-on-earth/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Bruce Wayne wakes up in Arkham Asylum. Young. Sane. And... he was never Batman. So begins this sprawling tale of the Dark Knight as he embarks on a quest through a devastated DC landscape featuring a massive cast of familiar faces from the DC Universe. As he tries to piece together the mystery of his past, he must unravel the cause of this terrible future and track down the unspeakable force that destroyed the world as he knew it... From the powerhouse creative team of writer Scott Snyder and artist Greg Capullo, the team that reinvented Batman from the emotional depths of 'Court of Owls' to the bombastic power of DARK NIGHTS: METAL, DC Black Label is proud to present the bimonthly, three-issue miniseries BATMAN: LAST KNIGHT ON EARTH. This could be the last Batman story ever told...</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/batman-last-knight-on-earth-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="black cat" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy, Leading ladies, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>black cat</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>black-cat</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jed Mackay, Mike Dowling, Travel Foreman, Nao Fuji</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/b/black-cat-(2019)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The Black Cat is back and starring in her first ever ongoing series! Felicia Hardy has a taste for the finer things in life and a certain set of skills that can get her into any mansion, vault or museum to...procure said finer things. But due to her actions in AMAZING SPIDER-MAN, Felicia's not only on the run from the police but also by the New York Theives Guild and their boss ODESSA DRAKE! High-octane heists, climactic chases and twist after twist that will keep you on the edge of your seat like a cat on a perch. IN THIS ISSUE: Find out a secret from Cat's past in a bonus story that sets a foundation for the future! All this and an all-new MARVEL MEOW short story by Nao Fuji!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/black-cat-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="fallen world" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy, Post-apocalyptic, Sci-fi, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>fallen world</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>fallen-world</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Dan Abnett, Adam Pollina</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/f/fallen-world/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>In the year 4002, a cyborg samurai named Rai struggles to find his morality, while the nanite-filled supersoldier Bloodshot is on a mission to save the citizens of Earth. Will they work together for the greater good? All signs point to no. Oh, and did we mention there are also dinosaurs on the loose and powerful animal-human hybrid mutants? Good luck with that, Rai.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/fallen-world-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="volition" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>volition</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>volition</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Ryan Parrott, Omar Francia</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/v/volition/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>In a not-too-distant future, artificial intelligence has spawned a race of robots that serve all of humanity. Robots are considered second class citizens, but a few in the A.I. community are fighting back in a constant struggle for equal rights. When a debilitating virus called 'Rust' threatens all artificial life, salvation lies in the most unlikely of robotic heroes-not a warrior or a solider, but in an obsolete construction worker and a dedicated caregiver. Together, HALE-19 and AMBER-7T embark on a perilous journey in search of a cure that could potentially change the balance of power on Earth forever.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/volition-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="the dreaming (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>the dreaming (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>the-dreaming-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Brian Wood, Mack Chater</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/the-dreaming-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>There is a place where stories are born. Today its walls lie slashed and bleeding. Dream has abandoned his realm, and until he is found, its residents must protect its broken borders alone. But the most senior storysmiths are tormented by invasive secrets, the warden Lucien is doubting his own mind—and beyond the gates something horrific waits with tooth and talon. Only Dora, the monstress, finds opportunity in madness, stealing dreams for the highest bidder. But she has no idea how deep the danger lies. Meanwhile, in Dream’s gallery, something new is growing...</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/the-dreaming-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="war of the realms strikeforce: the war avengers" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>war of the realms strikeforce: the war avengers</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>war-of-the-realms-strikeforce-the-war-avengers</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Dennis 'Hopeless' Hallum, Ario Anindito, Kim Jacinto</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/w/war-of-the-realms-strikeforce/the-war-avengers_1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>CAPTAIN MARVEL AND HER WAR AVENGERS HOLD THE FRONTLINE! While two other Strikeforce teams head out to other realms, Captain Marvel leads the fight to reclaim the Earth! But even with a crew of heavy hitters (Weapon H, Captain Britain, Venom, Deadpool) and two of the best spies on the planet (the Winter Soldier and the Black Widow), Carol's fighting a losing game. Malekith's allies are without number - and the battlefield bigger than any Carol's commanded before. Time to lay it all out on the line - and fight for a miracle.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/war-of-the-realms-strikeforce-the-war-avengers-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="war of the realms strikeforce: the land of giants" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>war of the realms strikeforce: the land of giants</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>war-of-the-realms-strikeforce-the-land-of-giants</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Tom Taylor, Jorge Molina</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/w/war-of-the-realms-strikeforce/the-land-of-giants_1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>THE GOD OF THUNDER IS TRAPPED IN THE LAND OF ICE AND SNOW...And it's up to Captain America to rescue him before all is lost! Taking up Thor's ax, Jarnbjorn, Cap and his team-Spider-Man, Wolverine, Luke Cage and Iron Fist-invade the Frost Giant realm in search of their fellow Avenger. But this rescue mission will cost far more than they expect.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/war-of-the-realms-strikeforce-the-land-of-giants-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="war of the realms strikeforce: the dark elf realm" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>war of the realms strikeforce: the dark elf realm</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>war-of-the-realms-strikeforce-the-dark-elf-realm</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Bryan Hill, Leinil Francis Yu</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/w/war-of-the-realms-strikeforce/the-dark-elf-realm_1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>THE PUNISHER LEADS THE CHARGE TO SHUT DOWN THE BLACK BIFROST! Deep in the swamps of Svartalfheim stands the Black Bifrost, Malekith's corrupted Rainbow Bridge and the only reliable means of travel between the realms with the true Bifrost in pieces. If the gods are going to stop Malekith's invasion, the Black Bridge must fall. With her son missing and husband injured, Lady Freyja must take up the challenge herself. But she won't go alone. Hulk (Jen Walters), the Punisher, Blade and Ghost Rider follow the All-Mother of Asgard straight into Malekith's home territory!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/war-of-the-realms-strikeforce-the-dark-elf-realm-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="high level" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>high level</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>high-level</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Rob Sheridan, Tom Fowler</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/h/high-level/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Hundreds of years after the world ended and human society was rebuilt from scratch, a self-interested smuggler is forced to traverse a new continent of danger and mystery to deliver a child messiah to High Level, a mythical city at the top of the world from which no one has ever returned. Don't miss the start of a new series from writer Rob Sheridan, co-creator of Nine Inch Nails' groundbreaking Year Zero alternate-reality game!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/high-level-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="books of magic (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Fantasy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>books of magic (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>books-of-magic-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Kat Howard, Barnaby Bagenda</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/b/books-of-magic-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Timothy Hunter may be destined to become the most powerful magician in the universe, but he's still a London teenager and having magical abilities complicates things more than it helps. It's not like he can use magic to pass his exams, stop being bullied, or convince his cute friend to date him. And while Tim's trying to live his life, there are cultists who want to kill him, believing his power will eventually corrupt him, and turn him into a merciless mage. Oh, and those are the good guys.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/books-of-magic-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="batman and the outsiders (2019)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>batman and the outsiders (2019)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>batman-and-the-outsiders-2019</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Bryan Edward Hill, Dexter Soy</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/b/batman-and-the-outsiders-(2019)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>When the quest for justice drives Batman into some morally ambiguous areas, he calls in the most moral man he knows: Jefferson Pierce, a.k.a. Black Lightning, and his team of operatives known as the Outsiders! Several years ago Batman personally put the Barrera family into hiding after they suffered through terrible experiments at the hands of an organization called the Ark. Now all but one of them has turned up dead...and Batman needs to locate Sofia Barrera before the wrong people get their hands on her-and her surprising power! But it wouldn't be Batman without a hidden agenda, would it? And when Black Lightning, Katana, the Signal and Orphan find out what Batman is really up to, their every loyalty will be called into question!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/batman-and-the-outsiders-2019-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="war of the realms: new agents of atlas" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>war of the realms: new agents of atlas</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>war-of-the-realms-new-agents-of-atlas</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Greg Pak, Gang Hyuk Lim</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/w/war-of-the-realms-new-agents-of-atlas/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>A WAR OF THE REALMS TIE-IN! As Sindr, Immortal Queen of Muspelheim, and her legions of Fire Demons march on Asia, it's time for a new band of heroes to unite to protect the Pacific Rim. Having brought together a ragtag team of heroes to defend the Earth from an alien invasion in the past, can Amadeus Cho reassemble his 'protectors' -- Shang-Chi, Silk and Jimmy Woo to save the world from incineration? And where is Kamala Khan? And just who are Crescent, Io and Luna Snow??? Featuring Marvel's newest heroes from China, AERO and SWORD MASTER, and a mysterious new Filipino heroine named WAVE!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/war-of-the-realms-new-agents-of-atlas-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="friendly neighborhood spider-man (2019)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>friendly neighborhood spider-man (2019)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>friendly-neighborhood-spider-man-2019</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Tom Taylor, Juann Cabal, Marcelo Ferreira</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/f/friendly-neighborhood-spider-man-(2019)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Spider-Man is the worst neighbor EVER! There are always crazy villains and property damage and drama and...and he CATCHES the villains. And he tries to fix the damage and he helps carry your groceries and actually that property damage keeps the rents down. You know what? Spider-Man is the best neighbor ever and this book will give you a closer look at Spider-Man's (and Peter Parker's) neighborhood than any book ever. Also, it wouldn't be a Spider-Man adventure without a threat that could destroy not only Spider-Man, but all his neighbors.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/friendly-neighborhood-spider-man-2019-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="league of legends: lux" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Fantasy, Video games" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>league of legends: lux</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>league-of-legends-lux</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>John O'Bryan, Haining And Gadson Of Tan Comics, Billy Tan</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/l/league-of-legends-lux/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>FIRST IN A NEW SERIES THAT EXPLORES AND EXPANDS UPON THE FAN FAVORITE LEAGUE OF LEGENDS LORE! Demacia is a peaceful utopia where order reigns. Maintaining that order at any cost are the Mageseekers, who hunt down anyone utilizing forbidden magic. Hailing from a respected noble family, LUXANNA 'LUX' CROWNGUARD is destined for a life of privilege-but is hiding a terrible secret. As her own magical light powers emerge, Lux must decide whether she stands with brother GAREN and the ruling class of Demacia...or the downtrodden Mages at the fringes of society. Written by Riot Games' John O'Bryan, and illustrated by Billy Tan, Haining, and Gadson of Tan Comics, LUX #1 is all-new adventure exploring another facet Riot Games' LEAGUE OF LEGENDS lore in the Mighty Marvel Manner!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/league-of-legends-lux-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="taarna" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Fantasy, Movies-tv, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>taarna</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>taarna</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Alex De Campi, Esau Escorza, Isaac Escorza, Carlos Cabrera, Alex Ross</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/taarna/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Heavy Metal's iconic warrior debuts in her pulse-pounding new series! A city besieged by demons seeks salvation when a hero from forgotten legends mysteriously arrives...</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/taarna-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="dceased" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>dceased</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>dceased</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Tom Taylor, Trevor Hairsine, James Harren</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/dceased/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>A mysterious techno-virus has been released on Earth, infecting 600 million people and turning them instantly into violent, monstrous engines of destruction. The heroes of the DCU are caught completely unprepared for a pandemic of this magnitude and struggle to save their loved ones first...but what happens to the World's Greatest Heroes if the world ends?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/dceased-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="marvel team-up (2019)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>marvel team-up (2019)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>marvel-team-up-2019</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jason Aaron, Russell Dauterman</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/m/marvel-team-up-(2019)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>THE CLASSIC MARVEL TEAM-UP RETURNS! After a science demonstration at Empire State University goes awry, Ms. Marvel and Spider-Man find themselves tangled up in the same chaotic adventure. Is it destiny? Or disaster?! Eve L. Ewing (IRONHEART) and Joey Vazquez (SPIDER-GEDDON) team up for the first thrilling arc of a mind-bending and magnificent new series!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/marvel-team-up-2019-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="female furies" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>female furies</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>female-furies</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Cecil Castellucci, Adriana Melo</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/f/female-furies/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>All their lives the Female Furies have been raised to be the meanest, most cunning and most ruthless fighting force on all of Apokolips. So why are Granny Goodness' girls left behind every time the men go to war? With the might of New Genesis hanging over the planet, and the Forever People making mincemeat out of Darkseid's army, Granny thinks it's about time that changed. And so, Big Barda, Aurelie, Mad Harriet, Lashina, Bernadeth and Stompa set out to beat the boys at their own game. Little do they know the game is rigged-and one accidental murder could spell disaster for them all!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/female-furies-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="cosmic ghost rider destroys marvel history" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>cosmic ghost rider destroys marvel history</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>cosmic-ghost-rider-destroys-marvel-history</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Nick Giovannetti, Paul Scheer, Gerardo Sandoval</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/c/cosmic-ghost-rider-destroys-marvel-history/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The Cosmic Ghost Rider is stuck in the past, so he might as well have some fun with the origins of the Marvel Universe, right?! After going back in time and trying to kill Thanos as a baby, Frank Castle has sworn off trying to alter history. But when he arrives in Earth's past at the birth of the Fantastic Four, how can he resist jumping in on the fun?!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/cosmic-ghost-rider-destroys-marvel-history-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="the girl in the bay" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Drama, Fantasy, Mature, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>the girl in the bay</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>the-girl-in-the-bay</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>J.M. DeMatteis, Corin Howell</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/the-girl-in-the-bay/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>In 1969, seventeen-year-old Kathy Sartori was brutally attacked, her body hurled into Brooklyn's Sheepshead Bay. Miraculously, she survives and fights her way back to the surface, only to discover that fifty years have passed and an eerie doppelganger has lived out an entire life in her place. Kathy soon confronts not just this strange double, but the madman who 'murdered' her five decades earlier. Will he, and the dark entity that lives inside him, hold the key to Kathy's missing years? Or will Kathy become a ghost of herself, forced to live out what remains of her life on the edge of the world that she desperately wants to be a part of?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Completed/the-girl-in-the-bay-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="war of the realms " tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>war of the realms </ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>war-of-the-realms</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jason Aaron, Russell Dauterman</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/w/war-of-the-realms/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Featuring action-packed extras including a Cover Gallery, Script, Inked And Color Pages and Character Designs! THE WORLD AT WAR! Asgard. Alfheim. Heven. Jotunheim. Muspelheim. Niffleheim. Nidavellir. Svartalfheim. Vanaheim. All of the Ten Realms have fallen to Malekith and his army except one: Midgard. Home to Thor's beloved humans. Home to heroes and gods alike. Now, at last, it burns. And Thor won't even be there to see it. All hell breaks loose in New York City as Malekith and his allies begin their invasion - and the greatest heroes of the Marvel Universe watch as the Earth falls!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/war-of-the-realms-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="war of the realms: journey into mystery" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>war of the realms: journey into mystery</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>war-of-the-realms-journey-into-mystery</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Clint McElroy, Griffin McElroy, Justin McElroy, Travis McElroy, Andre Lima Araujo</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/w/war-of-the-realms-journey-into-mystery/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The creators of the blockbuster podcast The Adventure Zone bring their talents to Marvel for a wild romp through THE WAR OF THE REALMS! Earth is at war, besieged by an army of Frost Giants, Trolls and Fire Goblins - and the mighty Thor is nowhere to be found! But could it be that the key to turning the tide is...Thor's baby sister? Journey into Mystery with Spider-Man (Miles Morales), Hawkeye (Kate Bishop), Wonder Man, and Balder the Brave as they go on an epic quest to save Earth's only hope! (And, yes, deal with diaper duty.)</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/war-of-the-realms-journey-into-mystery-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="war of the realms: war scrolls" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>war of the realms: war scrolls</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>war-of-the-realms-war-scrolls</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jason Aaron, Josh Trujillo, Ram V, Chip Zdarsky, CAFU, Ricardo Lopez Ortiz, Joe Quinones, Andrea Sorrentino</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/w/war-of-the-realms-war-scrolls/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>THE MUST-READ COMPANION TO WAR OF THE REALMS! Gifted the sight of the Bifrost, Daredevil watches all Midgard burn under Malekith's invasion. How will the Guardian of Hell's Kitchen...guard an entire Earth turned to Hell? Find out in a story by Jason Aaron and Andrea Sorrentino! All this and more (including a new Howard the Duck story by Chip Zdarsky and Joe Quinones!), straight from the battlefield of WAR OF THE REALMS!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/war-of-the-realms-war-scrolls-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="war of the realms: the punisher" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>war of the realms: the punisher</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>war-of-the-realms-the-punisher</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Gerry Duggan, Marcelo Ferreira</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/w/war-of-the-realms-the-punisher/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>PUNISHER: AVENGER OF MIDGARD! The War of The Realms has brought monsters to the streets of New York City, but New York has a monster all its own...Frank Castle, A.K.A. THE PUNISHER! And he'll be damned to Hel if he's going to let a bunch of Ten Realms tin-pot tyrants terrorize his town. But given he's one man against an army of monsters, Hel might soon have him! The War of Realms is about to meet Marvel's One Man Army. Expect Punishment!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/war-of-the-realms-the-punisher-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="oz: heart of magic" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>oz: heart of magic</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>oz-heart-of-magic</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Terry Kavanagh, Marcelo Mueller</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/o/oz-heart-of-magic/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Last we saw Dorothy she was trapped in a body that isn't hers by the evil Wizard of Oz, cut off from most of her loyal followers and exiled from the Emerald City. Now on the run through increasingly forbidding lands, with the very heart of the realm itself on the line, will she be able to protect herself and more importantly the people who rely on her?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/oz-heart-of-magic-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="symbiote spider-man" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>symbiote spider-man</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>symbiote-spider-man</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Iban Coello, Greg Land</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/s/symbiote-spider-man/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Everyone knows that Spider-Man's infamous black suit would someday become the wicked web-slinger called Venom - but what happened BEFORE Peter Parker discovered the black suit's sinister secret? Find out in this dynamic tale from comics legends PETER DAVID and GREG LAND! Set during the original 'Black Suit Saga,' this is an all-new tale that pits the wall-crawling wonder against that most mystifying of menaces...MYSTERIO!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/symbiote-spider-man-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="doctor who: the thirteenth doctor" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Movies-tv , Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>doctor who: the thirteenth doctor</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>doctor-who-the-thirteenth-doctor</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Richard Dinnick, Claudia Ianniciello, Mariano Laclaustra, Pasquale Qualano, Giorgia Sposito</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/doctor-who-the-thirteenth-doctor/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The ultimate celebration of Doctor Who - a perfect introduction for new fans and a brilliant tribute for long-time Whovians! When you die, your life flashes before your eyes - and the Doctor's had a lot of lives! The Thirteenth Doctor relives unseen adventures from all her past selves!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/doctor-who-the-thirteenth-doctor-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="ronin island" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Historical, Horror" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>ronin island</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>ronin-island</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Greg Pak, Giannis Milonogiannis</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/r/ronin-island/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>After a mysterious attack wipes out the major cities of 19th century Japan, Korea, and China, survivors from all three lands find refuge on a hidden island and build a new society. Hana, the orphaned daughter of Korean peasants, and Kenichi, son of a great samurai leader, have little in common except for a mutual disdain for the other. But these young warriors will have to work together when an army invades the island with shocking news: there is a new Shogun and the Island is expected to pay fealty in exchange for protection from a new enemy...a mutated horde that threatens to wipe out all humanity. Award-winning writer Greg Pak (Firefly, Mech Cadet Yu) and artist Giannis Milonogiannis (Prophet) present a story that examines how we move forward when our past divides, set against the backdrop of a post-disaster 19th century Japan.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/ronin-island-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="the empty man (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Horror, Mystery" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>the empty man (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>the-empty-man-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Cullen Bunn, Jesus Hervas</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/the-empty-man-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Horror sensation Cullen Bunn (Harrow County, Bone Parish) returns to the world of Empty Man with artist Jesus Hervas (Lucas Stand, Clive Barker's Hellraiser) in this new ongoing series. The nation is in the grip of a terrible pandemic. The so-called Empty Man disease causes insanity and violence. Government quarantines are mandatory. One of the afflicted is Melissa Kerry, and the next step should be to quarantine her-but those who enter quarantine are never seen again. Melissa's family won't let that happen. All they have to do is care for her, keep her worsening condition a secret-and they'll do anything, trust anyone, to keep her safe.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/the-empty-man-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="house of whispers" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Fantasy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>house of whispers</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>house-of-whispers</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Nalo Hopkinson, Dominike 'Domo' Stanton</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/h/house-of-whispers-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Welcome to the House of Dahomey, the houseboat of Erzulie Freda, where the souls of Voodoo followers go when they sleep to beseech the flirtatious and tragic goddess to grant them their hearts' desires and counsel them on their futures and fortunes. When you arrive, you'll find a party is in full swing, filled with all kinds of fabulous and fierce folk, while fish fry and music blasts. From her bayou, Erzulie scries upon the mortal realm and sees four human girls open a mysterious and magical journal filled with whispers and rumors that, if they spread, could cause a pandemic unlike any the Earth has seen, with the power to release Sopona, the loa lord of infectious disease and cousin to Erzulie, who is currently banned from the human plane. But even the fearsome Erzulie cannot be of assistance when her dream river turns tumultuous, tossing her house from her realm and into another...</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/house-of-whispers-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="star wars: vader - dark visions" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Movies-tv, Sci-fi, Space opera" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>star wars: vader - dark visions</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>star-wars-vader-dark-visions</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Dennis 'Hopeless' Hallum, Paolo Villanelli</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/s/star-wars-vader---dark-visions-(2019)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>WHO IS DARTH VADER? He has been many things: a SITH warrior, a commander, a destroyer. DARTH VADER is to many throughout the GALACTIC EMPIRE a symbol of fear and mysterious, otherworldly power. But there are some who have seen the DARK LORD in a different light. There are some corners of the galaxy so dark and desperate that even Vader can be a knight in shining armor. The first issue of a new STAR WARS limited series, writer Dennis Hopeless (CLOAK AND DAGGER, JEAN GREY) sheds new light on the many sides of the galaxy's greatest villain.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/star-wars-vader-dark-visions-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="age of x-man: apocalypse and the x-tracts" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>age of x-man: apocalypse and the x-tracts</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>age-of-x-man-apocalypse-and-the-x-tracts</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Tim Seeley, Salvador Espin</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/a/age-of-x-man-apocalypse--the-x-tracts/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>ENTER THE AGE OF X-MAN! X-Man has created a utopia for mutants... a utopia where no one knows love. Thankfully, a hero rises up to lead the rebellion against this way of life and teach the ways of family and romance, and he goes by the name... EN SABAH NUR?! Join Apocalypse and his rebel X-Tracts as they strive to teach the world to love again!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/age-of-x-man-apocalypse-and-the-x-tracts-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="dial h for hero" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>dial h for hero</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>dial-h-for-hero</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Sam Humphries, Joe Quinones</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/dial-h-for-hero-(2019)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Miguel, a teen daredevil, becomes the newest wielder of the Hero Dial-a rotary phone-like device that grants the user superpowers for one hour when they dial H-E-R-O. Will he rise as a new hero in the DC Universe or crumble under the weight of responsibility the dial thrusts upon him?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/dial-h-for-hero-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="daredevil (2019)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>daredevil (2019)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>daredevil-2019</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Chip Zdarsky, Marco Checchetto</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/daredevil-(2019)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>KNOW FEAR. Featuring action-packed extras including a Cover Gallery, Script, Inked And Color Pages and Character Designs!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/daredevil-2019-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="friendo" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>friendo</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>friendo</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Alex Paknadel, Martin Simmonds</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/f/friendo/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Leo wasn't allowed toys as a kid, but now that he's all grown up he's going to take yours. He used to play by the rules, but then governments and corporations set fire to the rules and still expected him to behave. He probably would have if it hadn't been for his new friend Jerry. See, Jerry isn't human; he's a personalized marketing VR... and he's malfunctioning.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/friendo-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="age of x-man: prisoner x" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>age of x-man: prisoner x</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>age-of-x-man-prisoner-x</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Vita Ayala, German Peralta</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/a/age-of-x-man-prisoner-x/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>ENTER THE AGE OF X-MAN! In the Age of X-Man, when you break the law, you aren't sent to just any prison. You're sent to the Danger Room...a penitentiary filled with the roughest and meanest mutants that don't fit into X-Man's utopia. They each have a reason for being there. And they're all ready to kill each other. But that's about to change, because the newest prisoner just arrived...Lucas Bishop!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/age-of-x-man-prisoner-x-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="meet the skrulls" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>meet the skrulls</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>meet-the-skrulls</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Robbie Thompson, Niko Henrichon</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/m/meet-the-skrulls/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The Warners are your typical family. Dad works at Stark. Mom works in a senator's office. Jennifer and Alice are students at Stamford High School. The only thing that makes them different is that they're shape-shifting Skrulls and have infiltrated our society to pave the way for a Skrull invasion. Robbie Thompson (SPIDER-MAN/DEADPOOL) and Niko Henrichon (DOCTOR STRANGE, Pride of Baghdad) bring the Marvel Universe down to earth with a bold new look at the Skrulls that will test even YOUR loyalty.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/meet-the-skrulls-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="starcraft: soldiers" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>starcraft: soldiers</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>starcraft-soldiers</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jody Houser, Andrew R. Robinson, Miguel Sepulveda</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/s/starcraft-soldiers/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Jody Houser (Stranger Things, Star Wars) joins Blizzard Entertainment writer Andrew R. Robinson (Overwatch Anthology) for issue #1 of StarCraft: Soldiers, the latest addition to the StarCraft expanded universe. Newly graduated Lieutenant Shivani Singh wants to defend the Dominion on the front lines, but it will take more than good grades and confidence to survive on the edge of zerg space.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/starcraft-soldiers-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="invisible kingdom" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>invisible kingdom</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>invisible-kingdom</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>G. Willow Wilson, Christian Ward</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/i/invisible-kingdom/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Set in a in a far-flung star system, this new epic sci-fi monthly saga tells the tale of two women-a young religious acolyte and a hard-bitten freighter pilot-who separately uncover a vast conspiracy between the leader of the system's dominant religion and the mega-corporation that controls society. On the run from reprisals on both sides, this unlikely pair of rebels risk plunging the world into anarchy if they reveal the truth. But when your beliefs betray you, what choice is there left? By Hugo Award-winning writer G. Willow Wilson (Wonder Woman, Ms. Marvel) and Eisner Award-winning artist Christian Ward (Black Bolt, ODY-C).</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/invisible-kingdom-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="criminal (2019)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Crime, Mystery" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>criminal (2019)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>criminal-2019</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Ed Brubaker, Jacob Phillips, Sean Phillips</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/c/criminal-(2019)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>THE RETURN OF THE MOST ACCLAIMED CRIME COMIC OF THE 21ST CENTURY! Hot off their bestselling series KILL OR BE KILLED and their original graphic novel MY HEROES HAVE ALWAYS BEEN JUNKIES, crime comic masters ED BRUBAKER and SEAN PHILLIPS finally return to their most-demanded title -- as a new MONTHLY SERIES! A perfect introduction to CRIMINAL and its dark, exciting world, this series will also include back page art and articles to bring readers more fully into the noir experience.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/criminal-2019-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="captain marvel (2019)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Leading ladies, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>captain marvel (2019)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>captain-marvel-2019</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Kelly Thompson, Carmen Carnero</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/c/captain-marvel-(2019)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>ALL THE STARS ALIGN AS KELLY THOMPSON AND CARMEN CARNERO TAKE ON MARVEL'S PREMIER FEMALE SUPER HERO! As Captain Marvel, Carol Danvers has spent months in space protecting Earth from alien threats big and small, but now it's time for Earth's mightiest hero to come home. New York City has never looked so good. But every re-entry comes with the unexpected, and Carol is about to hit a whole lot of unexpected. It's a fresh start and an oversized, star-studded welcome home for a hero who's been punching the glass ceiling since the 1970s - and just in time for the first female-led film from Marvel Studios! The next 50 years of Captain Marvel starts here!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/captain-marvel-2019-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="age of x-man: the amazing nightcrawler" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>age of x-man: the amazing nightcrawler</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>age-of-x-man-the-amazing-nightcrawler</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Seanan McGuire, Juan Frigeri</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/a/age-of-x-man-the-amazing-nightcrawler/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>ENTER THE AGE OF X-MAN! From the Munich circus to Hollywood Boulevard, Nightcrawler is starring in his own solo series! Kurt Wagner is the biggest celebrity slash super hero since Dwayne Johnson! Juggling Kurt's responsibilities as one of the X-Men and a slate of summer blockbusters would be tough without the best support staff in the business: Stunt coordinator Magma! Personal trainer Kylun! And of course, his leading lady Meggan! But there's something rotten in Tinseltown...</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/age-of-x-man-the-amazing-nightcrawler-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="savage sword of conan" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>savage sword of conan</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>savage-sword-of-conan</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Gerry Duggan, Ron Garney</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/s/savage-sword-of-conan-(2019)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>THE ANCIENT CULT OF KOGA THUN. A MYSTICAL TREASURE. AND THE ONLY MAN WHO CAN SAVE THE HYBORIAN AGE! Adrift at sea. No food. No weapons. Death surely awaits him. But the lionhearted CONAN is not so easily subdued, by Crom! When Conan finds himself captured, he unleashes his might on an unsuspecting pirate crew...one whose dark secrets will plunge Conan on the trail of an ancient treasure that may prove to be his undoing! An all-new age of SAVAGE SWORD OF CONAN begins with a five-part tale of swords and sorcery by Gerry Duggan (DEADPOOL, INFINITY WARS) and illustrated by legendary artist Ron Garney (DAREDEVIL, THOR: GOD OF THUNDER) with covers by the incomparable Alex Ross! Welcome to the deadly Hyborian Age-hope you survive the experience!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/savage-sword-of-conan-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="artifact one" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>artifact one</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>artifact-one</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Vince Hernandez, J.T. Krul, Romina Moranelli</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/a/artifact-one/0_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Introducing Remi, a young and energetic explorer and relic hunter, whose boundless curiosity leads to a startling discovery beyond anything she could have imagined! Along with her alchemist father, Remi works in secret, away from the prying eyes of the ruling clerics who lord over the realms of her world with their ancient decrees and strict devotion. Remi has her own sense of dedication - Her heart to adventure and her mind to the truth. But, what happens when that truth could change the fate of her entire planet, and destroy the very fabric of her civilization? An all-new Aspen Comics action-adventure epic debuts from the mind of creators Vince Hernandez (Michael Turner's Fathom: Kiani, Charismagic) and J.T. Krul (Michael Turner's Soulfire, Jirni) with breathtaking illustrations from newcomer Romina Moranelli!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/artifact-one-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="gretel" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Mystery" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>gretel</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>gretel</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Ben Meares, Allan Otero</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/g/gretel/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Gretel's story has been more nightmare than fairy tale ever since the tragic events of her childhood involving her brother and a maniacal witch. These events have left her cursed with a life that will span centuries. Picking up directly after her heart-wrenching debut in Grimm Universe Presents. After consuming the heart of a psychic witch, Gretel has been gifted the power of premonition. But when she has a psychic vision foretelling the end of the world, Gretel must open old wounds if she wants to try and prevent it from coming true. Introducing a new corner of the Grimm Universe, this will be one series you won't want to miss!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/gretel-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
</danh_sach_truyen>