<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<danh_sach_truyen>
	<truyen ten="black widow (2019)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Leading ladies, Spy, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>black widow (2019)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>black-widow-2019</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jen Soska, Sylvia Soska, Flaviano</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/b/black-widow-(2019)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Natasha Romanoff was trained to kill. For years now she's tried to overcome that programming, to side with the angels...to be a hero. And where'd that get her? Killed. By one of the few true friends she allowed herself to have. Now she's back from the dead, angry as hell and finding those better angels harder and harder to hear. Jen and Sylvia Soska - the Twisted Twins of horror - join rising artist Flaviano to weave a web of vice, violence and vengeance that will net Natasha the biggest bad men she's ever faced... or put her back in the ground for good.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/black-widow-2019-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="barbarella / dejah thoris" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Fantasy, Leading ladies, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>barbarella / dejah thoris</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>barbarella-dejah-thoris</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Leah Williams, German Garcia</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/b/barbarelladejah-thoris/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>From opposite ends of time, two heroines unite for an otherworldly adventure! Barbarella, the siren of space, meets Dejah Thoris, Princess of Barsoom, and together they must solve a murder mystery that spans time and space in order to find their way home. Leah Williams (Adventure Time Comics, X-Men: Black) teams with German García (Action Comics, X-men) for a fun, deadly, mind-bending epic!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/barbarella-dejah-thoris-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="babyteeth" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Horror" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>babyteeth</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>babyteeth</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Donny Cates, Garry Brown</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/b/babyteeth/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Sadie Ritter is sixteen years old, nine months pregnant, and scared out of her sweet nerdy mind. Having a baby that young is tough, but with the support of her loving family behind her, everything should be okay. OH YEAH, and also her baby is the antichrist and it's going to break open the barriers between the earthly and demonic planes and unleash eternal suffering to all of humankind. Other than that, though...should be fine.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/babyteeth-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="invaders (2019)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>invaders (2019)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>invaders-2019</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Chip Zdarsky, Butch Guice, Carlos Magno</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/i/invaders-(2019)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>THE GREATEST GENERATION OF MARVEL HEROES IS BACK - TO STOP ONE OF THEIR OWN! In commemoration of Marvel's 80th anniversary and springing from events in the pages of AVENGERS and THE BEST DEFENSE, the Marvel Universe's first super-team is back! CAPTAIN AMERICA. THE HUMAN TORCH. THE WINTER SOLDIER. NAMOR. They fought in WORLD WAR II together as THE INVADERS. But now NAMOR is the enemy, a global threat more powerful than ever. His deadly plans are as deep and far-reaching as the ocean and REVELATIONS about his past could THREATEN the MARVEL UNIVERSE! It's up to his old teammates to stop him, but what chance do they have against the man who knows their every move? 'War Ghost' begins here!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/invaders-2019-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="young justice (2019)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>young justice (2019)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>young-justice-2019</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Brian Michael Bendis, Patrick Gleason</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/y/young-justice-(2019)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Superboy! Wonder Girl! Robin! Impulse! Amethyst! They're all united in YOUNG JUSTICE #1, the debut issue of a brand-new series that also introduces new heroes Teen Lantern and Jinny Hex! When the nightmare dimension known as Gemworld invades Metropolis, these teen heroes reunite to deal with the situation-but they're shocked to discover the battle may be the key to the return of Conner Kent, a.k.a. Superboy! This mix of fan favorites and new legacy heroes will be the center point for some of the biggest goings-on at DC! As if that weren't enough, Bendis reunites with all-star artist Patrick Gleason (SUPERMAN, ACTION COMICS, GREEN LANTERN CORPS) to bring the new heroes of DC's Wonder Comics to life!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/young-justice-2019-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="infinity wars: infinity warps" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>infinity wars: infinity warps</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>infinity-wars-infinity-warps</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Ryan North, Mariko Tamaki, Jim Zub, Natacha Bustos, Francisco Herrera, Ozgur Yildirim</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/i/infinity-wars-infinity-warps/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>When you gaze into the warp...you get more stories of mad Two-In-One heroes! Read about the Star Siblings of the Warped Universe - MISTER INVISIBLE and HOT ROCKS, the TERRIFIC TWO! Then, see how the covert programs of the Green Room created the gamma-powered GREEN WIDOW! And join MOON SQUIRREL AND TIPPYSAUR as they save the planet from the most dangerous threat it's ever faced!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/infinity-wars-infinity-warps-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="champions (2019)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>champions (2019)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>champions-2019</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jim Zubkavich, Steven Cummings</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/c/champions-(2019)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>THE WORLD STILL NEEDS HEROES - AND THERE ARE HEROES ALL OVER THE WORLD! The Champions have gone global! The team has seen explosive growth under Ms. Marvel's leadership, with super-powered members ready to answer the call in a dozen different countries. They're saving people and improving lives across the planet while they inspire the next generation... but something sinister lurks beneath the surface of their expanded mission. It's a dark secret that could destroy the team and everything they stand for! Jim Zub (AVENGERS: NO SURRENDER, UNCANNY AVENGERS) and Steven Cummings (Wayward, Legends of the Dark Knight) ignite a new era of CHAMPIONS, filled to the brim with action, adventure and drama in the Mighty Marvel Manner!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/champions-2019-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="martian manhunter (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>martian manhunter (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>martian-manhunter-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Steve Orlando, Riley Rossmo</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/m/martian-manhunter-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The acclaimed team of writer Steve Orlando and artist Riley Rossmo (BATMAN / THE SHADOW, BATMAN: NIGHT OF THE MONSTER MEN) reteam for a reinvention of the Manhunter from Mars in this twisted, unexpected series. Back on Mars, J'onn was about as corrupt as a law officer can be, and when a reckoning comes for his entire society, he'll get a second chance he doesn't want or deserve! One shocking murder, and an unexpected fragment of the Mars he lost, will change his life-and the course of the Earth-forever!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/martian-manhunter-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="deadpool (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>deadpool (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>deadpool-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Skottie Young, Scott Hepburn, Nic Klein</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/deadpool-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>MERCIN' FOR A LIVING! Skottie Young and Nic Klein bring you the craziest tales of the Regeneratin' Degenerate yet! It's been a while since Deadpool's had to merc to make ends meet, but things are tough all over. While Deadpool tries to get his humble mercenary-for-hire business back off the ground, a catastrophic threat so unfathomably huge, so mind-breakingly cataclysmic it defies description, is heading toward Earth, and there's only ONE PERSON WHO CAN STOP IT!!! Oh no, wait... it's not Wade, is it? Oh, It's Wade.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/deadpool-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="man without fear" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>man without fear</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>man-without-fear</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jed Mackay, Danilo Beyruth</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/m/man-without-fear-(2019)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Daredevil is gone, but Hell's Kitchen is still a place of heroes and villains. Foggy Nelson will learn what it means to live in a world without a Daredevil. And without a Daredevil to protect it, has hell come for his city? Who is The Man Without Fear?!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/man-without-fear-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="doomsday clock" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>doomsday clock</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>doomsday-clock</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Geoff Johns, Gary Frank, Brad Anderson</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/doomsday-clock/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>DC Comics presents to you a 12-issue maxiseries from the critically acclaimed team of writer Geoff Johns, artist Gary Frank and colorist Brad Anderson. You are not prepared for what lies ahead within these pages, good readers.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/doomsday-clock-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="killmonger" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>killmonger</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>killmonger</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Bryan Hill, Juan E. Ferreyra</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/k/killmonger-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>THE BRUTAL TALE OF A MAN WHO WILL STOP AT NOTHING FOR FREEDOM...One day, Erik Killmonger will rise up and attempt to steal the throne of Wakanda. The throne he believes he is owed. But long before he became 'Killmonger', there was a boy known as N'Jadaka. A boy who was stolen from his home and taught only the world's cruelties. A boy who knew the Black Panther only as a fairy tale, a whisper from strangers. This is the story of a man who is driven by revenge. This is the legend of Killmonger.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/killmonger-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="x-force (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>x-force (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>x-force-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Ed Brisson, Dylan Burnett</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/x/x-force-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>FROM THE ASHES OF EXTERMINATION! Cable is dead...and now, the original X-Force team of Domino, Cannonball, Shatterstar, Boom Boom and Warpath. must hunt down the murderer of their former leader! The mutant militia are hot for blood... but when their target is the time-traveling younger version of their fallen mentor, is there a line they absolutely cannot cross? And what does Deathlok have to do with all of it? From Ed Brisson (EXTERMINATION, OLD MAN LOGAN) and Dylan Burnett (COSMIC GHOST RIDER), comes an all-new, high-octane mutant adventure! A reckoning will come!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/x-force-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="shazam! (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>shazam! (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>shazam-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Geoff Johns, Dale Eaglesham, Mayo 'SEN' Naito</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/s/shazam-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Teenager turned super-hero Billy Batson struggles to balance school and superheroics! (Guess which one is more fun?) But when Shazam unlocks a shocking secret deep within the Rock of Eternity, it challenges everything he knows about the worlds of magic and his family's future as its champions! Also, witness the bizarre team-up of Dr. Sivana and Mr. Mind as they set off to build a society all their own! Don't miss the start of an epic run in the making as 'Shazam and the Seven Realms' begins!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/shazam-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="superior spider-man (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>superior spider-man (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>superior-spider-man-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Christos N. Gage, Mike Hawthorne</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/s/superior-spider-man-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Otto Octavius leaves the moniker of Doctor Octopus behind and once again becomes THE SUPERIOR SPIDER-MAN! If you think you've already read the most intense and surprisingly heartbreaking Superior Spider-Man story, prepare to be wrong. Otto is going to prove to the world that he's the most effective and (to him at least) the best super hero in the world. But when a villain that overpowers him by so much shows up in San Francisco, there's no way Ock can win, right? Can you see Otto smirking from where you're reading this?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/superior-spider-man-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="freedom fighters (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>freedom fighters (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>freedom-fighters-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Robert Venditti, Eddy Barrows</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/f/freedom-fighters-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Line up for this all-new maxiseries set on Earth X, where the Nazis won World War II! Twenty years after invading and occupying America, Germany wiped out all metahuman resistance, including the original Freedom Fighters. Fast-forward to the present day, and a new team of Freedom Fighters emerges to challenge the Nazi occupation once again. But if they're to have any chance of victory, they're going to need Uncle Sam-who disappeared after his original team was killed. The 12-part epic 'Death of a Nation' storyline kicks off here!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/freedom-fighters-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="black panther vs. deadpool" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>black panther vs. deadpool</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>black-panther-vs-deadpool</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Daniel Kibblesmith, Ricardo Lopez Ortiz</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/m/miles-morales-spider-man-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>VIBRANIUM BULLETS AND REGROWING LIMBS - EVERYTHING YOU WANT FROM A COMIC IS HERE! Deadpool's teamed up with, taken down or taken a beating from just about every hero in the Marvel Universe - And no way is the Black Panther going to miss out on his turn! From Late Show writer Daniel Kibblesmith comes a hilarious romp through Wakanda as Deadpool goes on the hunt for the world's most valuable resource: Vibranium! When a beloved figure of the Marvel Universe becomes collateral damage in a fight between Deadpool and the Wrecker, the heroic Deadpool sets out to obtain a fragment of Vibranium that could save the victim's life. But his unconventional methods - ranging from poaching to dismemberment - don't sit well with the King of Wakanda, and Deadpool's about to learn that you don't bring a sword to a claw fight!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/black-panther-vs-deadpool-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="john wick" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Movies-tv, Suspense" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>john wick</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>john-wick</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Greg Pak, Giovanni Valletta</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/j/john-wick/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>When a young John Wick emerges from prison and embarks upon his first, epic vendetta, he comes up against a strange, powerful community of assassins and must learn how to master the Book of Rules that guides their lethal business. What are the Three Bills? Who is Calamity? And who was John Wick before he became the Baba Yaga? Here for the first time, read the thrilling origin story of John Wick, from 'Planet Hulk' writer Greg Pak and 'Dark Horse Presents' artist Giovanni Valletta.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/john-wick-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="miles morales: spider-man" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>miles morales: spider-man</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>miles-morales-spider-man</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Saladin Ahmed, Javier Garron</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/m/miles-morales-spider-man-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Balancing his normal life, school, parents, etc...and super-heroing has never been easy, but when the Rhino and a cadre of mysterious criminals start plaguing Brooklyn, things take a dark turn. And Miles doesn't even know the half of it yet. Eisner Award-winner Saladin Ahmed (BLACK BOLT) and Young Gun Javier Garron (ANT-MAN and THE WASP) bring you the latest incarnation of the coolest character in the Marvel Universe!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/miles-morales-spider-man-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="batman: damned" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Psychological, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>batman: damned</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>batman-damned</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Brian Azzarello, Lee Bermejo</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/b/batman-damned/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The Joker is dead. There is no doubt about that. But whether Batman finally snapped his scrawny neck or some other sinister force in Gotham City did the deed is still a mystery.Problem is, Batman can't remember...and the more he digs into this labyrinthian case, the more his mind starts to doubt everything he's uncovering. So who better to set him straight than...John Constantine? Problem with that is as much as John loves a good mystery, he loves messing with people's heads even more. So with John's 'help,' the pair will delve into the sordid underbelly of Gotham as they race toward the mind-blowing truth of who murdered The Joker.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/batman-damned-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="venom (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>venom (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>venom-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Donny Cates, Ryan Stegman</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/v/venom-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>In the wake of S.H.I.E.L.D.'s collapse, an ancient and primordial evil has been awakened beneath the streets of New York, and with it, something equally evil has awakened in that most Wicked of Webslingers - VENOM! Still a Lethal Protector of the innocents in New York, this never-before-seen threat could force Venom to relinquish everything it holds dear - including Eddie Brock! Join two of the hottest creators in comics today, Donny Cates and Ryan Stegman, for a VENOM adventure a thousand years in the making!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/venom-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="infinity wars: ghost panther" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>infinity wars: ghost panther</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>infinity-wars-ghost-panther</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jed Mackay, Jefte Palo</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/i/infinity-wars-ghost-panther/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Stripped of his kingdom, Prince T'Challa of Wakanda becomes a stunt performer under an assumed name... until a tragic accident and a sinister deal give him the power he needs to free his people!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/infinity-wars-ghost-panther-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="the batman who laughs" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>the batman who laughs</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>the-batman-who-laughs</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Scott Snyder, Jock</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/t/the-batman-who-laughs-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Left rattled by the events of DARK NIGHTS: METAL, Bruce Wayne must come face to face with the nightmares spawned from the Dark Multiverse. But even though evil devoured evil in the collapse of Challengers Mountain, the Dark Knight still has his doubts. He discovers that the Batman Who Laughs not only survived the fight with The Joker at the end of METAL, but now he is enacting a sinister plan across the Multiverse-something both terrifying and oddly familiar. But when Bruce Wayne realizes the only way to stop this madman is to kill him, he must consider violating the very rule Batman won't break...the same rule that created this insatiable villain-the Batman Who Laughs!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/the-batman-who-laughs-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="infinity wars: soldier supreme" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>infinity wars: soldier supreme</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>infinity-wars-soldier-supreme</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Gerry Duggan, Adam Kubert</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/i/infinity-wars-soldier-supreme/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Classified 4-F by the military, Stephen Rogers was unable to serve his country in World War II...until a secret government program tapping into arcane sorcery transformed him into the Soldier Supreme, the magical warrior embodiment of the American spirit!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Completed/infinity-wars-soldier-supreme-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="ironheart" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Leading ladies, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>ironheart</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>ironheart</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Eve Ewing, Kevin Libranda</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/i/ironheart/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>THE FORMER STAR OF INVINCIBLE IRON MAN HEADLINES HER OWN SOLO SERIES! When a group of world leaders is taken hostage by one of Spider-Man's old foes, Riri Williams will have to step up her game. And she'll be stunned when someone from back in Sweet Home Chicago enters her life... CHAMPIONS artist Kevin Libranda joins award-winning poet Eve Ewing, as Ironheart steps boldly out of Tony Stark's shadow to forge her own future!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/ironheart-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="dead man logan" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>dead man logan</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>dead-man-logan</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Ed Brisson, Mike Henderson</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/dead-man-logan/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>DEAD MEANS DEAD. The writing's been on the wall for months now... Logan is dying. And he ain't getting any better. Sick from the Adamantium coating his skeleton, his search for a cure has led to nothing but dead ends. But for once he's actually trying to leave this world with some unfinished business... Can Logan take his last breath without slaughtering the X-Men again? Not if Mysterio has anything to say about it...Superstar creative team ED BRISSON (OLD MAN LOGAN, UNCANNY X-MEN) and MIKE HENDERSON (DEADPOOL VS. OLD MAN LOGAN), with covers by DECLAN SHALVEY (MOON KNIGHT), is putting this old dog out of his misery with a bang!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/dead-man-logan-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="vampirella / dejah thoris" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Crossover, Leading ladies, Sci-fi" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>vampirella / dejah thoris</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>vampirella-dejah-thoris</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Erik Burnham, Ediano Silva</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/v/vampirelladejah-thoris/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The encounter that was destined to happen! When an alien scout ship crashes on Mars, Dejah Thoris must risk reigniting war with the Green Martians and becoming dinner for the white apes. But the stakes are raised so much higher when the ship is revealed to carry Vampirella, who is on a desperate mission of survival-one that might end before it truly begins!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/vampirella-dejah-thoris-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="infinity wars: weapon hex" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>infinity wars: weapon hex</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>infinity-wars-weapon-hex</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Ben Acker, Ben Blacker, Gerardo Sandoval</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/i/infinity-wars-weapon-hex/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>In a dark weapons program breeding subjects specifically for magic use, the 23rd attempt, now called Wanda, was finally able to connect to violent magics - making her one of the deadliest people on the planet!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/infinity-wars-weapon-hex-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="infinity wars: arachknight" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>infinity wars: arachknight</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>infinity-wars-arachknight</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Dennis Hopeless, Ale Garza</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/i/infinity-wars-arachknight/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Chosen as the Avatar of the Spider-Totem, Peter Parker is the dark guardian of destiny doing the bidding of the great weaver of fate... a role that has shattered his mind into multiple personas: a tech genius, a photographer, a teacher...</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/infinity-wars-arachknight-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="spider-gwen: ghost-spider" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Leading ladies, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>spider-gwen: ghost-spider</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>spider-gwen-ghost-spider</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Seanan McGuire, Rosi Kampe</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/s/spider-gwen-ghost-spider-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>A SPIDER-GEDDON TIE IN! What? You thought we were done with Gwen Stacy after the first two landmark volumes of her series?! GET OUTTA HERE. It's a whole new spin on Gwen and her world of Earth-65, brought to you by none other than SEANAN MCGUIRE and ROSI KAMPE! We pick up with Gwen right where we left her - fighting crime through her home reality, unaware that it sits on the precipice of interdimensional calamity! Someone's gonna be late to band practice...</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/spider-gwen-ghost-spider-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="west coast avengers (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>west coast avengers (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>west-coast-avengers-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Kelly Thompson, Stefano Caselli</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/w/west-coast-avengers-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>A NEW ERA DAWNS...AVENGERS ASSEMBLE! HAWKEYE (KATE BISHOP). HAWKEYE (CLINT BARTON). A guy named FUSE. Never have they ever been called 'the big three' of...anything. And now here they are, reunited for, okay, well, it's only the second time ever. Thank god they also brought AMERICA CHAVEZ, GWENPOOL and KID OMEGA. Wait. What? That's right, it's the new West Coast Avengers, son. And you better hope they can figure out how to save the world because BIG things are headed for the West Coast.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/west-coast-avengers-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="robots versus princesses" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Children, Comedy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>robots versus princesses</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>robots-versus-princesses</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Todd Matthy, Nicolas Chapuis</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/r/robots-vs-princesses/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The comic event of the year has arrived! When plucky Princess Zara stumbles upon the Decimator defector Wheeler, she sets in motion events that will pit the spritely cleverness of fairy tale princesses against the raw power of giant robots! The dream match you never thought you'd see begins here. Don't miss it!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/robots-versus-princesses-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="middlewest" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Fantasy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>middlewest</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>middlewest</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Skottie Young, Jorge Corona</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/m/middlewest/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The lands between the coasts are vast, slow to change, and full of hidden magics. Mistakes have been made, and in this NEW ONGOING SERIES, an unwitting adventurer searches for answers to quell a coming storm that knows his name. From author SKOTTIE YOUNG (I HATE FAIRYLAND, Deadpool) and artist JORGE CORONA (NO. 1 WITH A BULLET, Feathers, Big Trouble in Little China: Old Man Jack) comes the tale of Abel, a young boy who must navigate an old land in order to reconcile his family's history.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/middlewest-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="uncanny x-men (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>uncanny x-men (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>uncanny-x-men-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Ed Brisson, Matthew Rosenberg, Kelly Thompson, Mahmud A. Asrar, Mark Bagley, Mirko Colak</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/u/uncanny-x-men-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>THE CHILDREN OF THE ATOM ARE BACK! New ongoing series kicking off with a 10-part weekly epic, the flagship X-Men series that started it all is back and better than ever! Starting with a mysterious and tragic disappearance, the X-Men are drawn into what might be...their final adventure?!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/uncanny-x-men-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="electric warriors" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>electric warriors</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>electric-warriors</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Steve Orlando, Travel Foreman</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/e/electric-warriors/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>A new tale of the future DC Universe, set in a previously unexplored timeline-the Cosmic Dark Age! Years after the Great Disaster, the Earth has started to rebuild and rejoin the universal coalition. In order to prevent a galactic war, different worlds throughout the known cosmos have created a new system of competitive combat to give each participating planet their own voice in the intergalactic struggle. Each world has one diplomatic gladiator, chosen to possess the Electric Seed and fight for their homeland as the Electric Warrior!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/electric-warriors-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="daughters of the dragon (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>daughters of the dragon (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>daughters-of-the-dragon-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jed Mackay, Travel Foreman</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/daughters-of-the-dragon-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>A DOUBLE-SIZED Marvel Digital Original you don't want to miss! MISTY KNIGHT and COLLEEN WING have stolen the shows on Marvel's LUKE CAGE, IRON FIST and DEFENDERS on Netflix and now they have their own MDO series! This duo has been fighting crime as the Daughters of the Dragon for years but with Misty's new job with the FBI, does this mean the two are splitzies? NOT ON YOUR LIFE! A crazy adventure that Colleen initiates puts comics' two greatest ass-kickers on a collision course with a weird and scary side of the Marvel Universe that will have you on the edge of your seat.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/daughters-of-the-dragon-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="batman/the maxx: arkham dreams" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Crossover, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>batman/the maxx: arkham dreams</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>batman-the-maxx-arkham-dreams</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Sam Kieth, John Layman</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/b/batmanthe-maxx/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Batman must face the strangest and most bizarre adventure of his career, as he meets comics' strangest and most bizarre hero... THE MAXX! IDW and DC Comics proudly present the most surreal, quirky, and wonderful crossover of all time! A devious new doctor at Arkham Asylum is conducting unconventional experiments into the human psyche, and he kicks off a chain reaction of disaster when he experiments on Arkham's newest patient, The Maxx! The city of Gotham is starting to merge with The Maxx's psychedelic mental landscape, known as the Outback, blurring the line between real and unreal. It's up to Batman to save not just Gotham, but all of reality, and he and The Maxx are going to have to travel through some of the darkest places imaginable-the twisted minds of Batman's greatest enemies!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/batman-the-maxx-arkham-dreams-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="marvel knights: 20th" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>marvel knights: 20th</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>marvel-knights-20th</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Donny Cates, Travel Foreman</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/m/marvel-knights-20th/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>In celebration of the legendary imprint founded by Marvel's CCO Joe Quesada, a new crop of talent stands poised to tell a groundbreaking story across the Marvel Universe! In the cemetery, the blind man does not know who he is, or why he has come to this particular grave at this moment. He doesn't know the burly police officer with the wild story who has approached him. Or the strangely intense man who sits in the rear seat of the patrol car, his eyes flashing green. But all of that is about to change.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/marvel-knights-20th-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="van helsing: sword of heaven" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy, Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>van helsing: sword of heaven</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>van-helsing-sword-of-heaven</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Chuck Dixon, Julius Abrera</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/v/van-helsing-sword-of-heaven/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Is an ancient weapon feared by every undead creature a myth or a reality? Liesel is willing to risk everything, her life included, to get her hands on the legendary blade that could bring an end to vampirism the world over. Her quest takes her to a remote corner of India and beyond reality on an adventure that could bring her the vengeance she seeks if it doesn't drive her mad first.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/van-helsing-sword-of-heaven-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="x-men: black - emma frost" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>x-men: black - emma frost</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>x-men-black-emma-frost</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Leah Williams, Chris Bachalo</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/x/x-men-black-(2018)/emma-frost_1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>THE DIAMOND DIVA STRIKES BACK! Before she was an X-Man, Emma Frost was White Queen of the Hellfire Club where she labored under the yolk of Sebastian Shaw, the Black King. Now she sets her sights on the club, determined to tear down the organization that wronged her...if she can convince the X-Men to help out. PLUS: Part 5 of X-MEN BLACK: APOCALYPSE!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Completed/x-men-black-emma-frost-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="suicide squad: black files" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>suicide squad: black files</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>suicide-squad-black-files</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Mike W. Barr, Jai Nitz, Phil Briones, Scot Eaton</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/s/suicide-squad-black-files/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Sebastian Faust, the U.S. government's top arcane operative, has gone rogue! To track down America's most dangerous magician, Amanda Waller assembles a special-ops team unlike any other: an expendable coven of dark-arts experts including El Diablo, Enchantress and Gentleman Ghost. They are Suicide Squad Black, and they will take you to places where even the dead can die!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/suicide-squad-black-files-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="runaways (2017)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>runaways (2017)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>runaways-2017</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia> Rainbow Rowell, Kris Anka</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/r/runaways-(2017)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>GET READY TO RUN! The 'IT' book of the early 2000s with the original cast is back - Nico! Karolina! Molly! Chase! Old Lace! And, could it be? GERT?! The heart of the Runaways died years ago, but you won't believe how she returns! Superstar author Rainbow Rowell (Eleanor and Park, Carry On) makes her Marvel debut with fan-favorite artist Kris Anka (ALL-NEW X-MEN, CAPTAIN MARVEL) in the series that will shock you and break your heart!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/runaways-2017-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="heroes in crisis" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>heroes in crisis</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>heroes-in-crisis</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Tom King, Clay Mann</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/h/heroes-in-crisis/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>There's a new kind of crisis threatening the heroes of the DC Universe, ripped from real-world headlines by C.I.A.-operative-turned-comics-writer Tom King: How does a superhero handle PTSD? Welcome to Sanctuary, an ultra-secret hospital for superheroes who've been traumatized by crime-fighting and cosmic combat. But something goes inexplicably wrong when many patients wind up dead, with two well-known operators as the prime suspects: Harley Quinn and Booster Gold! It's up to the DC Trinity of Superman, Wonder Woman and Batman to investigate but can they get the job done in the face of overwhelming opposition?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/heroes-in-crisis-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="spider-force" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>spider-force</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>spider-force</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Christopher Priest, Shane Davis, Siquiera</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/s/spider-force/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>A SPIDER-GEDDON TIE IN! The deadliest task in all of SPIDER-GEDDON has come up and Kaine has stepped forward for what he's sure will be a suicide mission. But he can't do it alone and Jessica Drew, A.K.A. Spider-Woman has signed on to help, but has Kaine told her the whole truth? With Ashley Barton, from the OLD MAN LOGAN universe, and two new characters (Astro-Spider and Spider-Kid), Kaine's team is complete and their first mission may be their last!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/spider-force-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="batman: secret files" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>batman: secret files</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>batman-secret-files</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jordie Bellaire, Cheryl Lynn Eaton, Tom King, Tom Taylor, Ram V, Elena Casagrande, Jorge Fornes, Mikel Janin, Jill Thompson, Brad Walker</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/b/batman-(2016)/secret-files_1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Delve into Batman's case histories and discover brand-new stories by some of comics' most exciting talents. The BATMAN team of Tom King and Mikel Janin provides a framing sequence, setting up our hand-picked teams of creators to take a look at Bat-mysteries past and present. Featuring a bevy of Batman villains, including a look at how the Scarecrow's fear toxin affects the common man, and a special story written by Tom Taylor with art by Brad Walker that teams the Dark Knight Detective with Detective Chimp.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/batman-secret-files-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
</danh_sach_truyen>