<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<danh_sach_truyen>
	<truyen ten="west coast avengers (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>west coast avengers (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>west-coast-avengers-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Kelly Thompson, Stefano Caselli</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/w/west-coast-avengers-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>A NEW ERA DAWNS...AVENGERS ASSEMBLE! HAWKEYE (KATE BISHOP). HAWKEYE (CLINT BARTON). A guy named FUSE. Never have they ever been called 'the big three' of...anything. And now here they are, reunited for, okay, well, it's only the second time ever. Thank god they also brought AMERICA CHAVEZ, GWENPOOL and KID OMEGA. Wait. What? That's right, it's the new West Coast Avengers, son. And you better hope they can figure out how to save the world because BIG things are headed for the West Coast.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/west-coast-avengers-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="robots versus princesses" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Children, Comedy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>robots versus princesses</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>robots-versus-princesses</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Todd Matthy, Nicolas Chapuis</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/r/robots-vs-princesses/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The comic event of the year has arrived! When plucky Princess Zara stumbles upon the Decimator defector Wheeler, she sets in motion events that will pit the spritely cleverness of fairy tale princesses against the raw power of giant robots! The dream match you never thought you'd see begins here. Don't miss it!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/robots-versus-princesses-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="middlewest" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Fantasy" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>middlewest</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>middlewest</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Skottie Young, Jorge Corona</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/m/middlewest/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>The lands between the coasts are vast, slow to change, and full of hidden magics. Mistakes have been made, and in this NEW ONGOING SERIES, an unwitting adventurer searches for answers to quell a coming storm that knows his name. From author SKOTTIE YOUNG (I HATE FAIRYLAND, Deadpool) and artist JORGE CORONA (NO. 1 WITH A BULLET, Feathers, Big Trouble in Little China: Old Man Jack) comes the tale of Abel, a young boy who must navigate an old land in order to reconcile his family's history.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/middlewest-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="happiness" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Drama, Horror, School life, Shounen., Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>happiness</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>happiness</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Oshimi Shuzo</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/30345/6/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Makoto Okazaki is your run of the mill high-schooler, a perfect bullying target and a closet pervert. One night he decides to return a DVD to a friend of his and ventures out into the darkness. He notices a person on a nearby rooftop. The person lunges at him before he is able to make sense of this, and bites into his neck, drinking his blood. The attacker stops. At this point Makoto notices that the attacker is a beautiful girl. She asks him: 'Do you want to die or become like me?' He decides to live...</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/happiness-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="ratman" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Comedy, Ecchi, Romance, School life, Sci-fi, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>ratman</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>ratman</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Inui Sekihiko</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/8106/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Meet Shooto. He's a big hero fan and wants to become a hero! The problem is that he's mocked for being too short. One day, his classmate Mizushima invites him to become a 'hero' at her home which is actually a criminal organization called Jackal. Shooto then gets tricked by Jackal's leader Crea to become their supervillian, Ratman! Now the world's smallest hero will embark on his battle against heroes and villains alike!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/ratman-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="accel world" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Comedy, Drama, Romance, School life, Sci-fi, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>accel world</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>accel-world</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Kawahara reki, Aigamo Hiroyuki</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/300/3/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>No matter how much the times change, bullied kids aren't going anywhere. And fat junior high school student Haruyuki is one of them. But one day, Haruyuki encounters Kuroyukihime, the most beautiful and elegant girl at school, who gives him a mysterious program: 'Brain Burst'...and the secret of the 'Accelerated World.' He may be at the bottom of the food chain at school, but Haruyuki and his destiny begin to 'accelerate' with incredible speed in the virtual realm as he aims for the top.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/accel-world-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="solo leveling" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy, Shounen., Webtoons" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manhwa">
		<ten_truyen>solo leveling</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>solo-leveling</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Jang Sung-Lak, Gee So-Lyung</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-comic-4.anyacg.co/thumbs/w300/85/6f/856fdf5722eabbfe45cf0313d8f663621e74801c_36353_200_270.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>10 years ago, after 'the Gate' that connected the real world with the monster world opened, some of the ordinary, everyday people received the power to hunt monsters within the Gate. They are known as 'Hunters'. However, not all Hunters are powerful. My name is Sung Jin-Woo, an E-rank Hunter. I'm someone who has to risk his life in the lowliest of dungeons, the 'World's Weakest'. Having no skills whatsoever to display, I barely earned the required money by fighting in low-leveled dungeons... at least until I found a hidden dungeon with the hardest difficulty within the D-rank dungeons! In the end, as I was accepting death, I suddenly received a strange power, a quest log that only I could see, a secret to leveling up that only I know about! If I trained in accordance with my quests and hunted monsters, my level would rise. Changing from the weakest Hunter to the strongest S-rank Hunter!</gioi_thieu>
		<file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manhwa_Ongoing/solo-leveling-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="shen yi di nu" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Fantasy, Historical, Romance, Shoujo." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manhua">
		<ten_truyen>shen yi di nu</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>shen-yi-di-nu</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Ping Ping Jun, Yang Shi Liu, Keai Bu Yu</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/49103/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Passing to another world at the sound of duang, divine doctor in both Chinese and western medicine Feng YuHeng became the abused first wife's daughter of Da Shun Dynasty at the fraction of a minute. Wanting to kill me, one scalpel will cause you hemiplegia? Fighting with me? Carrying the pharmacy, holding fame and profit, even the Emperor worms his way into being friends with me! But what is the circumstances with that engagement, a disfigured lame person wall thumbed me, also wanting to help labor and capital to gain the world? Rogue Prince are you foolish!</gioi_thieu>
		<file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manhua_Ongoing/shen-yi-di-nu-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="s. i. d." tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Comedy, Horror, Mystery, Supernatural, Webtoon" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manhwa">
		<ten_truyen>s. i. d.</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>s-i-d</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Sa Da Ham</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-comic-4.anyacg.co/thumbs/w300/63/5b/635bde5404d03ce837dc7f7725c58b8e47990d8a_21004_200_314.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>As a little boy, Si Mun, the grandson of a famous shaman, had the ability to see - and communicate with - ghosts. His grandmother gave him a talisman which temporarily rid him of this ability and erased his memories of any supernatural phenomena he had witnessed. Years later, Si Mun is working a hectic, yet ordinary, job as a homicide detective in the Korean police force. His grandmother has since passed on - and the powers she sealed away appear to be reawakening...</gioi_thieu>
		<file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manhwa_Ongoing/s-i-d-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="uncanny x-men (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>uncanny x-men (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>uncanny-x-men-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Ed Brisson, Matthew Rosenberg, Kelly Thompson, Mahmud A. Asrar, Mark Bagley, Mirko Colak</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/u/uncanny-x-men-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>THE CHILDREN OF THE ATOM ARE BACK! New ongoing series kicking off with a 10-part weekly epic, the flagship X-Men series that started it all is back and better than ever! Starting with a mysterious and tragic disappearance, the X-Men are drawn into what might be...their final adventure?!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/uncanny-x-men-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="electric warriors" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>electric warriors</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>electric-warriors</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Steve Orlando, Travel Foreman</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/e/electric-warriors/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>A new tale of the future DC Universe, set in a previously unexplored timeline-the Cosmic Dark Age! Years after the Great Disaster, the Earth has started to rebuild and rejoin the universal coalition. In order to prevent a galactic war, different worlds throughout the known cosmos have created a new system of competitive combat to give each participating planet their own voice in the intergalactic struggle. Each world has one diplomatic gladiator, chosen to possess the Electric Seed and fight for their homeland as the Electric Warrior!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/electric-warriors-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="daughters of the dragon (2018)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>daughters of the dragon (2018)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>daughters-of-the-dragon-2018</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Jed Mackay, Travel Foreman</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/d/daughters-of-the-dragon-(2018)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>A DOUBLE-SIZED Marvel Digital Original you don't want to miss! MISTY KNIGHT and COLLEEN WING have stolen the shows on Marvel's LUKE CAGE, IRON FIST and DEFENDERS on Netflix and now they have their own MDO series! This duo has been fighting crime as the Daughters of the Dragon for years but with Misty's new job with the FBI, does this mean the two are splitzies? NOT ON YOUR LIFE! A crazy adventure that Colleen initiates puts comics' two greatest ass-kickers on a collision course with a weird and scary side of the Marvel Universe that will have you on the edge of your seat.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/daughters-of-the-dragon-2018-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="flying witch" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Fantasy, Shounen., Slice of life, Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>flying witch</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>flying-witch</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Ishizuka Chihiro</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/2769/3/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Kowata Makoto is an airhead with a bad sense of direction who just moved into her relative's house but is that all? A manga about the coming of age of a witch in modern day japan.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/flying-witch-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="nanba mg5" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Comedy, Drama, School life, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>nanba mg5</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>nanba-mg5</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Ozawa Toshio</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-comic-5.anyacg.co/thumbs/w300/e7/68/e768083f1f755f2ef4e5e5ddb703722e6dbcaa5e_18516_200_310.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Born in a family of delinquents, Nanba Tsuyoshi is expected to succeed his older brother as the strongest delinquent in school. Unbeknownst to his family however, he decides to enroll in the top high school in town to live as a normal high schooler. Can he maintain his double life as the strongest delinquent in town and as a normal high schooler?</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/nanba-mg5-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="enigma" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Adventure, Drama, Horror, Mystery, Psychological, Shounen., Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>enigma</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>enigma</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Sakaki Kenji</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/2586/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Haiba Sumio is a student at a Tokyo High School with an interesting ability... He occasionally falls asleep and wakes up with premonitions of the future written out on his 'Dream Diary'. With this ability, Sumio helps out people in trouble before anything bad happens, until one day when his peaceful life completely changes.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/enigma-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="batman/the maxx: arkham dreams" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Crossover, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>batman/the maxx: arkham dreams</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>batman-the-maxx-arkham-dreams</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Sam Kieth, John Layman</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/b/batmanthe-maxx/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Batman must face the strangest and most bizarre adventure of his career, as he meets comics' strangest and most bizarre hero... THE MAXX! IDW and DC Comics proudly present the most surreal, quirky, and wonderful crossover of all time! A devious new doctor at Arkham Asylum is conducting unconventional experiments into the human psyche, and he kicks off a chain reaction of disaster when he experiments on Arkham's newest patient, The Maxx! The city of Gotham is starting to merge with The Maxx's psychedelic mental landscape, known as the Outback, blurring the line between real and unreal. It's up to Batman to save not just Gotham, but all of reality, and he and The Maxx are going to have to travel through some of the darkest places imaginable-the twisted minds of Batman's greatest enemies!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/batman-the-maxx-arkham-dreams-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="marvel knights: 20th" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>marvel knights: 20th</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>marvel-knights-20th</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Donny Cates, Travel Foreman</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/m/marvel-knights-20th/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>In celebration of the legendary imprint founded by Marvel's CCO Joe Quesada, a new crop of talent stands poised to tell a groundbreaking story across the Marvel Universe! In the cemetery, the blind man does not know who he is, or why he has come to this particular grave at this moment. He doesn't know the burly police officer with the wild story who has approached him. Or the strangely intense man who sits in the rear seat of the patrol car, his eyes flashing green. But all of that is about to change.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/marvel-knights-20th-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="van helsing: sword of heaven" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Fantasy, Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>van helsing: sword of heaven</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>van-helsing-sword-of-heaven</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Chuck Dixon, Julius Abrera</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/v/van-helsing-sword-of-heaven/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Is an ancient weapon feared by every undead creature a myth or a reality? Liesel is willing to risk everything, her life included, to get her hands on the legendary blade that could bring an end to vampirism the world over. Her quest takes her to a remote corner of India and beyond reality on an adventure that could bring her the vengeance she seeks if it doesn't drive her mad first.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/van-helsing-sword-of-heaven-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="akb49 - renai kinshi jourei" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Drama, Ecchi, Gender bender, Romance, Shounen." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>akb49 - renai kinshi jourei</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>akb49-renai-kinshi-jourei</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Motoazabu Factory, Miyajima Reiji</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/505/3/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>This series is about a guy called Urakawa Minoru crossdressing as a girl to participate in a female idol group audition (akb48). The main objective is to help the girl he likes, Yoshinaga Hiroko, pass the audition. Yoshinaga Hiroko's dream is to become like her favorite idol who is in the akb48 group. This audition happens to be her final try, so Minoru crossdresses as Minori and took part in the audition to make sure she realizes her dream. Hiroko got qualified eventually, however, the shocking news was Minoru was qualified as well. Thus, the road to becoming a female idol begins...</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/akb49-renai-kinshi-jourei-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="kurosagi" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Drama, Mystery, Psychological, Seinen" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>kurosagi</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>kurosagi</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Takeshi Natsuhara, Kuromaru</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/5535/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>White swindlers (shirosagi) are those that cheat people to take their money, red swindlers (akasagi) are those that swindle the opposite sex, and black swindlers (kurosagi) are those that cheat the white and red swindlers. After his family is swindled by white swindlers, Kurosaki sets out to avenge them by becoming a black swindler. Kurosagi won the 2008 Shogakukan Manga Award for seinen/general manga along with Tetsuji Sekiya's Bambino!.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/kurosagi-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="mahou shoujo site" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Drama, Horror, Mature, Mystery, School life, Shounen., Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>mahou shoujo site</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>mahou-shoujo-site</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Sato Kentarou</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/23296/3/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Asagiri Aya, a girl bullied at school and at home. One day, an eerie website, Mahou Shoujo Site, flashes on her computer screen and welcomes her to the Mahou Shoujo World.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/mahou-shoujo-site-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="x-men: black - emma frost" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>x-men: black - emma frost</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>x-men-black-emma-frost</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Leah Williams, Chris Bachalo</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/x/x-men-black-(2018)/emma-frost_1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>THE DIAMOND DIVA STRIKES BACK! Before she was an X-Man, Emma Frost was White Queen of the Hellfire Club where she labored under the yolk of Sebastian Shaw, the Black King. Now she sets her sights on the club, determined to tear down the organization that wronged her...if she can convince the X-Men to help out. PLUS: Part 5 of X-MEN BLACK: APOCALYPSE!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Completed/x-men-black-emma-frost-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="suicide squad: black files" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>suicide squad: black files</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>suicide-squad-black-files</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia>Mike W. Barr, Jai Nitz, Phil Briones, Scot Eaton</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/s/suicide-squad-black-files/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>Sebastian Faust, the U.S. government's top arcane operative, has gone rogue! To track down America's most dangerous magician, Amanda Waller assembles a special-ops team unlike any other: an expendable coven of dark-arts experts including El Diablo, Enchantress and Gentleman Ghost. They are Suicide Squad Black, and they will take you to places where even the dead can die!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/suicide-squad-black-files-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="runaways (2017)" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Adventure, Superhero" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Comic">
		<ten_truyen>runaways (2017)</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>runaways-2017</ma_truyen>
        <tac_gia> Rainbow Rowell, Kris Anka</tac_gia>
        <tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://comicbookroundup.com/img/covers/r/runaways-(2017)/1_medium.jpg</hinh_nho>
        <gioi_thieu>GET READY TO RUN! The 'IT' book of the early 2000s with the original cast is back - Nico! Karolina! Molly! Chase! Old Lace! And, could it be? GERT?! The heart of the Runaways died years ago, but you won't believe how she returns! Superstar author Rainbow Rowell (Eleanor and Park, Carry On) makes her Marvel debut with fan-favorite artist Kris Anka (ALL-NEW X-MEN, CAPTAIN MARVEL) in the series that will shock you and break your heart!</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Comic_Ongoing/runaways-2017-eng.xml</file_xml>
    </truyen>
	<truyen ten="platinum end" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Drama, Ecchi, Mature, Mystery, Psychological, School life, Shounen., Supernatural" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>platinum end</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>platinum-end</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Ohba Tsugumi, Obata Takeshi</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/36176/4/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>The story tells of a human and an angel, and centers around Mirai Kakehashi, a boy who 'does not seek out hope in order to live.'</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/platinum-end-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="p to jk" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Comedy, Romance, School life, Shoujo." nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>p to jk</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>p-to-jk</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Miyoshi Maki</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/27317/2/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Kako fell in love with Kouta, a guy who saved her in a mixer while she's posing as a 22-year-old girl, only to find out the next day that he's a police officer. Just when they were getting closer to each other, he realized she's actually a high school student and distanced himself from her. But Kako continued her advances and accidentally got injured while protecting him, so he eventually decided to give into his feelings and face the complications of a policeman having a relationship with a high school girl.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Ongoing/p-to-jk-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="eyeshield 21" tinh_trang_truyen="het" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Comedy, School life, Shounen., Sports" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manga">
		<ten_truyen>eyeshield 21</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>eyeshield-21</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Inagaki Riichiro, Murata Yuusuke</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Completed</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/2658/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Wimpy Sena Kobayakawa has been running away from bullies all his life. But when the football gear comes on, things change--Sena's speed and uncanny ability to elude big bullies just might give him what it takes to become a great high school football hero! Enjoy all the bone-crushing action and slapstick comedy that this heartwarming coming-of-age story has to offer.</gioi_thieu>
        <file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manga_Completed/eyeshield-21-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="hunter age" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Adventure, Comedy, Fantasy, Romance" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manhua">
		<ten_truyen>hunter age</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>hunter-age</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Firepower Panda</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>http://avatar.mkklcdnv2.com/avatar_manga/21553-tf917684.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>A naive youngster, ignorant of the tragedy that happened 16 years ago, travels with the sworn enemy of his tribe; a Princess out on an excursion, due to the internal conflicts within the royal family, has to risk her life and survive in the mountains; A prodigy carrying the hopes of the entire tribe, at this very moment, doesn't have much time left in this world... The 3 of them meet in a world fraught with dangers, will they be able to free themselves from their accursed fate?</gioi_thieu>
		<file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manhua_Ongoing/hunter-age-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="hardcore leveling warrior" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Action, Shounen., Webtoons" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manhwa">
		<ten_truyen>hardcore leveling warrior</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>hardcore-leveling-warrior</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Kim Se Hun</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-thumb.mpcdn.net/38858/1/200.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>'Those who clear quests, shall receive everything.' An RPG adventure with Hardcore Leveling Warrior and his allies, set in a lucid reality.</gioi_thieu>
		<file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manhwa_Ongoing/hardcore-leveling-warrior-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
	<truyen ten="immortal merchant" tinh_trang_truyen="con" nhan_the_loai="Genre(s)" nhan_tinh_trang="Status" nhan_tac_gia="Author(s)" nhan_gioi_thieu="Summary" the_loai="Adventure, Comedy, Fantasy, Harem" nhan_kieu_truyen="Type" kieu_truyen="Manhua">
		<ten_truyen>immortal merchant</ten_truyen>
		<ma_truyen>immortal-merchant</ma_truyen>
		<tac_gia>Liuhua Man Chuang Tu</tac_gia>
		<tinh_trang>Ongoing</tinh_trang>
        <hinh_nho>https://file-comic-4.anyacg.co/thumbs/w300/fd/88/fd8805a34c74666e7c48f37baf83233d36de62ab_29238_200_280.jpg</hinh_nho>
		<gioi_thieu>Other people cultivate I open my store, other people shut in and cultivate I go for bidding sales, people tease me full of bronze smell, I tease other people full of fakes pride/honour, looking at those upper deities have to kneel down and negotiate with me makes me happy... watch me using gold silver jade to make my dao...</gioi_thieu>
		<file_xml>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/tttuploaddigital/TT_du_lieu/master/Manhua_Ongoing/immortal-merchant-eng.xml</file_xml>
	</truyen>
</danh_sach_truyen>